<planetinfos>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>0</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Citadel</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Supposedly constructed by the long-extinct Protheans, this colossal deep-space station serves as the capital of the Citadel Council. Gravity is simulated through rotation, and is a comfortable 1.02 standard Gs on the Wards and a light 0.3 standard Gs on the Presidium Ring. (Small sections of graffiti have been found in station sub-structures, suggesting that perhaps the Protheans were not responsible for the bulk of construction. Bemused maintenance workers report that the graffiti is often a variation of ‘Keeper #13489317498813789 was here.’)

TRAVEL ADVISORY: Due to new Citadel regulations, ‘down the shaft’ is no longer an acceptable vector when speaking with Traffic Control. There are also no fish in the Presidium.

TRAVEL ADVISORY: Elevators to and from the Presidium are currently experiencing issues and are operating at minimum speeds, please plan accordingly. If you are in need of urgent transportation, please use the Citadel shuttles or use the stairs.

Total Length (Open): 44.7 km
Diameter (Open): 12.8 km
Population:  13.2 million (not including keepers)
Gross Weight: 7.11 billion metric tons
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>true</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>1</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>*Placeholder*</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>*Placeholder*</PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>2</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mercury</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Initial exploration on Mercury was limited by the planet's proximity to the sun. However, a probe sent into the atmosphere transmitted images of development on the surface. Most were of blocky, unremarkable ruins. However, a large triangular super-structure was clearly visible in one of the images. Later attempts at investigation were unsuccessful, as the probes simply disappeared upon contact with the super-structure. Several solar power stations were eventually established. All but a few seem to have collapsed into the mass of blocks and rubble.

Population: 340

Orbital Distance: 0.39 AU
Orbital Period: 88 Earth Days
Radius: 2440 km
Day Length: 58.7 Earth Days
Atmospheric Pressure: Trace
Surface Temperature: 430 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.38 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>3</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Venus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Due to the inhospitable atmosphere, development on Venus has been limited to research facilities. A small company known as Au Raa holds most of the rights to the planet. Information on this company is not available to the general public. As such, the nature of their research facilities is a topic of much speculation, with the most popular rumors involving manipulation of the human genome. However, this cannot be substantiated and the sulphuric atmosphere of the planet deters any long-range scanning from curious eyes.

Population: 800

Orbital Distance: 0.72 AU
Orbital Period: 224.7 Earth Days
Radius: 6052 km
Day Length: 243 Earth Days
Atmospheric Pressure: 90 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 465 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>true</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>4</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Earth</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
For detailed information, please refer to the standard issue Alliance Galactic Codex. Please note: the section regarding ‘Flat Earth and You’ is no longer up to date, as it was discovered just last year that the planet is not, in fact, a giant disc supported by four elephants and floating through space on the back of a giant turtle.

Population (Surface): 11.4 billion
Population (L4 and L5 stations): 250,000

Orbital Distance: 1 AU
Orbital Period: 1 Earth Years
Radius: 6378 km
Day Length: 23.9 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 23 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>5</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mars</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Mars was once the future hope of humanity, as wars and resource shortages made life on Earth ever more untenable. However, the first scientific teams sent to the planet discovered that terraforming on a massive scale had turned the planet into an unstable warren of tunnels, inhabited by a massive worm. Carvings found in caves on the surface suggest that the as-yet unknown inhabitants of the planet may have formed a cult, worshipping this worm as their god.

Colony Founded: 2103
Population: 3.4 million
Capital: Lowell City

Orbital Distance: 1.52 AU
Orbital Period: 1.88 Earth Years
Radius: 3402 km
Day Length: 24.6 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.06 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -138 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.38 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>6</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Jupiter</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Jupiter's deep gravity well and lethal radiation have prevented any signficant exploration of the planet. Some of the moons have been developed, with the largest outpost belonging to SST Laboratories, located on Ganymede. Most commonly associated with their Siege Automatons, the company has fallen out of favor in recent years due to Automaton usage in a major Earth crisis. Several abandoned B73 models can be seen littering the upper atmosphere of the moon.

Population (all moons): 9100

Orbital Distance: 5.2 AU
Orbital Period: 11.7 Earth Years
Radius: 71,492 km
Day Length: 9.93 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>7</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Saturn</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Saturn has been a major source of helium-3 fuel for fusion plants since the 2150s. The moon of Titan is mined for hydrocarbons, and used as a hostile environment training facility for Alliance Marines. The rings of Saturn are littered with shredded ship remains, as competitive racing along the rings has proliferated.

Population (orbitals and Titan): 117,000
Capital: Huygens Dome

Orbital Distance: 9.5 AU
Orbital Period: 29.5 Earth Years
Radius: 60,268 km
Day Length: 10.3 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>8</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Uranus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
After the development of mass effect FTL drive, distant Uranus was the target of a "land rush" to exploit its combination of plentiful helium-3 fuel and shallow (for a gas giant) gravity well. Today Uranus is the largest producer of He-3 in Alliance space. Probing is the most common way to extract gas and other useful resources from the  gas giant’s exterior, but some deep investigative vessels have also attempted to extract denser gases from farther within the planet. Most attempts have proven unsuccessful as commercial-grade fuel tanks are unable to sustain the pressure and result in a blow out.

Population: 371,000
Capital: Sakharov Station

Orbital Distance: 19.2 AU
Orbital Period: 121.1 Earth Years
Radius: 25,559 km
Day Length: 17.3 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>9</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Neptune</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Neptune is an advanced training facility for combat operations. While used heavily by the Alliance, it is a commercial offering, permitting training for both military and non-military personnel. Through the use of cutting edge simulation technology, training can be done with very high degrees of realism, with low potential psychological impact on the participants in the event of a catastrophic failure. Their most famous simulation takes place in a crashed subway station, aptly named Firebase Neptune. This simulation is designed to improve the participants resistance to optical attacks on the battlefield by utilizing purple and white squares to represent walls and ceilings. Viewers of this simulation often call this "Eyebleed".

Population (Triton): 70

Orbital Distance: 29.1 AU
Orbital Period: 164.8 Earth Years
Radius: 24,764 km
Day Length: 16.1 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>10</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pluto</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Pluto is the gravitational "anchor" for the Prothean mass relay to Arcturus. Pluto and the Charon Relay (formerly encased in ice, and considered a moon) orbit each other. Pluto was stripped of its planetary status in the year 2006 after leading scientists on the systems capital planet, Earth, started betting on an ancient sports game known as "Curling". Leaders from multiple countries disagreed with the decision, but were unable to change course as the lead scientists of space at the time were bound by their bet. Today, Pluto is little more than a staging ground for the Charon Mass Relay.

Population (gateway stations): 9300

Orbital Distance: 39.5 AU
Orbital Period: 247.7 Earth Years
Radius: 1151 km
Day Length: 9.4 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: Trace
Surface Temperature: -229 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.06 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>11</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Luna</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
An early source of helium-3, Luna is now mined for materials used in space habitat construction. A folk legend from before space travel in the Sol system once described Luna as being made of cheese, of which kind being debated widely among the population of Earth. While it has long been proven that Luna is in fact not made out of cheese, Neil Armstrong, the first human to step foot on Luna, is said to have thrown a wheel of cheese out of his landing craft upon first touchdown in 1969, in commemoration of this legend. While the wheel has never been recovered, it was supposedly of the Gouda variety. When asked why he chose this type, Neil supposedly replied with  "It is simply the best kind of cheese".

Colony Founded: 2069
Population: 4.1 million
Capital: Armstrong

Orbital Distance:  384,403 km (from Earth)
Orbital Period: 27.3 Earth Days
Radius: 1737 km
Day Length: 27.3 Earth Days
Atmospheric Pressure: Trace
Surface Temperature: -53 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>12</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Corporate investment of the asteroid belt is at all time high due to discovery of a new element, adamantium. Considered one of the hardest minerals known in the galaxy, mining it has proved elusive for even the most powerful explosives. Some asteroids have been hauled away to be used directly as projectiles in warfare.

Orbital Distance: 1.8 to 4.5 AU
Population: 11,000
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>13</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Eden Prime</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Dorstonis</PlanetName2>
    <PlanetDescription>
This pastoral world marks the founding of the first Earth colony beyond a mass relay. The biosphere, though slightly thin, is well-suited to both humans and native Earth species. The original Systems Alliance colony was soon augmented by the arrival of corporate developments. Most notable of these was Ondore Lhusu’s discovery of the magicite mines, now a major export and source of revenue. The bulk of the development on %PLANETNAME% is still primarily agricultural, however, and the rolling green hills would not look out of place on Earth.

Colony Founded: 2152
Population: 3.7 million
Capital: Bhujerba

Orbital Period: 2.5 Earth Years
Radius: 7026 km
Day Length: 64.1 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.45 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 23 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.04 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>true</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>14</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Neo Arcadia</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A hostile and closed off world, Neo Arcadia was once a world filled with lush forests and deep blue oceans. Technology use on Neo Arcadia advanced too rapidly for sustainability, eventually plunging the world into multiple devastating wars spanning hundreds of years.

Today Neo Arcadia is the name of the capital city, the only remaining hospitable place on the planet. Facing an energy crisis to power their remaining technologies, the leadership is in a civil war with a resistance force that is attempting to solve the energy crisis.

Attempts to intervene and stop the war have proven unsuccessful, and other space faring species have found little success in their attempts to negotiate trade deals.

Orbital Period: 0.6 Earth Years
Radius: 10893 km
Day Length: 25.6 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 16.17 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 358 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 5.0 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>true</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>15</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Corneria</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Corneria, the fourth planet of the %SYSTEMNAME% system, is an Earth-like terrestrial world primarily used for farming. It is the most populated planet in the system, with the majority of the population living in the mountain ranges that have rich soils for farming. The capital city has been targeted multiple times by terrorists in recent years as several parties from opposing political factions have attempted to conquer the planet.

Population: 2.2 Billion

Orbital Period: 52.8 Earth Years
Radius: 74,333 km
Day Length: 10.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>true</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>16</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Titania</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Millions of years ago, Titania was a once beautiful planet, with a thriving ecosystem full of intelligent, non-space faring life. A meteor impact with the planet reduced the paradise world to the arid desert it can be seen as today. Scientific expeditions by the asari have found remains of a civilization from some of the ancient races, however most intact pieces are thought to be buried deep under layers of ancient ash.

Orbital Period:	129.9 Earth Years
Radius: 3212 km
Day Length: 63.9 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.02 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -203 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>17</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Venom</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A world once considered a possible golden planet, Venom now serves as a reminder about the dangers of terraforming uncharted worlds. Decades ago during an advanced terraforming experiment, multiple catastrophic events chained into one other, turning plans for a new paradise world into an evacuation.

Venom’s oceans are now highly acidic, toxic to all but the most hearty of creatures. The majority of the planet’s surface is in low light or complete darkness, due to a constant thin layer of toxic smog in the atmosphere that killed off most surface dwelling organisms.

Venom now acts as a popular death trap world, where all who are unfortunate enough to be stranded, are doomed to die a painful death.

Known surviving population: 1
Orbital Period: 1029.9 Earth Years
Radius 3730 km
Day Length: 69.8 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.19 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -216 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.3 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>18</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Noveria</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Grunty Industries</PlanetName2>
    <PlanetDescription>
%PLANETNAME% is a small, frozen terrestrial world, barely habitable by conventional definitions. It is privately run by the %PLANETNAME% Development Corporation, which controls the production facilities that cover the planet. Due to the significant overcrowding of factories on the planet, pollution is widespread, some factories even being surrounded by toxic moats.

Secret investigations into the factories have surfaced pictures of incredibly dangerous working conditions, including multiple broken windows going unrepaired, an open elevator shaft that several workers have died in, and a sentient blowtorch that lives in the basement of one of the facilities.

Colony Founded: 2000
Population: 2,200
Planetary leader: Gruntilda Winkybunon

Orbital Distance: 0.9 AU
Orbital Period: 0.9 Earth Years
Radius: 5656 km
Day Length: 52.0 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.87 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -1 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.81
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>19</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Arrakis</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Arrakis has constant wind storms blowing across the surface due to its planetary tilt. Millenia of windstorms has eroded the surface crust down to a fine dust, which is carried around the planet on a near constant basis. With only trace amounts of natural precipitation, colonization attempts have proven to be tough for nearly all races, leaving Arrakis as a quiet, oft forgotten world.

Orbital Period: 0.2 Earth Years
Radius: 32,285 km
Day Length: 13.4 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>20</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Outset</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Outset is a water world, with over 99% of its surface covered in ocean. Many small islands near the equator mark the only habitable areas for terrestrial life. Orbital scans show several underwater anomalies, but without further investigation, these items remain a mystery.

Orbital Distance: 6.3 AU
Orbital Period: 17.7 Earth Years
Radius: 1089 km
Day Length: 17.7 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.1 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 20 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.89 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>true</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>21</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Oswald</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Oswald is a private world, with little known about the planetside business conducted by its owner, Binary Helix. Named after an invention of the original corporation’s founder in the 1900s, Oswald is a quiet world. Orbital scans show multiple planetary defense installations on at least 6 different regions of the planet.

Orbital Distance: 24.5 AU
Orbital Period: 136.3 Earth Years
Radius: 7547 km
Day Length: 62.0 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.07 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -220 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>true</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>22</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Tallon IV</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
51 years ago, Tallon IV was impacted by a small meteorite that crashed into the northern hemisphere of the planet. In the years that followed, mutations of the local wildlife have rapidly increased, with the planet’s wildlife becoming increasingly hostile to visitors. Scientific instruments on the surface of the planet indicate a large radioactive energy source at the planet’s core, which has been steadily increasing over time.

Orbital Period: 97.3 Earth Years
Radius: 5756 km
Day Length: 21.8 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.79 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 28 Celsius
Surface Gravity:  0.97 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>23</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Aether</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Aether is a rogue planet in the %SYSTEMNAME% system, home to the Luminoth. Fifty years ago, a meteorite crashed into Aether with unusual force, destroying the planet's natural beauty. Shortly after the impact, all communication to the planetary leadership was lost, and teams sent by the Citadel Council to investigate never returned. Orbital scans indicate there has been no recent planetside activity by intelligent species.

WARNING: This planet has been marked as hostile to lifeforms by the Citadel Council. Landing on this planet is not permitted.

Orbital Period: 5.8 Earth Years
Radius: 4905 km
Day Length: 55.2 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 2.1 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 24 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>24</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Bespin</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Bespin is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant with traces of ammonia. Hydrocarbons in the atmosphere lend it a distinct tint. Thousands of gas mining stations litter the high atmosphere.

Orbital Period: 52.0 Earth Years
Radius: 35,417 km
Day Length: 14.7 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>25</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Trelyn</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Trelyn is a lifeless rock with a trace atmosphere of xenon and krypton. Its surface contains large amounts of iron and magnesium silicates. Due to heavily cratered terrain, starships are discouraged from landing. A salarian religious cult claims that a certain pattern of overlapping craters in the southern hemisphere resembles their goddess.

Orbital Period: 74.9 Earth Years
Radius: 1163 km
Day Length: 36.7 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -147 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>26</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>true</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>MSV Kaldwin</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
The Kaldwin is a Kowloon-class modular conveyor of human design. The ship appears to have been torn apart from the inside by some kind of void. A glowing emblem can be seen on a piece of metal spinning through space. The Normandy’s scanners identify it only as "Mark of the Outsider".

Registry: Private Owner, Captain Sokolov
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>27</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Thesalgon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A standard hydrogen-helium gas giant, Thesalgon's atmosphere is tinted blue by trace quantities of methane.

Orbital Period: 173.4 Earth Years
Radius: 53,520 km
Day Length: 15.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>28</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Antoneese</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
When Antoneese was first discovered, orbital surveys showed remains of an extinct species. Further investigation found inscriptions detailing the last days of intelligent life on the planet, which showed that they were nearing the ability to reach low orbit. During a commemorative event, the leader of the Antoneese told an ill timed joke, which escalated and eventually plunged their planet into a global war. The populations of Antoneese were devastated, leading to famine and a solar shield. Most, if not all life on the planet died shortly after. The age of the texts detailing these events could not be reliably determined.

Orbital Period: 12.0 Earth Years
Radius: 6694 km
Day Length: 59.7 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.19 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -178 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.16 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>29</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Maganlis</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Maganlis is a rock terrestrial with an atmosphere of sulphur dioxide and trace amounts of helium. Scans reveal ancient lava plains on the surface, implying a geologically active past. The crust consists of sulphur and basalts, but the planet’s mass suggests a core or iron and heavier materials. Cursory drill coring suggests the possibility of simple subterranean life.

Orbital Period: 2.4 Earth Years
Radius: 7708 km
Day Length: 33.2 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.03 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -150 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>30</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Gusty Garden</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Therumlon is a frigid world with a thick nitrogen-argon atmosphere. The crust consists of silicates and various unremarkable ores, but is surprising rich in phosphates. Since the atmosphere lacks free oxygen, the phosphates are relatively pure, and could be of value in the manufacture of fertilizers and incendiary ammunition.

Orbital Period: 31.4 Earth Years
Radius: 5492 km
Day Length: 69.0 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 17.11 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -134 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>31</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Shiva</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A small, unmanned flyby probe provides the only available data for this tiny planet. It is composed almost completely of ice, with a trace atmosphere of krypton. Mapping of mass concentrations shows a core of carbon under intense pressure. Normandy's more detailed survey suggests the core may solidify into something akin to diamond. The difficulty of extracting it, however, will likely deter any mining interest in the planet.

Orbital Period: 82.2 Earth Years
Radius: 3198 km
Day Length: 32.5 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.03 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -237 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>true</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>32</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nonuel</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
WARNING: Level 1 Heat Hazard

Though it is one of the oldest entries in the star charts, Nonuel has not yet been fully mapped. It is the largest body in the asteroid belt of the blue star Plutus, not only large enough to maintain a spherical shape, but also massive enough to retain the noxious carbon and sulphur dioxides venting from its many volcanoes as an atmosphere.

Nonuel is rabidly volcanic, and the source of its great heat is also the source of its inordinate mass. Nonuel is a "secondary source" of element zero, coalesced around a large chunk of eezo ejected by a supernova billions of years ago.

Surface conditions are extremely hazardous. In addition to the thin crust and numerous magma flows, wide stretches of the landscape are coated with slippery ash and cinders ejected from the volcanoes.

Orbital Period: 94.0 Earth Years
Radius: 4439 km
Day Length: 46.9 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.88 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 127 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.85 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>33</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mingito</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Mingito is a sunbaked wasteland of sodium, chorates, and radioactives. Its relatively light mass has left it tidally-locked to the star Plutus, with a dayside "hot pole" and a night side "cold pole." The powerful solar wind has stripped most of the atmosphere away.

Orbital Period: 1.4 Earth Years
Radius: 4384 km
Day Length: 1.4 Earth Years
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.2 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 675 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.44 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>34</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Clocrolis</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Clocrolis is a modest rock planet, roughly the size of Mars. It has a thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and ethane. Its scorching hot surface is mainly composed of silicate rock with deposits of aluminum and other light metals.

Clocrolis has a very weak magnetic field. In addition to very high levels of solar radiation, it is not suitable for mass effect drive discharge operations.

Orbital Period: 25.2 Earth Years
Radius: 3675 km
Day Length: 57.0 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.37 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 161 Celsius
Surface gravity: 0.39 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>35</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Maidla</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Maidla is a terrestrial planet with a light atmosphere of carbon dioxide and hydrogen sulfide. The surface is hot, and mainly composed of magnesia with deposits of sulfur. Over a dozen volcanoes are currently erupting across the surface.

Orbital Period: 3.3 Earth Years
Radius: 6914 km
Day Length: 33.4 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.48 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 497 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>36</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Veyaria</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Veyaria is a huge hydrogen-helium gas giant with traces of methane in its atmosphere.

Orbital Period: 239.2 Earth Years
Radius: 78204 km
Day Length: 10.0 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>37</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription ></PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>38</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Klensal</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Klensal has a thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and ethane. Its first geological surveys were performed by batarians, and suggested areas of great mineral wealth. Human mining concerns spent billions of credits hustling to the distant system and sinking test bores to claim the system for humanity.

But Klensal had only an average level of mineral wealth – valuable, but hardly worth the rush and expense. Merida Industria, a small Mexican company hoping to strike it rich in their first extrasolar mining venture, had to file for bankruptcy protection.

Investigation revealed the batarian crew had deliberately falsified their surveys, hoping it would encourage human rivals to invest in a costly boondoggle. While unethical, this was not technically illegal, and the batarian government disavowed the "personal actions of a few misguided patriots." The planet is still littered with abandoned mining bases, which are often used as temporary meeting places for criminals

Orbital Period: 21.4 Earth Years
Radius: 5447 km
Day Length: 37.2 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.58 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -35 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.86 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>39</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Monokuma</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Monokuma is a terrestrial world with traces of several toxic gases in the atmosphere. It is tidally locked to its star, resulting in extreme cold temperatures on the permanently dark side of the planet. The light side is covered in what appears to be large salt flats, giving it an almost reflective appearance.

Monokuma has a noticeable rift in its upper quadrant. While the origins of the rift are still unknown, geological studies indicate that its steep reddish cliffs likely contain large amounts of precious metal. A small mining outpost was established on the rift’s outcropping, aptly named ‘Hope’s Peak’.

Orbital Period: 2.8 Earth Years
Radius: 1410 km
Day Length 2.8 Earth Years
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 82 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.17 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>40</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nearrum</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Nearrum is a terrestrial world with a thin atmosphere of methane and argon. Its surface is mainly composed of basaltic rock. Its most prominent feature is the Farrum Rift, a long volcanic divergence zone that stretches across half of the northern hemisphere. The cliff surfaces are covered in massive circular fissures that appear artificially created, but their size makes this unlikely.

Orbital Period: 6.3 Earth Years
Radius: 6779 km
Day Length: 31.7 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.67 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 58 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.82 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>41</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nirn</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Nirn is an icy terrestrial planet with a thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and krypton. The planet’s mantle is hollow in most places and its surface is marred with holes large enough to see from space.

Nirn’s underground cave systems support a surprisingly large variety of algaes and planktons, but the most notable is a small, weed-like root. This pale-green species gives off a faint glow that provides light enough for other fauna to grow. A red variety of the same root does not glow, but instead emits a faint, high-pitched chiming noise. The mechanism of the sound is still unknown, as the sample canister obtained by the original scientific exploration was noted on the manifest as ‘lost in accidental airlock cycling sequence’.

Orbital Period: 35.4 Earth Years
Radius: 3691 km
Day Length: 61.7 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.27 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -84 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.28 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>42</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Raysha</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Raysha is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant with an traces of sodium and ammonia in its atmosphere.

During the brief "gold rush" to Klensal, a few companies established an infrastructural for helium-3 skimming and deuterium mining on Raysha's icy moons. When Klensal proved to be less wealthy than expected, the facilities were stripped for parts and abandoned.

Orbital Period: 85.5 Earth Years
Radius: 34,914 km
Day Length: 11.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>43</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>Asteroid belt description</PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>44</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Metallic Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A metal-rich asteroid.
Radius: 94 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>45</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>true</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>MSV Toronto</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
The Toronto is a Kowloon-class modular conveyor of human design, configured for mixed freight and passenger hauling. There is a large "No. 1" and what appears to be a maple leaf painted in blue on the side, possibly a reference to the city after which the conveyor was named. It is currently broadcasting garbled, vaguely insulting transmissions.

Registry: Private Owner, Citadel Station
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>46</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Tunshagon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Tunshagon is a hydrogen-helium gas giant with traces of chlorine and nitrogen in its atmosphere. It has an unusually small number of moons for a gas giant; a mere 7. This is no doubt due to the star Farinata capturing the majority of the mass during the nebular collapse that created the system.

Orbital Distance: 5.6 AU
Orbital Period: 3.2 Earth Years
Radius: 42,418 km
Day Length: 9.1 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>47</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Juntauma</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Juntauma is a small, broiling terrestrial world. Its thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and ethane is being steadily "blown off" by the powerful solar wind from the star Farinata. The surface is scorching hot, and mainly composed of sulphur with deposits of copper. Its density is low enough to leave the world tidally locked to Farinata.

The Alliance Defense Data Network notes that several ships have been spotted cruising near Juntauma with transponders turned off. While an Alliance patrol attempted pursuit of one, the unidentified vessel "rabbited" to FTL. Its trail was lost when it obscured its light trace in the confusion of signals along the Anansi-Ishtar shipping lane.

Orbital Distance: 69.9 AU
Orbital Period: 102.0 Earth Years
Radius: 4227 km
Day Length: 102.0 Earth Years
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.36 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 1176 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.38 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>48</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nepneu</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
With a rare combination of features, Nepneu is of particular interest to the scientific community. Nepneu is a small terrestrial planet, with a thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and krypton. As with all the worlds of Farinata, its surface is scorching hot. The crust mainly consists of silicates laced with iron.

Orbital Period: 302.0 Earth Years
Radius: 3742 km
Day Length: 30.1 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.23 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 848 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.27
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>49</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>50</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Rocky Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
This large asteroid has several smaller bodies orbiting it.
Radius: 336 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>51</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>52</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Chohe</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Chohe is a terrestrial planet whose surface is mainly composed of aluminum, with numerous deposits of calcium. Though it has enough mass to retain a dense atmosphere, Chohe is nearly a vacuum. This lack of atmosphere allows a moderate average temperature, but the differences between day and night are extreme.

The surface of Chohe's sunward-facing side is usually covered by a haze of volatiles (mainly water vapor and carbon dioxide), which return to the ground as frost over the course of the long, cold night.

The Sirta Foundation has established a research outpost on Chohe to investigate the native subterranean life of Chohe, which shows incredible resilience to extremes of heat and cold.

Orbital Distance: 3.7 AU
Orbital Period: 5.4 Earth Years
Radius: 8000 km
Day Length: 54.5 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 11 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.0 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>53</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Zavalater</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
An enigmatic terrestrial planet, Zavalater has a atmosphere of nitrogen and argon. It is blisteringly cold and a faint whitish haze can be seen rippling across its blue surface.

Three times in the last century, ships stopping to discharge at nearby planets have reported geometric patterns of lights on the dark side of Zavalater. Attempts at closer investigation could not be made, as an asteroid belt of whitish fragments surrounded the planet, and ship transponders were overridden with static laced references to ‘the Traveler’.

Orbital Distance: 2.0 AU
Orbital Period: 2.1 Earth Years
Radius: 5535 km
Day Length: 53.8 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.5 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 166 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>54</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Xamarri</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Xamarri is a small, airless, cratered terrestrial -- a lifeless rock quite similar to Luna. Its frozen surface is mainly composed of silicates, though one hemisphere has several "seas" of dark basaltic rock.

Orbital Period: 36.1 Earth Years
Radius: 2236 km
Day Length: 42.1 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -117 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.19 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>55</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Faringor</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A large but low-density terrestrial world, Faringor is generally believed to consist mainly of water ice. Occasional upwelling of metals, caused by the interacting tidal forces of several large moons, suggest the core is small, but extremely dense.

Faringor has a thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and ethane. Its frozen surface is mainly composed of dark carbon-laced water ice.

Ten years ago, Faringor's grim surface color and dim illumination drew the cinematographer Risa Uvarsen to film the exterior scenes of "Starless" on location. Acknowledged as a masterpiece of gothic horror, the sets – well-preserved by the vacuum – draw hundreds of tourists to the backwater system every year.

Orbital Distance: 20.2 AU
Orbital Period: 69.8 Earth Years
Radius: 11129 km
Day Length: 69.6 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -144 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>56</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Treyarmus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Treyarmus is a hydrogen-helium gas giant with a powerful magnetic field, making it a popular discharge site for freighters working the Anansi-Ishtar shipping route.

It is popular enough, in fact, that quarian ships can often be found loitering in orbit, selling the freighter crews cheap refreshments, salvage, and odd craftworks assembled by their children. There are no ships in orbit at present, however.

Orbital Distance: 51.8 AU
Orbital Period: 286.7 Earth Years
Radius: 42,211 km
Day Length: 12.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>57</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>58</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Trebin</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Trebin is a modest terrestrial world, with an atmosphere composed of nitrogen and argon.  Its surface is mainly composed of nickel with deposits of silver.

Trebin's environment is relatively mild, but the scarcity of water or similar enabling substances has prevented the development of any biosphere. ExoGeni Corp recently performed a test impact of a single water-ice comet into the surface, the first step of a long-term plan to thicken the atmosphere and introduce water to the environment.

A survey team is on the surface, monitoring the geological and meteorological effects of the test impact. Most of the water released is still in the form of atmospheric vapor, but thick cloud banks have formed. There is every indication that this arid world will soon see its first rain. The survey team’s progress has been hampered by frequent mechanical or computer failures in their GPS satellites.

Orbital Period: 1.1 Earth Years
Radius: 5489 km
Day Length: 41.8 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.84 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 8 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.86 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>59</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ageko</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
During the initial survey of the Anataeus system, only a single fly-by probe was spared for the small, scorched world of Ageko. It revealed a planet unusually rich in heavier elements, given its size.

Ageko is a standard terrestrial with a thin atmosphere of krypton and xenon. Its crust is mainly composed of magnesium with deposits of cobalt and other heavy metals. Due to extremely rough, cratered terrain, starships are discouraged from landing.

Orbital Period: 0.1 Earth Years
Radius: 2147 km
Day Length: 59.9 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.27 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 346 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.25 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>60</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Edmos</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Edmos is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant with traces of methane in its atmosphere. If Trebin's terraforming is successful, it is expected that a helium-3 fuel refining facility for the system will be set up here.

Orbital Period: 7.8 Earth Years
Radius: 36,826 km
Day Length: 13.7 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>61</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Bray</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Bray is a massive red planet with an unusually smooth surface. Sonar scans indicate the presence of a nearly hollow core. Ruined ships of failed expeditions still remain floating in low orbit, some of bearing the signs of an EMP attack, others crushed by unknown forces.

A privately-funded scan of the planet from far above the atmosphere revealed a lattice of structures just beneath the surface, most notably a large pyramid at the center of the core. Despite several conspiracies arguing that the planet was created by a sentient ‘brain’, no other useful information has been discovered.

Orbital Period: 20.4 Earth Years
Radius: 74,221 km
Day Length: 17.3 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>62</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Vemal</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Vemal is an enormous terrestrial world of mixed rock and ice with an atmosphere of methane and ethane. Its frozen surface is mainly composed of calcium with deposits of iron. Because of noxious surface gases, explorers are warned to use extreme caution.

Orbital Period: 37.5 Earth Years
Radius: 10,314 km
Day Length: 36.3 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.0 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -61 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>63</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Hunidor</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Hunidor is a moderately sized ice world with an extremely thin atmosphere composed of krypton and xenon. Its frozen surface is unusually smooth, suggesting widespread "repaving" by cryovolcanic processes though no such activity is currently evident.

Orbital Period: 90.5 Earth Years
Radius: 3686 km
Day Length: 48.2 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.2 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -202 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.22 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>64</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Virmire</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Mandalore</PlanetName2>
    <PlanetDescription>
%PLANETNAME% is a lush frontier world, covered in veshok forest, oceans, and rolling grasslands. Unique to the planet and its moon Concordia is beskar ore, a nearly indestructible material akin to iron.

The warrior tradition of the Taung clans has been passed down through ages and the unscrupulous denizens of the nearby Terminus Systems have learned to leave the planet well enough alone.

Capital: Keldabe

Orbital Period: 1.1 Earth Years
Radius: 6440 km
Day Length: 19 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.9 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 32 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.06 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>true</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>65</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Jafar</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Jafar is a large, sulfurous gas giant with dark clouds of ash circling its atmosphere. Two reddish moons sit high in its orbit. The gravitational pull exerted by Jafar and its moons is slowly pulling Sultan, a small white dwarf star, out of position. Research suggests that the star’s collapse into a black hole could happen within the next quarter-million years.

Orbital Period: 1.3 Earth Years
Radius: 63,169 km
Day Length: 1.3 Earth Years
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>66</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nemata</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Nemata is a terrestrial planet with a thick, hazy atmosphere of ammonia, methane, and a cocktail of other hydrocarbon gases. The surface is scorching hot, and mainly composed of nickel with deposits of iron.

With a density 1.4 times that of Earth, it is obvious that Nemata is rich with heavier elements. Mining could be extremely profitable, though the lethal heat and high gravity would make initial development costly. Given the political instability of the nearby Terminus Systems, investment is unlikely.

Orbital Period: 3.5 Earth Years
Radius: 7318 km
Day Length: 70.4 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.6 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 168 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.4 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>67</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Cloroplon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Cloroplon is a relatively small hydrogen-helium gas giant, with a haze of methane in the upper atmosphere.

Orbital Period: 47.8 Earth Years
Radius: 32,191 km
Day Length: 13.4 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>68</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Telos IV</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
The planet Telos IV was once a world of natural beauty and home to a thriving ecosystem. Decades ago, civil war between two opposing political forces lead to planetary bombardment, destroying significant parts of the ecosystem. A restoration project is underway to restore the planet to its former glory, with the planet sectioned off into chunks using Mass Effect fields.

A space station orbits over the 45 degree northern latitude of the planet, which is used as a staging area and monitoring station for the restoration efforts. The majority of the population of Telos IV lives aboard this space station.

Orbital Period: 6.7 Earth Years
Radius: 4075 km
Day Length: 24.9 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.6 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 5 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.3 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>69</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Feros</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Nirvash</PlanetName2>
    <PlanetDescription>
%PLANETNAME% is a small, temperate planet notable for the vast reef-like growths forming the bulk of its landmass. The atmosphere is laced with trapar, a particulate matter linked to the biological activities of these growths. There are indications that %PLANETNAME% may have been mostly oceanic in the past and that the so-called "Scub Coral" is a relatively new arrival, despite covering the vast majority of the planet’s surface. The ExoGeni Corporation founded a small colony to explore this unusual phenomena.

%PLANETNAME% has two large moons, Eureka and Sakuya.

Colony Founded: 2178
Population: 300
Capital: ExoGeni Building

Orbital Period: 3.2 Earth Years
Radius: 8366 km
Day Length: 30.3 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 5.44 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 10 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>70</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Sytau</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Sytau is shrouded by a high-pressure atmosphere composed of carbon dioxide and sulphuric acids. The surface is composed of geologically young plains of volcanic basalts and rhyolites, with high concentrations of carbon and radioactives.

Sytau is rabidly volcanic; a dozen "supervolcanoes" 50-120 kilometers wide are erupting across the planet. Sytau’s carbon content and constant volcanism make natural diamonds plentiful, if extremely costly and dangerous to recover.

Orbital Period: 1.1 Earth Years
Radius: 9547 km
Day Length: 32.2 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 94.51 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 343 Celsius
Surface Gravity 1.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>71</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Sharring</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Sharring is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant. The atmosphere contains traces of ammonia, methane, and surprisingly large amounts of water vapor, making the atmosphere a striking mix of browns, blues, and whites. Of Sharring's 60-odd moons, two have diameters of over 3000 kilometers. Both have signs of former Prothean development, suggesting Sharring may have been mined for helium-3.

Orbital Period: 46.6 Earth Years
Radius: 55,721 km
Day Length: 14.6 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>72</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Quana</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Quana's frozen surface is rich with heavy metals, and the planet’s higher than average density suggests further mineral richness in the depths. The atmosphere is composed of nitrogen and carbon monoxide.

The remains of a well-developed Prothean mining infrastructure dot the planet. Abandoned mines are connected to dead cities by collapsed maglev lines. Unlike the crumbling skyscrapers of Feros, Quana's ruins are reasonably intact. Unfortunately, this only made it easier for looters to strip the silent necropoli of anything valuable.

Orbital Period: 9.0 Earth Years
Radius: 7271 km
Day Length: 67.8 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.91 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -141 Celsius
Surface Gravity 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>73</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Logan</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Logan is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant. The survey team who charted the system twenty years ago reported many strange disturbances in Logan's cloud bands, suggesting many remarkably large solid objects were present beneath the cloud tops. As the ship approached, however, they subsided one by one. These disturbances have not been reported again.

Orbital Period: 112.6 Earth Years
Radius: 66,341 km
Day Length: 18.6 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>74</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Eletania</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
WARNING: Level 1 Toxic Hazard

Eletania appears to be a world eminently suited for colonization. Sadly, appearances are deceiving. It is covered by a verdant carpet of mosses, algae, and lichen, and possesses a thick oxygenated atmosphere, but the animal kingdom is a web of microscopic symbiotic creatures. These are impossible to filter from the air and necessary for the native life to thrive. Unfortunately, they also cause anaphylactic shock when inhaled by non-native life.

In short, settlement requires either fully sealed environment suits, or replacement of the entire world's ecosystem. Some have proposed limited colonization at altitudes above the symbiots' range, or in areas where favorable winds keep the air clear.

Orbital Distance: 12.6 AU
Orbital Period: 34.4 Earth Years
Radius: 8864 km
Day Length: 35.6 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 2.1 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 13 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>75</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Syided</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
The proximity of the energetic star Hercules causes constant blue and violet aurorae in Syided's nitrogen-argon atmosphere. During periods of increased solar flares, the aurorae are bright enough to read by on the surface, and can be seen with off-the-shelf optics from a distance of several AU.

Syided's scorching hot surface is mainly composed of magnesium with deposits of iron. A surprising variety of simple carbon-based life flourishes in a complex network of cave systems that wind through the crust, protected from Hercules' heat and radiation.

Orbital Period: 0.4 Earth Years
Radius: 7702 km
Day Length: 67.0 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.18 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 523 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.3 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>76</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Xathorron</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Xathorron is a small rock planet, with a thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and hydrogen sulfide. The surface is scorching hot, and mainly composed of sulfur with deposits of boron.

Orbital Period: 9.5 Earth Years
Radius: 3537 km
Day Length: 64.9 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.37 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 388 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.39 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>77</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ramuh</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Ramuh is a hydrogen-helium gas giant. Charged ions in the sulfuric atmosphere have created billowing, cloudy storm fronts. Lightning can be seen flickering almost constantly across the dark side of the planet.

The constellation Olduum, with its noticeably purple-hued stars, is visible even through the heavy cloud cover.

Orbital Period: 113.1 Earth Years
Radius: 52,290 km
Day Length: 17.2 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>78</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ilos</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
In the golden age of the Protheans, Ilos was a verdant world, dotted with the spires and arches of magnificent cities. Even casual observation shows this is no longer the case. Ilos has been devastated by means unknown, its entire surface changed to the color of rust. The atmosphere shows heightened levels of oxygen. Wildfires, presumably ignited by lightning strikes, can be seen burning on the dark side. This indicates that most - if not all - respirating animal life forms have died off. Surface gravity is a comfortable 1.17 standard G's.

Orbital Period: 261 Earth Days
Radius: 8607 km
Day Length: 54.5 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 11.26 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 38 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>79</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Agetoton</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Agetoton has a pressure-cooker atmosphere composed of carbon dioxide and ethane. Its scorching hot surface is mainly composed of sulfur with deposits of gold. Surface gravity is comfortable at 1.0 standard G's.

There are several areas of debris that may be the wreckage of downed Prothean aerostat colonies. Based on the size of the debris fields, a population of over 100,000 was likely.

Orbital Period: 0.4 Earth Years
Radius: 6172 km
Day Length: 53.5 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 84.30 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 510 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>80</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Zafe</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Zafe is a relatively small hydrogen and helium gas giant. There are several tenuous belts of debris in equatorial orbit. Spectral analysis of the material suggests artificial origin, perhaps the remains of stations that once mined Zafe for helium-3.

Orbital Period: 33.8 Earth Years
Radius: 30,488 km
Day Length: 12.2 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>81</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Agebinium</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Agebinium is a small terrestrial world with an extremely thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and krypton. Though the planet has sufficient mass to maintain a much thicker atmosphere, much of it has been blasted away.

The red giant Amazon is a long-period variable star, currently at the nadir of a 16-year cycle. At peak, its energy output doubles, lashing Agebinium with intense heat and radiation.

The crust is mainly composed of aluminum with deposits of tin. Much of the surface is coated with fine silicate dust, which easily penetrates the smallest cracks to foul machinery.

Orbital Period: 1.8 Earth Years
Radius: 4910 km
Day Length: 42.1 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.17 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -72 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.79 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>82</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Derneuca</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Derneuca is an enormous terrestrial world, nearly twice the size of Earth. Its environment is similar to that of Mars; arid, and a mix of craggy basalt highlands and sand-scoured deserts of iron-laced silicate dust.

Derneuca's atmosphere mainly consists of carbon dioxide and argon, but the planet's mass is great enough that measurable amounts of helium, and even molecular hydrogen, remain trapped in its atmosphere.

The planet's gravity well is deep enough that it has collected nearly a dozen small satellites, most captured asteroids. Its surfaced is scarred by many large impact craters, marking the final resting place of other captured asteroids.

Orbital Period: 3.1 Earth Years
Radius: 11,728 km
Day Length: 65.5 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.93 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -60 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>83</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Tremar</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Tremar is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant with traces of methane and nitrogen in its upper atmosphere.

Orbital Period: 33.4 Earth Years
Radius: 61,266 km
Day Length: 12.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>84</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Sonedma</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Sonedma is the second of the Amazon system's arid "super-terrestrial" worlds. It is considerably less dense than its neighbor Derneuca and has an atmosphere of carbon dioxide and ethane. Its frozen surface is mainly composed of iron-laced silicates with deposits of sulfur.

Orbital Period: 6.2 Earth Years
Radius: 9647 km
Day Length: 44.7 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.16 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -108 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>85</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Sybin</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A small rock and ice planet, Sybin has an extremely thin atmosphere of hydrogen sulfide and ethane. Its frozen surface is mainly composed of magnesium and silicates with deposits of iron.

Sybin's crust contains significant deposits of green serpentine, a mineral formed by volcanic activity. This suggests Sybin was a more geologically active world in the distant past.

Orbital Period: 15.1 Earth Years
Radius: 4645 km
Day Length: 62.6 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.18 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -169 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.5 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>86</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Cuchulainn</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Cuchulainn’s atmosphere consists of massive sulphur dioxide clouds, which flood the surface with acid rain. The Garamsythe Ocean, which covers most of the planet, rises an average of five millimeters per year. A brief Alliance survey suggests that the acidity of the water may eventually break down the terrestrial surface altogether.

The planet glows a sickly green color when viewed from space, due to traces of ionized nitrogen in the upper atmosphere.

Orbital Period: 5 Earth Years
Radius: 5935 km
Day Length: 53.2 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.91 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 94 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.94 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>87</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Renshato</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Renshato is a close-orbiting "Hot Jupiter" with traces of sulphur its hydrogen-helium atmosphere. The disruptive gravity well of the gas giant prevented any planets from forming nearby.

Orbital Period: 0.5 Earth Years
Radius: 25,957 km
Day Length: 18.1 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>88</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Dregir</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Dregir is a small, barren rock world with a trace atmosphere of krypton and xenon. The surface is frigid, and mainly composed of silicates with deposits of magnesium, aluminum, and other light metals. Dregir has a weak magnetic field, making it unsuitable for drive discharge operations.

Orbital Period: 23.7 Earth Years
Radius: 2843 km
Day Length: 34.0 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -96 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.28 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>89</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Alrumter</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Alrumter is a small, rocky terrestrial planet with a trace atmosphere of nitrogen and krypton. Its frigid surface is mainly composed of light metals with deposits areas of frozen ammonia.

Orbital Period: 35.2 Earth Years
Radius: 3718 km
Day Length: 39.5 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -96 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.39 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>90</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Patajiri</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Patajiri has a thin atmosphere composed of neon and chlorine. Its frozen surface is mainly composed of silica with deposits of copper. During the long, cold night, the chlorine in the atmosphere falls to the ground in the form of frost.

Orbital Period: 123.6 Earth Years
Radius: 7304 km
Day Length: 57.7 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.42 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -118 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.99 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>91</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Natina</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Natina is a barren, volcanic terrestrial world with an atmosphere choked in soot. The planet’s incredibly strong gravity and atmospheric pressure causes the magma eruptions to condense and harden almost immediately. The resulting surface is deep black and ash-laden winds have scoured it to almost uniformly reflective sheen.

This unique display, along with the frequent volcanic eruptions, makes Natina a popular destination for artists of all kinds. The planet has been affectionately dubbed ‘Yellow’ by many photography fans, alluding to the distinctive cover of the famous Galactic Geographic holozine.

Orbital Period: 0.8 Earth Years
Radius: 6865 km
Day Length: 56.2 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 5.73 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 37 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 2.78 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>92</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Clojiia</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Clojiia is a "hothouse" terrestrial world with a dense atmosphere of nitrogen and sulphur dioxide. The surface is scorching hot, and mainly composed of iron with deposits of gold.

The core of Clojiia is very hot and tectonically active. Volcanic eruptions are common, and outgassing continues to add to the density of the atmosphere. The largest active volcano has a caldera nearly 100 kilometers in diameter, and its basalt floods have covered an area roughly the size of the Earth continent of Australia.

Orbital Period: 0.3 Earth Years
Radius: 7074 km
Day Length: 47.6 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 18.33 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 312 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>93</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ontaheter</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Ontaheter is an unusually large ice world, with a core of silicate rock and light metals, and a trace atmosphere of krypton and xenon. The crust is mainly composed of water ice. Ontaheter’s ice sheets show obvious signs of large scale fracture and refreezing, centered on a massive crater near the south pole.

A recent extranet meme suggests that a Prothean ship crashed through the crust of the planet before the collapse of their empire, and might still be recovered from the planetary core. This is purportedly the source of the planet’s unusually high mass. Careful mapping of Ontaheter's gravity field by orbiting satellites have proved that the planetary core is entirely normal.

Orbital Period: 5.2 Earth Years
Radius: 3718 km
Day Length: 56.3 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.06 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -124 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>94</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Gromar</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Gromar is a rocky terrestrial world with a trace atmosphere of krypton and xenon. The frozen surface is mainly composed of copper with deposits of calcium.

Prior to the Alliance's expansion into the Voyage Cluster, Gromar hosted one half of a turian interferometric telescope array. Connected with similar telescope in the Attican Beta cluster by an expensive chain of FTL comm buoys, the two functioned as a single virtual "lens" with an effective aperture equal to the thousands of light years between them. The turians used this to chart the Terminus Systems with great accuracy.

Orbital Period: 115.6 Earth Years
Radius: 4911 km
Day Length: 30.3 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.13 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -218 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.28 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>95</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>96</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>97</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Sharjila</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
WARNING: Level 1 Pressure Hazard

Sharjila has a very dense atmosphere of ammonia and oxygen.  Its temperate surface is mainly composed of alumina with deposits of sulfur. Comm buoys in the system have recently logged a number of unregistered vessels operating nearby.

Sharjila has an extensive silicon-based, oxygen-breathing ecology. Heavily populated areas are covered with fine silica (silicon dioxide) dust, the respiratory by-product of the world's higher animal forms. High-speed surface winds, often laden with abrasive silica dust, present a hazard. In areas where the wind deposits a great deal of silica, footing can be treacherous. EVAs are discouraged.


Orbital Period: 1.0 Earth Years
Radius: 5693 km
Day Length: 40.6 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 39.16 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 25 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.9G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>98</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Porolan</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Porolan is an enormous terrestrial planet, half again the size of Earth. Despite its thick atmosphere, the weak output of the red dwarf Macedon leaves its surface biting cold. The crust is mainly composed of silica, but significant deposits of iron and other industrial metals are present. These lodes may prove rich enough to be profitably mined despite the heavy gravity.

Orbital Period: 21.0 Earth Years
Radius: 9749 km
Day Length: 45.4 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.4 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -197 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.5 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>99</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Patavig</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Patavig is the second of the Macedon system's giant terrestrial planets, and by far the more interesting. Most of the surface is covered by a vast sea of liquid ammonia, in which a unique aquatic ammonia-based biosphere has developed. While the frozen continents are largely bereft of life, a rich bounty of complex organisms - many larger than a human - flourish in the chilly, toxic seas.

While dreadfully inhospitable to humans, Patavig is suitable for colonization by the volus. Negotiations between the Systems Alliance and the volus' patrons, the Turian Hierarchy, have made good progress.

Orbital Distance: 11.3 AU
Orbital Period: 69.8 Earth Years
Radius: 10,529 km
Day Length: 30.4 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 22.4 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -130 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.6 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>100</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Fargeluse</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Fargeluse is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant with an abundance of airborne hydrocarbons.

Orbital Period: 111.7 Earth Years
Radius: 40,394 km
Day Length: 19.1 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>101</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>102</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Metallic Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A metal-rich asteroid.
Radius: 91 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>103</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Proteus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Like the hanar homeworld, Proteus has more than 90% oceanic cover. The incredible heat thrown off from Athens raises global humidity to 100%, creates constant cloud cover, and powers colossal typhoons that rage across the surface year-round.

Hot, humid, and storm-wracked, Proteus' rare combination of oxygen-nitrogen atmosphere and carbon-based biosphere nevertheless recommend it for colonization. A pilot program is studying the possibility of colonies below the ocean surface, safe from the worst effects of the weather.

Colony Founded: 2179
Population: 12,470
Capital: Ithaka

Orbital Period: 4.9 Earth Years
Radius: 10,210 km
Day Length: 51.4 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.21 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 34 Celsius
Surface Gravity 1.3 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>104</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Salamis</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
The geological properties of Salamis have been scanned from orbit, but little else is known about it. Due to its thick carbon dioxide atmosphere and proximity to the energetic star Athens, the equatorial daytime temperatures have been known to turn the surface molten. The crust is composed of iron with deposits of platinum group metals.

Orbital Period: 0.4 Earth Years
Radius: 6894 km
Day Length: 58.6 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.40 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 520 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.3 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>105</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mononoke</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Traces of sodium in the atmosphere give Mononoke its overall dark grey color, but it is otherwise a typical hydrogen-helium gas giant. An abundance of water vapor in the upper atmosphere account for its white clouds.

A long-range probe recorded footage of a brief phenomena in which the surface of the planet appeared to be covered in long, trailing spores.

Orbital Period: 57.6 Earth Years
Radius: 59,729 km
Day Length: 14.0 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>106</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Circe</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Circe is a modestly sized hydrogen-helium gas giant with traces of sulphur and chlorine. These give it its striking yellow-green tint. As the development of the Proteus colony continues, Circe will likely be developed for helium-3 mining.

Orbital Period: 141.9 Earth Years
Radius: 22,479 km
Day Length: 10.9 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>107</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pharos</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Distant Pharos has seen only a cursory examination by an unmanned probe. It has a trace atmosphere of nitrogen and argon. Its surface is mainly composed of tin with deposits of carbon. Deeper craters have been partly filled by ice, suggesting there may be a significant amount of water locked up beneath its frozen surface. A large, ice-bright crater in the southern hemispshere makes the planet visible from the inner system, leading to the planet’s name.

Orbital Period: 275.4 Earth Years
Radius: 7623 km
Day Length: 47.4 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.04 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -176 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.9 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>108</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>109</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Edolus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Edolus is a terrestrial planet with an atmosphere of carbon dioxide and nitrogen. Edolus's surface is covered by wide deserts of silicate sand, with only a few areas of igneous rock highlands to break the abrasive, dust-choked wind.

Edolus's orbit is congested with debris thrown inwards by the gravity of the gas giant Ontamalca. Due to a high rate of meteor impacts, exploration is highly dangerous.

Orbital Period: 2.7 Earth Years
Radius: 5729 km
Day Length: 50.3 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.8 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -1 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.87 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>110</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Tremanre</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Tremanre is a dwarf planet composed of light magnesium silicates, with deposits of aluminum. Its surface is covered by wide swathes of ancient, dark basaltic lava, possibly indicating the world was created though an impact with some other body in the system.

Tremanre's magnetic field is nonexistent. This makes it impossible for ships to dump drive charge from orbit. That said, Tremanre's miniscule gravity allows even cruiser-sized vessels to land safely for direct grounding.

Orbital Period: 1.0 Earth Years
Radius: 1528 km
Day Length: 1.0 Earth Years
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 55 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>111</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Altaaya</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Altaaya is an unusually large terrestrial world with a trace atmosphere of methane and ammonia. The surface is frozen, and mainly composed of sandstone and other sedimentary rocks with deposits of iron and chlorides. Judging by the sedimentary composition of the crust, it appears that Altaaya once possessed an atmosphere thick enough to support some form of liquid. What cataclysm stripped the atmosphere and left the planet to freeze is not currently known.

Orbital Period: 18.1 Earth Years
Radius: 11190 km
Day Length: 47.2 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.20 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -136 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>112</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Zeromus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Zeromus is a large hydrogen-helium gas giant. Its massive gravity well has attracted hundreds of moons and asteroids into its orbit. Most are ripped apart by the forces and become part of an ever-growing ring system. Indigo vapor trails make a faint haze in the atmosphere as the planet’s solid copper core slowly collapses under the pressure.

The planet is commonly called “the Condemner”, and not even pirates venture too close. Even out of the gravity well’s range, the sheer amount of space debris can obliterate all but the most strongly-shielded ships.

Orbital Period: 39.1 Earth Years
Radius: 72,492 km
Day Length: 17.7 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>113</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Alsages</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Small, distant Alsages is a small terrestrial, with a trace atmosphere of methane and argon. The surface is composed of water ice and calcium with occasional deposits of light metals.

During the Alliance's pirate suppression campaign in the 2160's, the batarian Eluam Ran'perah was caught with his frigate Tunerron grounded on Alsages for drive discharge. When challenged by the cruiser Hyderabad, Ran'perah refused to surrender. The Tunerron was destroyed attempting to take off. The debris is strewn across the southern hemisphere.

Orbital Period: 73.8 Earth Years
Radius: 4926 km
Day Length: 23.3 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -193 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>114</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>115</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Cluster</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A collection of small siliceous asteroids, loosely bound together by gravity.
Radius: 12 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>116</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>117</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Therum</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Therum is a distant but rich industrial world claimed by the human Systems Alliance. Its plentiful heavy metals have fueled the recent manufacturing boom on Earth. Core samples rich with the fossils of simple silicon-based organisms indicate Therum was more habitable in the past than it is at present. Perhaps this explains the many Prothean ruins dotting the surface, most of which have been looted by mining corporations.

Colony Founded: 2167
Population: 34,000
Capital: Nova Yekaterinburg

Orbital Period: 6.4 Earth Years
Radius: 6724 km
Day Length: 28.3 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.68 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 59 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.12 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>118</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Phaistos</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Phaistos is a small terrestrial with a trace atmosphere of carbon dioxide and xenon. The surface is scorching hot, and mainly composed of sulphur and various silicates. There is little of interest on this desolate world.

Orbital Period: 0.3 Earth Years
Radius: 4238 km
Day Length: 57.2 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.27 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 551 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.63 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>119</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Oculon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Oculon is a terrestrial world with a nitrogen-methane atmosphere containing trace amounts of hydrocarbons. Its frigid surface is mainly composed of water ice and hydrocarbon slush.

Several space stations of salarian design orbit the planet, but closer inspection shows significant damage to several of them. They appear to have been long since abandoned, the cause of the damage unknown.

Orbital Period: 33.9 Earth Years
Radius: 4572 km
Day Length: 45.6 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.40 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -71 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.4 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>120</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Vermillion</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Vermillion is a terrestrial world with an unusually thin atmosphere of krypton and xenon. Its surface is composed of silica with deposits of carbonaceous materials. The initial flyby probe of Vermillion detected multiple areas at the equator with oddly regular surface protrusions.

Closer investigation revealed these as millions of elaborate crypts a few meters below the surface, left by a long-extinct spacefaring species called the zeioph. Many human universities wish to perform archeological excavations. Council law holds grave sites as sacrosanct, however, and the matter has been tied up in court for a decade.

Orbital Period: 151.3 Earth Years
Radius: 6077 km
Day Length: 57.8 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.18 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -168 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>121</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Medoh</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A small oxygen-nitrogen gas giant, Medoh has become has been developed as a full-featured testing ground for aerodynamic non-space-faring vehicle design. Constant winds that swirl due to the high rotation rate of the planet provide excellent conditions for testing unpredictable wind patterns on habitable planets. Due to the relatively small size of the planet, combined with the high rate of rotation, it is expected to lose most of its atmosphere within the next 10,000 years.

The single moon of Medoh, Revali, is uncharted except for a single tower that marks an otherwise unremarkable surface.

Orbital Period: 470.2 Earth Years
Radius: 1,350 km
Day Length: 2.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>122</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>123</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Distress signal</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A distress call is coming from this asteroid, however nothing adorns the surface except for a single large tunnel entrance. The distress call signal is weak and appears to be coming from the asteroid’s interior, repeating a message about ‘Giant alien spiders’.

This is almost certainly a trap. Risking the Normandy to save these unknown victims from ‘Giant alien spiders’ is certainly not worth the risk.

Radius: 127 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>124</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>125</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Carbonaceous Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A dark, carbon-rich asteroid.
Radius: 83 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>126</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Liara's Dig Site</PlanetName>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>127</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Vah Rudania</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Vah Rudania is a hot, barren terrestrial world. Chiseled into the surface are maze-like patterns, with scans indicating a subterranean tunnel system that can be entered from specific points in the maze. The surface is dotted with these labyrinths, though no surface dwelling life appears to be able to survive the intense heat to make use of it.

The single moon of Vah Rudania, Daruk, has several large craters on it. The few colonial areas on the moon have a planetary defense system to defend against incoming meteors.

Radius: 5171 km
Day Length: 60.5 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.84 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 180 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.87
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>128</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ruta</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Ruta is a water planet, with a very cold terrestrial atmosphere. Volcanic activity under the planetary ocean and water currents keep the majority of the surface from freezing. A haven for marine life, Ruta has many unexplored secrets in it’s depths.

A colonized moon of Ruta, Mipha, is considered one of the leading pioneers in medical science. The moon’s capital research facility, named Mipha’s Grace, contributed significantly to the development of Medi-Gel, in partnership with the Sirta Foundation.

Orbital Period: 0.2 Earth Years
Radius: 10,480 km
Day Length: 56.7 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.96 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -60 Celsius
Surface gravity: 0.98 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>129</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pressha</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Pressha is a relatively small hydrogen-helium gas giant with large amounts of hydrocarbons in the middle layers of the atmosphere.

When the Krogan Rebellions ended three millennia ago, the turian chief of naval operations, a distinguished soldier named Mehrkuri, declared his immediate retirement. He disappeared into what was then uncharted territory. It was only two hundred years ago that his ship was found on the surface Pressha's largest moon. It had landed gently and been deliberately shut down. Of Admiral Mehrkuri, however, no trace was ever found.

Orbital Period: 0.7 Earth Years
Radius: 38,482 km
Day Length: 16.2 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>130</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Sogelrus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Sogelrus is a small terrestrial planet with a thin atmosphere of nitrogen and argon. The frigid surface is mainly composed of water ice, which can be plainly seen in the bottoms of recent craters. The dark coloration of the surface is caused by a carbon and ferrous material, pushed up from the denser core by cryovolcanic processes.

Orbital Period: 1.8 Earth Years
Radius: 4327 km
Day Length: 63.9 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.52 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -136 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.46 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>131</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Antirumgon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Antirumgon is a small rock and ice planet, with a trace atmosphere of methane and ethane. The frozen surface is mainly composed of carbon with deposits of calcium.
Antirumgon has been used as a crude anchorage for Terminus pirates for many years. The shells of temporary dwellings blasted by Alliance frigate patrols dot the surface. But always, the pirates return to ground their ships' drive charges, chip out some water ice, and trade slaves and stories.

The deeper layers of Antirumgon's interior are semi-liquid slush, due to the presence of methanol. It is thought that bacterium in the deep core create this natural anti-freeze. Some species of Terminus pirate drill through the ice crust to recover this natural alcohol.

Orbital Period: 4.0 Earth Years
Radius: 9508 km
Day Length: 32.1 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -178 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.90
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>132</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Antibaar</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Antibaar is a cold terrestrial world with an atmosphere of methane and argon.  Its frozen surface is mainly composed of iron with deposits of magnesium. The world has been noted as a possible target for long-term terraforming; if the atmosphere could be increased to the thickness of Earth's, the global average temperature would rise by 10 degree Celcius.

Antibaar's combination of low temperatures, high speed surface winds, and low visibility make it dangerous to explore on foot.

Orbital Period: 3.2 Earth Years
Radius: 6501 km
Day Length: 54.1 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.79 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -34 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>133</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Patamalrus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Patamalrus' atmosphere is very similar to Venus in terms of pressure and temperature. Unlike Venus, however, Patamalrus' atmosphere has a significant quantity of oxygen, both free and bound in sulpher dioxides. The surface is largely composed of magnesia with deposits of carbon. It is possible, if unlikely, that simple life may be developing on Patamalrus.

Computer modeling suggests that the powerful solar winds from the Tereshkova stars will blow off Patamalrus' atmosphere in a few million years, lowering the temperature on the surface to the -70s.

Orbital Period: 15.3 Earth Years
Radius: 5831 km
Day Length: 47.1 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 90.47 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 451 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.78 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>134</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Hunsalra</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Hunsalra is a small hydrogen-helium gas giant. It has unusually large amounts of nitrogen in the upper atmosphere, which glow purple when ionized by the solar wind. Hunsalra’s convenience as a place to dump drive charge has left its orbit littered with debris "dumped overboard" by visting crews.

Orbital Period: 46.2 Earth Years
Radius: 11,496 km
Day Length: 18.6 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>135</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Thegeuse</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Thegeuse is a terrestrial world with an atmosphere of chlorine and krypton. The surface is mainly composed of silicates with deposits of carbon. Thegeuse has a low mass for its size, and is tidally locked to the star Tereshkova-A. The temperature difference between the sunward "hot pole" and the dark side "cold pole" creates constant gale-force winds across the terminator.

Orbital Period: 25.3 Earth Years
Radius: 5130 km
Day Length: 5.2 Earth Years
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.49 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -141 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.47 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>136</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Solmarlon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Solmarlon is one of Tereshkova's two outer worlds. Significantly removed from the rest of the system, and with unstable elliptical orbits, it is thought they may have formed within 3 AU of the binary stars, and were hurled outward due to the instability of such an orbit.

Solmarlon is a hydrogen-helium gas giant with significant quantities of sodium in the upper atmosphere, giving it a distinct grey color.

Orbital Period: 399.7 Earth Years
Radius: 69,862 km
Day Length: 14.4 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>137</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mawinor</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Mawinor is the second of Tereshkova's outer worlds. It is essentially a rock of unremarkable ores with some deposits of water ice, but no minerals of value. The frozen surface is composed of silica.

Like the gas giant Solmarlon, it is thought that Mawinor formed too close to the Tereshkova stars and was thrown outwards by gravitational effects. Computer models suggest it will be ejected from the system in a few hundred thousand years.

Orbital Period: 662.7 Earth Years
Radius: 1170 km
Day Length: 61.8 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -228 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.08 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>138</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>139</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Carbonaceous Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A dark asteroid of mixed carbonaceous materials.
Radius: 42 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>140</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Solcrum</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
WARNING: Level 1 Heat Hazard

Solcrum is the largest moon of the gas giant Notanban. It has a trace atmosphere of krypton and xenon. The crust is composed of various metals with deposits of sodium. As with every body in the solar system, the surface is scorching hot and thoroughly irradiated by the blue giant Grissom. Surface excursions without proper protective gear are certain to prove fatal.

On approach to Notanban, Normandy's passive sensor array intercepted a fragmentary coded transmission from the surface of Solcrum. Attempts to decrypt the message were fruitless; it does not appear to be in any software coding language used by the Citadel races.

Orbital Distance: 10,367,883 km (from Notanban)
Orbital Period: 0.6 Earth Years
Radius: 4534 km
Day Length: 0.6 Earth Years
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 351 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>141</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Benda</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Benda has a dense atmosphere of sulphur dioxide and chlorine. Though technically classified as a "terrestrial" world, but the surface of the planet has never cooled enough for a crust to form. It is a global sea of molten rock. Like Zaherux, its atmosphere is being blasted away by the solar wind. Once its thick atmosphere is gone, Benda’s surface will be a "mere" 400 degree C.

Orbital Period: 812.3 Earth Years
Radius: 6788 km
Day Length: 41.2 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 26.35 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 3151 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>142</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Zaherux</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Zaherux's nitrogen-argon atmosphere is being blasted away by the solar wind of the blue giant Grissom. Its surface consists of "seas" of loose silica dust, some kilometers deep, which periodically swirl into global sandstorms.

Many unmanned probes to Zaherux have been lost over the years. Though investigation has attributed all to mechanical failure or computational error, a popular extranet meme insists the entire planet is composed of dormant nanotechnology, created millennia ago by a race even more advanced than the Protheans.

According to the story, Zaherux's silica dust is actually "disassembler" robots which periodically awaken to defend themselves. Though discounted by every reputable scientist, this theory has been popularized by a series of sensationalistic texts by asari author Delsae Orthysa.

Orbital Period: 266.8 Earth Years
Radius: 6729 km
Day Length: 51.5 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.32 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 959 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.61 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>143</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Notanban</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Notanban is a hydrogen-helium gas giant with traces of ammonia. Molecular nitrogen is present in the highest levels of the atmosphere, giving the planet its odd violet tint.

The upper levels of Notanban's atmosphere are inhabited by "shoals" of tiny ammonia-based lifeforms, no larger or more complex than the plankton of Earth's oceans. Held aloft by air pressure and wind, these bioluminescent creatures constantly flee from the approach of the terminator. Should they be exposed to the light and heat of Grissom, they die.

Orbital Period: 990.5 Earth Years
Radius: 73,314 km
Day Length: 16.9 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>144</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>145</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Rocky Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
An asteroid composed of mixed metals and silicates.
Radius: 54 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>146</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>147</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Maji</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Maji orbits the Vamshi binary giant stars. Vamshi-A is a blue star of spectral class A4III which burns at half again the temperature of Sol. Vamshi-B is an aging red giant of class M5III, over 220 times the size of Sol.

Maji has a thin atmosphere of methane and carbon monoxide. The difference in temperature between the hemisphere facing the suns and that facing deep space causes constant wind, stirring the silica and sodium dust of the surface.

Unsavory characters from the Terminus Systems occasionally use Maji for forms of cruel sport, dumping slaves, hostages, quarreling shipmates, or even (when bored) vicious animals on the surface. One must kill the other before they will be rescued from the lethal radiation of the giant stars.

Orbital Period: 5.9 Earth Years
Radius: 5727 km
Day Length: 55.3 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.42 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -121 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.85 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>148</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Almos</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Almos is a hydrogen-helium gas giant with traces of sodium darkening its atmosphere.

Orbital Period: 46.7 Earth Years
Radius: 60,948 km
Day Length: 67.1 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>149</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pregel</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Pregel is an enormous terrestrial world with an atmosphere of chlorine and ethane. Its surface is mainly composed of sulphur with deposits of aluminum. No landing has ever been attempted.

Orbital Period: 17.8 Earth Years
Radius: 10,510 km
Day Length: 49.8 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.0 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -131 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>150</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Casbin</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Casbin is a classic "pre-garden" terrestrial world, with conditions similar to those on Earth millions of years ago. Its hot, humid atmosphere is mainly composed of nitrogen and carbon dioxide. An increasing amount of the surface is covered by simple lichen and algae. Should no unexpected calamity occur, these tiny plants will change the atmosphere to an Earth-like nitrogen-oxygen mix over the next few millennia.

Due to its potential for future habitability and sapient life, Casbin has been designated a Sanctuary World by the Citadel Council. Landing is prohibited by law, and any disturbance of the fragile young ecosystem will result in harsh fines and imprisonment.

At present, the planet is passing through the debris trail of a long-period comet.

Orbital Period: 1.1 Earth Years
Radius: 7819 km
Day Length: 44.6 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.1 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 99 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>151</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pomal</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Pomal is an enormous terrestrial planet, with a very dense atmosphere of carbon dioxide and sodium. The surface is scorching hot, and mainly composed of sodium oxides and deposits of nickel. There is evidence that Pomal was once covered with broad, shallow seas. Should a probe ever be sent to the surface, a check for ancient fossil life might prove valuable.

Orbital Period: 0.5 Earth Years
Radius: 9616 km
Day Length: 47.0 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 31.59 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 492 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>152</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Matar</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Matar is terrestrial planet with a thick atmosphere composed of nitrogen and krypton. Its frigid surface is mainly composed of sodium oxide with deposits of copper. Because of noxious surface gases, explorers are warned to use extreme caution.

Matar lacks a magnetic field. This makes it useless for discharging FTL drive cores in orbit. The energetic particles of solar wind from Hong strike the upper atmosphere directly, ionizing the krypton. This gives the planet its distinctive "minty" green-white hue.

Orbital Period: 29.8 Earth Years
Radius: 4599 km
Day Length: 54.5 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 3.72 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -64 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.57 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>153</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Theshaca</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Theshaca is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant. In the past, it was often used as a drive discharge point for pirates raiding human settlements from the Terminus Systems. In 2178 the Alliance set up a network of covert sensing devices on Thesaca's moons. Recordings of pirate FTL exit vectors over the course of six months led the Alliance Navy to eight major pirate anchorages. Since the "Theshaca Raids," no ships from the Terminus have been reported in the Hong system.

Orbital Period: 84.4 Earth Years
Radius: 65,976 km
Day Length: 14.0 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>154</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Cayde-6</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Cayde-6 is a tiny dwarf planet with a trace atmosphere. The surface is mainly composed of water ice trapped beneath a skin of weak ammonia ice. Bioluminescent plankton beneath the surface spread a faint bluish glow through the frozen layers.

Orbital Period: 238.8 Earth Years
Radius: 1402 km
Day Length: 30.2 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.04 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -211 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>true</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>155</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nodacrux</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Nodacrux is a verdant world, with abundant water, temperate climate, a thick nitrogen-oxygen atmosphere, and a rich ecosystem. It would seem to be perfect for life. The relatively high percentage of oxygen makes humans feel energized and alive, though it has also allowed insect analogues to grow to frightful sizes.

Unfortunately, Nodacrux is a case of "almost, not quite." Thunderstorms are as common as on Earth, but in Nodacrux’s thicker, oxygen-rich atmosphere, they are deafening and spark constant wildfires. More damning, however, are the large and ubiquitous tufts of pollen that float on the high-pressure air. In humans and other oxygen-breathing species, they cause severe or lethal allergic reactions.

Orbital Period: 3.6 Earth Years
Radius: 5988 km
Day Length: 22.2 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 2.63 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 23 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.9 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>156</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Clomarthu</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Clomarthu has a reducing atmosphere of methane and nitrogen. The surface is hot, and mainly composed of sodium with deposits of uranium. In terms of size and orbit, Clomarthu is a virtual twin of Earth, but utterly lacks life.

Orbital Period: 1 Earth Year
Radius: 6028 km
Day Length: 18.8 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.9 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 95 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.9 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>157</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Alko</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
The geological properties of Alko have been scanned from orbit, but little else is known about it. A fairly typical mix outer system terrestrial of rock and ice, Alko has a trace atmosphere of krypton and xenon. Its crust is composed of silicates and water ice with deposits of aluminum. Unregistered starship traffic has been recorded in the vicinity of this planet. Travel is not advised.

Orbital Period: 28.7 Earth Years
Radius: 4949 km
Day Length: 45.2 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -167 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.5 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>158</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pataiton</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A rather small hydrogen-helium gas giant, Pataiton’s atmosphere contains large quantities of chlorine.

Orbital Period: 110.2 Earth Years
Radius: 16,622 km
Day Length: 18.6 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>159</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A dark asteroid of mixed carbonaceous materials.
Radius: 42 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>160</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Metallic Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A metal-rich asteroid.
Radius: 139 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>161</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>true</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>MSV Khenarthi</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
The Khenarthi is a modular conveyor of unknown design, and looks much like a tent drifting through space. The surface is covered with large, crudely-drawn advertising billboards. Attempting to ping the ship resulted in a return transmission showing an image of a feline biped, who ‘has wares if you have coin’. A secondary transmission, poorly encrypted, makes reference to an illicit substance known only as ‘moon sugar’.

Registry: Rawl'kha Shipping, Elsweyr
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>162</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Clotanca</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Clotanca is a large but low-density terrestrial world with an atmosphere of nitrogen and carbon monoxide. Its crust is composed of sulphur and unremarkable silicates. Occasional deposits of heavy metals, usually the result of meteor strikes, dot the surface.

High-speed winds, powered by the hot blue star Caspian, present a constant hazard. Atmospheric entry is hazardous, and EVAs are discouraged.

Orbital Period: 124.7 Earth Years
Radius: 7810 km
Day Length: 19.7 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.73 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 92 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.78 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>163</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Almarcrux</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Almarcrux has an atmosphere of methane and ethane. Despite its great distance from Caspian, the energetic young star heats the surface almost temperate levels. Thick ground fogs are common at the terminator, where water ice frozen during the long dark side night meets the warm air masses from the day side. The crust is mainly composed of copper with deposits of sodium.

Almarcrux's abundant water and relatively mild temperature and gravity have placed it on the short list of terraforming candidate worlds. However, there is significant opposition from eco-ethics groups, who assert that Almarcrux's primitive methanotrophic bacteria may be a precursor to a full-fledged native ecology.

Orbital Period: 584.1 Earth Years
Radius: 4715 km
Day Length: 64.7 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.76 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 31 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.78 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>164</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Farnuri</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Farnuri has a trace atmosphere of carbon dioxide and helium. The surface is mainly composed of silica laced with iron oxides, indicating the world had an oxygenated atmosphere at some time in the past. Given the relative youth of the blue star Caspian and the significant gravity well of Farnuri, this must have occurred with astonishing swiftness, perhaps a result of some cataclysmic event. Further research is required.

Orbital Period: 352.7 Earth Years
Radius: 8968 km
Day Length: 67.8 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -98 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>165</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Antida</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Antida is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant. Its atmosphere is darkened by traces of sodium. It is one of relatively few planets known with an orbital period of more than a millennium.

Orbital Period: 1296.1 Earth Years
Radius: 29,657 km
Day Length: 12.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>166</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>167</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Chasca</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Chasca is a large but low-density world, fundamentally similar to its inner neighbor Inti. Like Inti, Chasca is tidally-locked to Matano. The same side always faces the sun, resulting in a scorching day side and a frozen night side. In the temperate areas around the terminator, temperatures average around 30 Celcius. Combined with a nitrogen-oxygen atmosphere, this slender band of habitable terrain allows limited colonization by humans.

Chasca's ring is unique. It appears to be, for lack of a better term, a massive piece of alien "installation art." The rings are made of small pieces of synthetic material, and are almost invisible from space. From the ground, they catch and scatter the light of Matano in picturesque ways. It is not known who created the ring, or when.

Chasca is very early development, with little more than a few pioneer teams scattered across the surface. Information is being collated about native hazards and ecology, while a massive colonist recruiting drive is gearing up back on Earth.

Colony Founded: 2183
Population: 150

Orbital Period: 1.3 Earth Years
Radius: 8059 km
Day Length: 1.3 Earth Years
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.86 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 67 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>168</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Inti</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Inti is a terrestrial planet with an atmosphere composed of ammonia and helium. Its surface is mainly composed of sodium oxide with deposits of magnesium. Its density is rather low, leaving the planet tide-locked to Matano.

Inti is an unremarkable world, drawing little more than a cursory scan for surface pirate anchorages when Alliance patrols enter the system.

Orbital Period: 0.6 Earth Years
Radius: 9032 km
Day Length: 0.6 Earth Years
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.56 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 157 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.99 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>169</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Hashmal</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A craggy world of basaltic mountains, Hashmal is wracked by constant geologic activity. Tectonic plates are constantly piling up new mountains or collapsing old ones. The planet’s surface is covered in massive rifts.

Orbital scans show what appears to be a tower standing on one of the tallest peaks, dubbed the “Pharos of Ridorana” for its luminous surface. Much like the lighthouses of ancient Earth, the foot is littered with the remains of expeditionary ships that ventured too near and crashed against the rocks. The tower itself, however, remains untouched by the chaos.

Orbital Period: 29.7 Earth Years
Radius: 6843 km
Day Length: 56.7 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.2 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -116 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>170</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Illapa</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Illapa is a hydrogen-helium gas giant with an unusual ruby color caused by contaminants in the atmosphere. The world has over 120 moons, one of the highest totals of all known systems.

Once full development of Chasca colony begins, a helium-3 refining infrastructure will be developed in the Illapa system, concentrated on the large ice moon of Coniraya.

Orbital Period: 74.1 Earth Years
Radius: 72,820 km
Day Length: 15.7 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>171</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Supay</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Supay has the composition of an ice dwarf planet, but is unusually large for such a body. It has a trace atmosphere of krypton and xenon. The frozen surface is dotted with deposits composed of potassium and light metals, brought to the surface by cryovolcanic processes.

Supay's icy surface was often used as a source of potable water by passing merchant vessels. Since the Alliance claimed the inner system world of Chasca, satellites placed in orbit automatically bill any vessel landing on the world for the mass of water removed from the surface.

ExoGeni has had a difficult time keeping these satellites operational; they often meet with "accidents" caused by impact with jettisoned ship debris.

Orbital Period: 275.5 Earth Years
Radius: 4317 km
Day Length: 63.4 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -216 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.25 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>172</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>173</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Metallic Asteroid </PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A metal-rich asteroid.
Radius: 47 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>174</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>175</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Rocky Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
This asteroid has an unusually sculpted and artistic appearance, with many long, sweeping curves.
Radius: 34 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>176</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Tuntau</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Tuntau is an enormous, low-density terrestrial planet, with a thick atmosphere of methane and helium. Despite being nearly 20 AU from Phoenix, the star’s great heat and the insulating thickness of the atmosphere make the surface surprisingly temperate.

The crust is mainly composed of sodium and silicon dioxide with deposits of various light metals. While Tuntau is not habitable, the relative pleasantness of the surface conditions make it a popular location for small ships traveling through the Argos Rho cluster to land for drive discharge.

Orbital Period: 63.8 Earth Years
Radius: 11,867 km
Day Length: 69.7 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 3.12 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 21 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>177</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Patashi</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Patashi is a sun-blasted terrestrial world whose atmosphere was blasted away millennia ago by the star Phoenix. The surface is scorching hot, and mainly composed of iron with deposits of tin.

Due to its relatively low density, Patashi is tidally locked to Phoenix. Seas of molten light metals cover much of the sunward side.

Orbital Period: 0.3 Earth Years
Radius: 7082 km
Day Length: 0.3 Earth Years
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 546 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.75 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>178</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Sylsalto</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Sylsalto is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant. It has no remarkable features.

Orbital Period: 36.0 Earth Years
Radius: 56,621 km
Day Length: 13.6 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>179</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Vebinok</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Vebinok is a small terrestrial world with a thin atmosphere of krypton and xenon. Its frozen surface is mainly composed of carbonaceous material, water ice, and low-density silicates. Rare but concentrated lodes of light metals have been deposited by asteroid impacts.

One hemisphere of Vebinok is covered by surface deposits of oxidized copper. Approximately 270 years ago a turian bulk gas transport was attacked by pirates in the Phoenix system. Damaged, it made a rough landing on Vebinok. The heat of the landing melted significant quantities of surface ice, and ruptured shipping containers spilled LOX across the surface. Before this evaporated and escaped Vebinok’s weak gravity, it reacted to cause the widespread rust.

Orbital Period: 94.5 Earth Years
Radius: 3379 km
Day Length: 68.3 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.27 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -154 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.28 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>180</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>181</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Fragmented Asteroid </PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
This asteroid appears to be a piece of a larger planet that was blasted away by firepower of unimaginable magnitude. Debris litters the area around it. Ships with high-grade sensor packages can pick up a weak, intermittent transmission that one ship log described as ‘millions of voices crying out in terror.’
Radius: 71 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>182</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>183</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Metgos</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
WARNING: Level 2 Heat Hazard

Metgos is a large terrestrial planet with an atmosphere of carbon dioxide and nitrogen. Its hot surface is mainly composed of nickel with deposits of potassium and heavy metals. It is a mineralogical treasure trove, with concentrated heavy elements constantly being brought to the surface by volcanic activity.

Metgos is inhospitable and dangerous, and expeditions must be well-prepared to survive any length of time. With its high mass, heat-trapping clouds and constant volcanic venting, Metgos seems well on its way to becoming a Venusian "pressure cooker" world.

Orbital Period: 2.8 Earth Years
Radius: 7301 km
Day Length: 47.2 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 169 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>184</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Varmalus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Varmalus has a thick atmosphere of nitrogen and helium. Its surface is scorching hot, and mainly composed of alumina with deposits of borax. The planet has an extensive network of subterranean caves, formed over the millennia by volcanic processes. In these relatively cool areas, some primitive life has developed.

Orbital Period: 0.4 Earth Years
Radius: 9593 km
Day Length: 19.4 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.3 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 503 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>185</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Theyar</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Theyar is a large gas giant with traces of chlorine and sodium in its atmosphere. It also has a significant amount of water vapor in the clouds of its upper atmosphere.

Theyar was struck by an asteroid at least 12 kilometers in diameter within the last hundred years. The superheating caused by the impactor’s atmospheric passage created a large bank of vicious storms along the equatorial band.

Orbital Period: 12.8 Earth Years
Radius: 60,774 km
Day Length: 11.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>186</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Canrum</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Canrum is a small, rocky world with a trace atmosphere of methane and krypton. Its surface is mainly composed of magnesium and silicates with deposits of carbon.

Canrum was the site of the warlord Shiagur's defeat by turian peacekeeping forces during the Krogan Rebellions. While this band was not especially powerful, Shiagur was a female warlord – and one of the few remaining fertile females, at that. She had, through viciousness and cunning, parlayed her unique value into a position of power. Krogan males competed for the right to join her band and lie with her.

When Shiagur's death was announced, vengeful male krogan admirers near and far swore blood oaths against the participating turian crews. In the end, several thousand of the turian participants were killed in open combat or through assassination. To this day, many krogan proudly proclaim that they have the "blood of Shiagur."

Orbital Period: 67.3 Earth Years
Radius: 5,220 km
Day Length: 32.5 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.07 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -132 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.55 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>187</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Syba</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Syba is a standard Neptune-type gas giant, the upper cloud decks of its hydrogen-helium atmosphere tinted a dramatic blue by traces of methane.

Orbital Period: 162.1 Earth Years
Radius: 45,145 km
Day Length: 12.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>188</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Unidentified Space Facility</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>This space station appears to have been assembled from used "off the shelf" civilian ship modules of diverse origins. There are no obvious hull markings, and it is not broadcasting any ID signal.</PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>189</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Vectra</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Vectra is a typical hydrogen-helium gas giant with traces of methane and sodium in its atmosphere. The heat of the star Gorgon is slowly blasting away the gas giant's massive atmosphere, which is visible as a long, dim tail that trails behind the planet.

Orbital Period: 234.7 Earth Years
Radius: 69,833 km
Day Length: 234.7 Earth Years
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>190</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Camaron</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Camaron is a terrestrial world with a thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and argon. The surface is scorching hot, and mainly composed of iron with deposits of nickel. Like Wuo, Camaron is tide-locked to the blue giant, forever "looking into the face of the Gorgon."

Orbital Period: 664.8 Earth Years
Radius: 5198 km
Day Length: 664.8 Earth Years
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.23 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 747 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.55 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>191</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Sharblu</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A standard hydrogen-helium gas giant, the methane in Sharblu's atmosphere gives it an azure hue.

The asari crew who initially surveyed the system (during Earth's 17th century) named Sharblu after a then-popular soprano. The singer was renowned for her unusual skin tone, which was quite similar to that of the planet.

Orbital Period: 1711.0 Earth Years
Radius: 43,342 km
Day Length: 1711.0 Earth Years
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>192</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Slekon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Orbiting at an unbelievable distance of 710 AU (over 66 billion kilometers) from Gorgon, Slekon is a huge gas giant, with an atmosphere tainted by methane and chlorine.

Orbital Period: 4483.1 Earth Years
Radius: 77,115 km
Day Length: 4483.1 Earth Years
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>193</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Wuo</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Wuo is a terrestrial planet only known from scan data picked up by unmanned probes. Though over 76 AU from the blue giant Gorgon, temperatures in Wuo's orbit are still dangerously high. Only ships with very powerful heat radiating systems can venture that deep into the system.

Fortunately, Wuo is not a terribly interesting world. It has a thin atmosphere of nitrogen and methane, and the scorching surface is mainly composed of alumina with deposits of platinum. The world is tidally locked to Wuo, leaving the sunward side scorched and irradiated wasteland, and the dark side a frigid and ice-crusted.

Orbital Period: 158.0 Earth Years
Radius: 6959 km
Day Length: 158.0 Earth Years
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.44 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 1157 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.66 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>194</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Presrop</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Presrop is the moon of Klendagon. It is a frigid, barren world, with an extremely thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and ethane. The crust contains plentiful deposits of heavy metals. The Alliance has opened bidding for the moon's mineral rights, but exploitation will be complicated by the system's proximity to the "Five Kiloparsec Ring" around the galactic core. The Ring is an area of intense star formation, and too dangerous to safely travel.

Presrop's landscape is a nightmare of jagged, overlapping ridges and geological shock zones created by some ancient disaster. This has not deterred a generation of illegal "wildcat miners" from attempting to exploit the moon's mineral riches. Unfortunately, many have lost their lives.

Orbital Distance: 168,500 km (from Klendagon)
Orbital Period: 10.8 Earth Days
Radius: 4113 km
Day Length: 10.8 Earth Days
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.1 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -73 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>195</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Tamahera</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Tamahera has a thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and xenon. The surface is icy, and composed of sodium oxide with deposits of calcium. It contains a few unremarkable metals, but mainly consists of rock. The presence of canyons and flood plains indicates that liquid water once existed, suggesting Tamahera had a thicker insulating atmosphere in the past.

Orbital Period: 1.4 Earth Years
Radius: 6302 km
Day Length: 40.1 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.34 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -30 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.66
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>196</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Canctra</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A terrestrial world of average size, Canctra's atmosphere is composed of nitrogen and argon. Its frozen surface is mainly composed of tin with deposits of calcium. Aside from some spectacular formations of water-ice at the poles, the planet has little to recommend it.

Orbital Distance: 14.3 AU
Orbital Period: 60.6 Earth Years
Radius: 5471 km
Day Length: 66.7 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.83 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -175 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>197</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Altea</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Altea is a large, terrestrial world and was the seat of King Alfor at the height of his power. A peaceful and learned people, the Alteans had keen interest in science, diplomacy, and technological advancement. Unfortunately, a large-scale scientific experiment in collaboration with the Galra caused unimaginable destruction and their alliance was broken. Zarkon, now styling himself Emperor, betrayed King Alfor and turned his fleets on Altea. The combined firepower of his capital ships devastated the planet.

Once verdant and thriving, Altea is now devoid of life. Magma storms erupt continuously from the shattered core. The planet is surrounded by a ring system of its own rubble as it slowly breaks into pieces in the aftermath of the destruction.

Orbital Period: 128.2 Earth Years
Radius: 68,714 km
Day Length: 17.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>true</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>198</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>199</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Metallic Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A metal-rich asteroid.
Radius: 83 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>200</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Klendagon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Klendagon is an arid terrestrial, slightly larger than Earth, but with a lower density that reflects its relative lack of heavier elements. The crust is composed of tin and aluminum, with wide deserts of dust-fine sand that are easily stirred by the wind.

Klendagon's most striking feature is, of course, the Great Rift valley that stretches across the southern hemisphere. What is most fascinating about the Rift is that it does not appear to be natural. The geological record suggests it is the result of a "glancing blow" by a mass accelerator round of unimaginable destructive power. This occurred some thirty-seven million years ago.

Orbital Period: 2.3 Earth Years
Radius: 7377 km
Day Length: 53.6 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.64 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -53 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>201</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ontarom</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Though Ontarom's surface is uncomfortably hot, its nitrogen-oxygen atmosphere and abundant, shallow seas make it an ideal candidate for habitation by most known species.

Unfortunately, the orbit of the moon of Thonal has been slowly decaying since the system coalesced. Its proximity is beginning to have tidal effects, and its dynamo-like revolution through Ontarom's magnetic field is generating increasing powerful electrical storms.

While some have suggested emplacement of mass effect drives in an attempt to lighten the moon and correct its orbit, the scale of such a project - tens of thousands of drives, costing enough to bankrupt the governments of all the Citadel races - make it a pipe dream. A multi-racial effort is underway to catalogue and preserve the unique genetic diversity of Ontarom's vibrant young biosphere. ExoGeni Corp. and Heyuan Genomics represent the Alliance's share of the effort.

Orbital Period: 1.2 Earth Years
Radius: 6443 km
Day Length: 39.1 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.79 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 58 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.82 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>202</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Klencory</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Klencory is a rock and ice planet with an atmosphere composed of chlorine and argon. The frozen surface is mainly composed of potassium with deposits of Iron.

Klencory is famously claimed by the eccentric volus billionaire Kumun Shol. He claims that a vision of a higher being told him to seek on Klencory the "lost crypts of beings of light". These entities were supposedly created at the dawn of time to protect organic life from synthetic "machine devils."

Shol has been excavating on Klencory's toxic surface for two decades, at great expense. No government has valued the world enough to evict his small army of mercenaries.

Orbital Period: 20.6 Earth Years
Radius: 7677 km
Day Length: 18.3 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.01 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -109 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.82 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>203</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Famfrit</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Famfrit is an ice dwarf world, its surface composed almost entirely of frozen water. Solar winds stir the dark cloud cover into a roiling mass. An unusually large and beautiful ring of ice crystals orbits the planet, the result of an asteroid impact that shattered the surface and threw a great deal of melted water into the atmosphere. The rings will completely decay in a few thousand years. Nevertheless, they remain a popular subject in the art forms of several species.

Orbital Period: 272.2 Earth Years
Radius: 3111 km
Day Length: 23.9 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -188 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.09 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>true</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>204</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Juncro</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Juncro is a hydrogen-helium gas giant with traces of chlorine and sodium in its upper atmosphere. Like Uranus is the Sol system, it is "tipped on its side," its north pole facing the star Newton.

Orbital Period: 60.0 Earth Years
Radius: 66,642 km
Day Length: 16.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>205</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>MSV Fedele</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
The Fedele is a Kowloon class modular conveyor of human design. In addition to the standard cargo bay, the hull has several biological research modules attached.

Registry: Private Owner, Dr. R. Heart
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>206</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Matol</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Several attempts to chart Matol have been made, but none have been successful. By normal standards a small rock planet, Matol has a dense atmosphere composed of carbon dioxide and argon, with a surprising amount of water vapor. Fogs and rain are common on the barren, lifeless surface.

Matol is pleasant enough to be considered a terraforming prospect, though its low mass and the high radiation of the energetic blue star Herschel place it fairly far down on the list.
Orbital Period: 207.3 Earth Years
Radius: 4077 km
Day Length: 34.6 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.49 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 33 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.5 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>207</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Clugon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Clugon's hydrogen-helium atmosphere is given a fairly dramatic emerald tint by chlorine and ionized gases. It has nearly 100 moons.

Orbital Period: 1013.7.1 Earth Years
Radius: 17,988 km
Day Length: 19.2 Earth Hour
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>208</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Clobaka</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Clobaka is a moderately sized terrestrial world with a hazy hydrocarbon atmosphere. Its surface is mainly composed of chlorides with deposits of solid and liquid-form hydrocarbons.

Orbital Period: 2052.3 Earth Years
Radius: 8198 km
Day Length: 59.7 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.81 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 7 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>209</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>210</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Tungel</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Tungel is a massive terrestrial world, nearly twice the size of Earth, with a dense atmosphere of nitrogen and ethane. Its scorching hot surface is mainly composed of iron, with extensive deposits of heavy metals and radioactives. It is a mineralogical treasure trove, and many corporations are lobbying for mining rights.

Orbital Period: 85.8 Earth Years
Radius: 11,539 km
Day Length: 42.4 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 2.0 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 242 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.9 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>211</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Rocky Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A metal-rich asteroid.
Radius: 118 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>212</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Altahe</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Altahe is an exceptional form of planet called a Roche World. Put simply, it is one half of a pair of small and unusually dense terrestrial worlds (Altahe and Ontahe) that orbit each other so closely, they effectively share a single atmosphere. This is does not mean that one could fly from one to the other, but both have identical atmospheres, and dust from one often can be found on the other.

Both worlds share an atmosphere of nitrogen and ethane.  The surface is warm, and mainly composed of silica dust and dark basaltic rocks, with extensive deposits of heavy metals and radioactives. Tidal effects from Ontahe create constant heavy wind.

Orbital Distance: 0.8 AU
Orbital Period: 0.8 Earth Years
Radius: 4404 km
Day Length: 53.8 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.98 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 36 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.1G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>213</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Farthorl</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A modest terrestrial planet, Farthorl has a thin atmosphere composed of carbon dioxide and chlorine. The crust is mainly composed of sulfur with deposits of nickel. The terrain is extremely rough - a patchwork of craggy, overlapping craters dating back to the formation of the solar system. Farthorl is tidally locked to the star Acheron. The day side has never been fully mapped.

Orbital Period: 0.2 Earth Years
Radius: 6506 km
Day Length: 0.2 Earth Years
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.69 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 239 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>214</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Grosalgen</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
An enigmatic rock and ice planet, Grosalgen has a thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and ethane. The surface is composed of frozen water and chlorine.

Orbital Period: 41.5 Earth Years
Radius: 5198 km
Day Length: 28.9 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.53 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -175 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.6 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>215</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Imaneya</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Though exceptionally large for a terrestrial world, Imaneya is composed of water ice and with a core of various carbonaceous compounds. It has a density only half that of Earth, and an atmosphere of nitrogen and carbon monoxide. The surface is composed of surprisingly pure water ice, with a high albedo.

Orbital Distance: 22.2 AU
Orbital Period: 117.7 Earth Years
Radius: 11,621 km
Day Length: 56.4 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.88 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -185 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.9 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>216</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>217</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Carbonaceous Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A dark asteroid of mixed carbonaceous materials. This asteroid shows sign of impacts by weapons fire.
Radius: 63 km
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>218</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nepmos</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Nepmos is a resource-rich terrestrial world somewhat larger than Earth, with a dense atmosphere of sulphur dioxide and argon. Nepmos' crust is very thin and unstable, not more than 8 kilometers deep in any location. Subsurface magma flows are a hazard to ground travel, and earthquakes are frequent. While heavy metals and radioactives are plentiful, this geological instability has deterred investment by mining concerns.

An additional complication is that the Styx Cluster lies uncomfortably close to the "Five Kiloparsec Ring" around the galactic core. The Ring contains a great deal of molecular hydrogen, fueling the majority of the galaxy's star formation. This area is too dangerous to safely travel.

Orbital Period: 0.7 Earth Years
Radius: 7593 km
Day Length: 68.1 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.12 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 68 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>219</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Quaji</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Quaji is a terrestrial planet with an atmosphere of methane and ethane. The surface is composed of silica with deposits of uranium and heavy metals. Clouds of small water ice crystals are common. Quaji's skies are full of fine silica dust. From the surface, the sky has a pronounced salmon hue.

The cursory initial scans from the Alliance surveyor ship Ibn Battuta showed geometric patterns in the northern hemisphere deserts, visible only in the ultraviolet band. Normandy's sensors see nothing of the kind.

Orbital Period: 2.9 Earth Years
Radius: 5160 km
Day Length: 38.7 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.83 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -7 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>220</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Wermani</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Wermani has only been visited by a single unmanned probe. It is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant with large formations of water vapor clouds in the upper atmosphere.

Orbital Period: 9.9 Earth Years
Radius: 71541 km
Day Length: 9.2 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>221</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Chofen</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Chofen is an unusually small hydrogen-helium gas giant, with traces of sulphur and hydrocarbons in the atmosphere. The Alliance surveyor ship Ibn Battuta reported inconclusive evidence of hydrocarbon life in the deeper layers of the atmosphere (over 1000 kilometers below the cloud tops), where pressure compresses Chofen's hydrogen into a liquid state.

Proof of life in this environment would prove many long-standing theories. Unfortunately, only a probe with extremely expensive mass effect generators could survive the crushing pressure long enough to send back useful data - and the probe would be lost in the attempt. Simple expense makes investigation doubtful.

Orbital Period: 56.9 Earth Years
Radius: 21481 km
Day Length: 13.7 Earth Hours



    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>222</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>223</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>true</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>MSV New York</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
The New York is a Kowloon class modular conveyor of human design, named after one of the largest metropolitan areas of Earth. The ship is known as a traveling tourist trap, bringing many New York cultural sensations around the galaxy.

This ship appears to be in a shut down state; the systems powered down and the pizza long cold, adrift in space. Visual scans show a large poster sized sticker near the rear thrusters, with the faded phrase "We brake for nobody".

Registry: Traveling Rays, Earth
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>224</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Antiroprus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Antiroprus is a hydrogen-helium gas giant that formed in the outer regions of Ming's system, and is in the process of migrating inwards. In a few million years, the planet's atmosphere will begin to "boil away" into space.

There is a sizeable temperature difference between the side of Antiroprus facing the energetic blue giant primary and the side facing the cold of deep space. This variance powers massive cyclonic wind systems. The intense heat it absorbs from the sun, in addition to its own internal heat engine, causes the planet's dark side to radiate faintly in the infrared.

Orbital Period: 284.2 Earth Years
Radius: 57,948 km
Day Length: 10.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>225</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Parag</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Parag is a large rock planet, with an atmosphere composed of nitrogen and argon. Despite lying over 600 AU from Ming, its surface is scorching hot, and mainly composed of alumina with deposits of silver. Due to the radiation and heat, landing on Parag's sunward side with anything less than warship-grade shielding will likely be fatal. Parag rotates at a retrograde to the rest of the Ming system, indicating it is likely a captured body.

Orbital Period: 1930.3 Earth Years
Radius: 7979 km
Day Length: 22.4 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 1.58 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 1117 Celsius
Surface Gravity 2.0 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>226</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Altanorch</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Altanorch is a small but typical hydrogen-helium gas giant with no outstanding features. Its combination of strong magnetic field and relatively shallow gravity well make it a popular "stopover" world for discharging FTL drive cores.

Orbital Period: 4005.7 Earth Years
Radius: 32,605 km
Day Length: 16.3 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>227</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>228</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mavigon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
WARNING: Level 1 Cold Hazard

Mavigon is a small rock and ice planet with a thin atmosphere of ammonia and methane. The surface is frozen, and mainly composed of tin with deposits of potassium.

The planet has a rudimentary ammonia-based life, mainly concentrated around geothermal vents deep underground. Severe storm cycles are common; due to limited visibility, navigation may be difficult.

Orbital Period: 42.3 Earth Years
Radius: 4906 km
Day Length: 52.0 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.82 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -124 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>229</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Paravin</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Paravin is a small, unremarkable rock world. The surface is scorching hot, and mainly composed of calcium with deposits of aluminum. Paravin's low mass has left it tidally locked to the star Han. If there were any resources of value, mining stations could be established on the relatively temperate "twilight band".

Orbital Period: 0.5 Earth Years
Radius: 4839 km
Day Length: 0.5 Earth Years
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.0 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: 414 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 0.5 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>230</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Huningto</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Huningto is a Jovian-sized gas giant with a standard hydrogen-helium atmosphere. Traces of methane give the planet its distinct cobalt blue tint. Spectral analysis indicates its extensive ring system is mostly composed of ice crystals. Huningto has an exceptionally powerful magnetic field, which creates strong radio interference throughout the inner system.

Orbital Period: 31.8 Earth Years
Radius: 73,733 km
Day Length: 16.7 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>231</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Farcrothu</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
A standard gas hydrogen-helium gas giant, Farcrothu is only distinguished by its moons; several dozen of them have been sculpted into the likenesses of an arthropodal alien race not yet known to Council science. Radiometric dating suggests the moons were worked over half a million years ago.

Orbital Period: 112.1 Earth Years
Radius: 66,014 km
Day Length: 8.4 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>232</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pantsless</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
Pantless is a large rock world, with an unusually thin atmosphere of methane, likely caused by uncovered emissions from the surface. The world’s crust contains extensive deposits of uranium. With a total mass more than four times that of Earth, Pantsless should have a significantly thicker atmosphere. It also features an unusual crater on the lower half, effectively splitting the planet into two ‘limbs’. This unusual feature has flagged it as worthy of scientific investigation.

Orbital Period: 297.4 Earth Years
Radius: 8927 km
Day Length: 36.0 Earth Hours
Atmospheric Pressure: 0.06 Earth Atmospheres
Surface Temperature: -174 Celsius
Surface Gravity: 2.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
    <IsHotOnly>false</IsHotOnly>
    <IsColdOnly>false</IsColdOnly>
    <IsHabitable>false</IsHabitable>
    <PopulationMin>0</PopulationMin>
    <PopulationMax>0</PopulationMax>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
</planetinfos>
