<planetinfos>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>0</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Citadel</PlanetName>
    <MapBaseNames>
      <MapBaseName>MapEND</MapBaseName>
      <MapBaseName>MapSTA</MapBaseName>
    </MapBaseNames>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Supposedly constructed by the long-extinct Protheans, this colossal deep-space station serves as the capital of the Citadel Council. Gravity is simulated through rotation, and is a comfortable 1.02 standard Gs on the Wards and a light 0.3 standard Gs on the Presidium Ring. (Small sections of graffiti have been found in station sub-structures, suggesting that perhaps the Protheans were not responsible for the bulk of construction. Bemused maintenance workers report that the graffiti is often a variation of ‘Keeper #13489317498813789 was here.’)

      TRAVEL ADVISORY: Due to new Citadel regulations, ‘down the shaft’ is no longer an acceptable vector when speaking with Traffic Control. There are also no fish in the Presidium.

      TRAVEL ADVISORY: Elevators to and from the Presidium are currently experiencing issues and are operating at minimum speeds, please plan accordingly. If you are in need of urgent transportation, please use the Citadel shuttles or use the stairs.

      Total Length (Open): 44.7 km
      Diameter (Open): 12.8 km
      Population:  13.2 million (not including keepers)
      Gross Weight: 7.11 billion metric tons
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>1</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>*Placeholder*</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>*Placeholder*</PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>2</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mercury</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Initial exploration on Mercury was limited by the planet's proximity to the sun. However, a probe sent into the atmosphere transmitted images of development on the surface. Most were of blocky, unremarkable ruins. However, a large triangular super-structure was clearly visible in one of the images. Later attempts at investigation were unsuccessful, as the probes simply disappeared upon contact with the super-structure. Several solar power stations were eventually established. All but a few seem to have collapsed into the mass of blocks and rubble.

      Population: 340

      Orbital Distance: 0.39 AU
      Orbital Period: 88 Earth Days
      Radius: 2440 km
      Day Length: 58.7 Earth Days
      Atmospheric Pressure: Trace
      Surface Temperature: 430 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.38 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>3</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Venus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Due to the inhospitable atmosphere, development on Venus has been limited to research facilities. A small company known as Au Raa holds most of the rights to the planet. Information on this company is not available to the general public. As such, the nature of their research facilities is a topic of much speculation, with the most popular rumors involving manipulation of the human genome. However, this cannot be substantiated and the sulphuric atmosphere of the planet deters any long-range scanning from curious eyes.

      Population: 800

      Orbital Distance: 0.72 AU
      Orbital Period: 224.7 Earth Days
      Radius: 6052 km
      Day Length: 243 Earth Days
      Atmospheric Pressure: 90 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 465 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>4</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Earth</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      For detailed information, please refer to the standard issue Alliance Galactic Codex. Please note: the section regarding ‘Flat Earth and You’ is no longer up to date, as it was discovered just last year that the planet is not, in fact, a giant disc supported by four elephants and floating through space on the back of a giant turtle.

      Population (Surface): 11.4 billion
      Population (L4 and L5 stations): 250,000

      Orbital Distance: 1 AU
      Orbital Period: 1 Earth Years
      Radius: 6378 km
      Day Length: 23.9 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 23 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>5</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mars</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Mars was once the future hope of humanity, as wars and resource shortages made life on Earth ever more untenable. However, the first scientific teams sent to the planet discovered that terraforming on a massive scale had turned the planet into an unstable warren of tunnels, inhabited by a massive worm. Carvings found in caves on the surface suggest that the as-yet unknown inhabitants of the planet may have formed a cult, worshipping this worm as their god.

      Colony Founded: 2103
      Population: 3.4 million
      Capital: Lowell City

      Orbital Distance: 1.52 AU
      Orbital Period: 1.88 Earth Years
      Radius: 3402 km
      Day Length: 24.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.06 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -138 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.38 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>6</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Jupiter</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Jupiter's deep gravity well and lethal radiation have prevented any significant exploration of the planet. Some of the moons have been developed, with the largest outpost belonging to SST Laboratories, located on Ganymede. Most commonly associated with their Siege Automatons, the company has fallen out of favor in recent years due to Automaton usage in a major Earth crisis. Several abandoned B73 models can be seen littering the upper atmosphere of the moon.

      Population (all moons): 9100

      Orbital Distance: 5.2 AU
      Orbital Period: 11.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 71,492 km
      Day Length: 9.93 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>7</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Saturn</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Saturn has been a major source of helium-3 fuel for fusion plants since the 2150s. The moon of Titan is mined for hydrocarbons, and used as a hostile environment training facility for Alliance Marines. The rings of Saturn are littered with shredded ship remains, as competitive racing along the rings has proliferated.

      Population (orbitals and Titan): 117,000
      Capital: Huygens Dome

      Orbital Distance: 9.5 AU
      Orbital Period: 29.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 60,268 km
      Day Length: 10.3 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>8</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Uranus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      After the development of mass effect FTL drive, distant Uranus was the target of a "land rush" to exploit its combination of plentiful helium-3 fuel and shallow (for a gas giant) gravity well. Today Uranus is the largest producer of He-3 in Alliance space. Probing is the most common way to extract gas and other useful resources from the  gas giant’s exterior, but some deep investigative vessels have also attempted to extract denser gases from farther within the planet. Most attempts have proven unsuccessful as commercial-grade fuel tanks are unable to sustain the pressure and result in a blow out.

      Population: 371,000
      Capital: Sakharov Station

      Orbital Distance: 19.2 AU
      Orbital Period: 121.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 25,559 km
      Day Length: 17.3 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>9</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Neptune</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Neptune is an advanced training facility for combat operations. While used heavily by the Alliance, it is a commercial offering, permitting training for both military and non-military personnel. Through the use of cutting edge simulation technology, training can be done with very high degrees of realism, with low potential psychological impact on the participants in the event of a catastrophic failure. Their most famous simulation takes place in a crashed subway station, aptly named Firebase Neptune. This simulation is designed to improve the participants resistance to optical attacks on the battlefield by utilizing purple and white squares to represent walls and ceilings. Viewers of this simulation often call this "Eyebleed".

      Population (Triton): 70

      Orbital Distance: 29.1 AU
      Orbital Period: 164.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 24,764 km
      Day Length: 16.1 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>10</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pluto</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Pluto is the gravitational "anchor" for the Prothean mass relay to Arcturus. Pluto and the Charon Relay (formerly encased in ice, and considered a moon) orbit each other. Pluto was stripped of its planetary status in the year 2006 after leading scientists on the systems capital planet, Earth, started betting on an ancient sports game known as "Curling". Leaders from multiple countries disagreed with the decision, but were unable to change course as the lead scientists of space at the time were bound by their bet. Today, Pluto is little more than a staging ground for the Charon Mass Relay.

      Population (gateway stations): 9300

      Orbital Distance: 39.5 AU
      Orbital Period: 247.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 1151 km
      Day Length: 9.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: Trace
      Surface Temperature: -229 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.06 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>11</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Luna</PlanetName>
    <MapBaseNames>
      <MapBaseName>MapUNC51</MapBaseName>
    </MapBaseNames>
    <PlanetDescription>
      An early source of helium-3, Luna is now mined for materials used in space habitat construction. A folk legend from before space travel in the Sol system once described Luna as being made of cheese, of which kind being debated widely among the population of Earth. While it has long been proven that Luna is in fact not made out of cheese, Neil Armstrong, the first human to step foot on Luna, is said to have thrown a wheel of cheese out of his landing craft upon first touchdown in 1969, in commemoration of this legend. While the wheel has never been recovered, it was supposedly of the Gouda variety. When asked why he chose this type, Neil supposedly replied with  "It is simply the best kind of cheese".

      Colony Founded: 2069
      Population: 4.1 million
      Capital: Armstrong

      Orbital Distance:  384,403 km (from Earth)
      Orbital Period: 27.3 Earth Days
      Radius: 1737 km
      Day Length: 27.3 Earth Days
      Atmospheric Pressure: Trace
      Surface Temperature: -53 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>12</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Corporate investment of the asteroid belt is at all time high due to discovery of a new element, adamantium. Considered one of the hardest minerals known in the galaxy, mining it has proved elusive for even the most powerful explosives. Some asteroids have been hauled away to be used directly as projectiles in space warfare by various species.

      Orbital Distance: 1.8 to 4.5 AU
      Population: 11,000
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>13</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Eden Prime</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Dorstonis</PlanetName2>
    <MapBaseNames>
      <MapBaseName>MapPRO</MapBaseName>
    </MapBaseNames>
    <PlanetDescription>
      This pastoral world marks the founding of the first Earth colony beyond a mass relay. The biosphere, though slightly thin, is well-suited to both humans and native Earth species. The original Systems Alliance colony was soon augmented by the arrival of corporate developments.

      Most notable of these was Ondore Lhusu’s discovery of the magicite mines, now a major export and source of revenue. The bulk of the development on %PLANETNAME% is still primarily agricultural, however, and the rolling green hills would not look out of place on Earth.

      Colony Founded: 2152
      Population: 3.7 million
      Capital: Bhujerba

      Orbital Period: 2.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 7026 km
      Day Length: 64.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.45 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 23 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.04 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>14</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Neo Arcadia</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A hostile and closed off world, Neo Arcadia was once a world filled with lush forests and deep blue oceans. Technology use on Neo Arcadia advanced too rapidly for sustainability, eventually plunging the world into multiple devastating wars spanning hundreds of years.

      Today Neo Arcadia is the name of the capital city, the only remaining hospitable place on the planet. Facing an energy crisis to power their remaining technologies, the leadership is in a civil war with a resistance force that is attempting to solve the energy crisis.

      Attempts to intervene and stop the war have proven unsuccessful, and other space faring species have found little success in their attempts to negotiate trade deals.

      Orbital Period: 0.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 10893 km
      Day Length: 25.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 16.17 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 358 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 5.0 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>15</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Corneria</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Corneria, the fourth planet of the %SYSTEMNAME% system, is an Earth-like terrestrial world primarily used for farming. It is the most populated planet in the system, with the majority of the population living in the mountain ranges that have rich soils for farming. The capital city has been targeted multiple times by terrorists in recent years as several parties from opposing political factions have attempted to conquer the planet.

      Population: 2.2 Billion

      Orbital Period: 52.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 74,333 km
      Day Length: 10.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>16</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Titania</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Millions of years ago, Titania was a once beautiful planet, with a thriving ecosystem full of intelligent, non-space faring life. A meteor impact with the planet reduced the paradise world to the arid desert it can be seen as today. Scientific expeditions by the asari have found remains of a civilization from some of the ancient races, however most intact pieces are thought to be buried deep under layers of ancient ash.

      Orbital Period:	129.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 3212 km
      Day Length: 63.9 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.02 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -203 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>17</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Venom</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A world once considered a possible golden planet, Venom now serves as a reminder about the dangers of terraforming uncharted worlds. Decades ago during an advanced terraforming experiment, multiple catastrophic events chained into one other, turning plans for a new paradise world into an evacuation.

      Venom’s oceans are now highly acidic, toxic to all but the most hearty of creatures. The majority of the planet’s surface is in low light or complete darkness, due to a constant thin layer of toxic smog in the atmosphere that killed off most surface dwelling organisms.

      Venom now acts as a popular death trap world, where all who are unfortunate enough to be stranded, are doomed to die a painful death.

      Known surviving population: 1
      Orbital Period: 1029.9 Earth Years
      Radius 3730 km
      Day Length: 69.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.19 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -216 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.3 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>18</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Noveria</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Grunty Industries</PlanetName2>
    <MapBaseNames>
      <MapBaseName>MapICE</MapBaseName>
    </MapBaseNames>
    <PlanetDescription>
      %PLANETNAME% is a small, frozen terrestrial world, barely habitable by conventional definitions. It is privately run by the %PLANETNAME% Development Corporation, which controls the production facilities that cover the planet. Due to the significant overcrowding of factories on the planet, pollution is widespread, some factories even being surrounded by toxic moats.

      Secret investigations into the factories have surfaced pictures of incredibly dangerous working conditions, including multiple broken windows going unrepaired, an open elevator shaft that several workers have died in, and a sentient blowtorch that lives in the basement of one of the facilities.

      Colony Founded: 2000
      Population: 2,200
      Planetary leader: Gruntilda Winkybunon

      Orbital Distance: 0.9 AU
      Orbital Period: 0.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 5656 km
      Day Length: 52.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.87 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -1 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.81
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>19</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Arrakis</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Arrakis has constant wind storms blowing across the surface due to its planetary tilt. Millenia of windstorms has eroded the surface crust down to a fine dust, which is carried around the planet on a near constant basis. With only trace amounts of natural precipitation, colonization attempts have proven to be tough for nearly all races, leaving Arrakis as a quiet, oft forgotten world.

      Orbital Period: 0.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 32,285 km
      Day Length: 13.4 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>20</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Outset</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Outset is a water world, with over 99% of its surface covered in ocean. Many small islands near the equator mark the only habitable areas for terrestrial life. Orbital scans show several underwater anomalies, but without further investigation, these items remain a mystery.

      Orbital Distance: 6.3 AU
      Orbital Period: 17.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 1089 km
      Day Length: 17.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.1 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 20 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.89 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>21</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Oswald</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Oswald is a private world, with little known about the planetside business conducted by its owner, Binary Helix. Named after an invention of the original corporation’s founder in the 1900s, Oswald is a quiet world. Orbital scans show multiple planetary defense installations on at least 6 different regions of the planet.

      Orbital Distance: 24.5 AU
      Orbital Period: 136.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 7547 km
      Day Length: 62.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.07 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -220 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>22</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Tallon IV</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      51 years ago, Tallon IV was impacted by a small meteorite that crashed into the northern hemisphere of the planet. In the years that followed, mutations of the local wildlife have rapidly increased, with the planet’s wildlife becoming increasingly hostile to visitors. Scientific instruments on the surface of the planet indicate a large radioactive energy source at the planet’s core, which has been steadily increasing over time.

      Orbital Period: 97.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 5756 km
      Day Length: 21.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.79 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 28 Celsius
      Surface Gravity:  0.97 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>23</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Aether</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Aether is a rogue planet in the %SYSTEMNAME% system, home to the Luminoth. Fifty years ago, a meteorite crashed into Aether with unusual force, destroying the planet's natural beauty. Shortly after the impact, all communication to the planetary leadership was lost, and teams sent by the Citadel Council to investigate never returned. Orbital scans indicate there has been no recent planetside activity by intelligent species.

      WARNING: This planet has been marked as hostile to lifeforms by the Citadel Council. Landing on this planet is not permitted.

      Orbital Period: 5.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 4905 km
      Day Length: 55.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 2.1 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 24 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>24</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Bespin</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Bespin is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant with traces of ammonia. Hydrocarbons in the atmosphere lend it a distinct tint. Thousands of gas mining stations litter the high atmosphere.

      Orbital Period: 52.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 35,417 km
      Day Length: 14.7 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>25</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Trevelyan</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Trevelyan is a lifeless rock with a thick, cloudy atmosphere. A glowing green "Jupiter spot" spins violently over the axis of the planet. A salarian religious cult claims that this spot is actually a breach between waking and dreaming worlds. Their teachings make many references to a Herald that will come and seal the rift forever.

      Orbital Period: 74.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 1163 km
      Day Length: 36.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -147 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>26</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>true</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>MSV Kaldwin</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      The Kaldwin is a Kowloon-class modular conveyor of human design. The ship appears to have been torn apart from the inside by some kind of void. A glowing emblem can be seen on a piece of metal spinning through space. The Normandy’s scanners identify it only as "Mark of the Outsider".

      Registry: Private Owner, Captain Sokolov
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>27</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Kass</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Kass’ atmosphere is tinted blue by trace quantities of methane. Deep crevasses criss-cross the surface, and a cheerfully eerie whistling noise can be heard when the wind blows across them.

      Orbital Period: 173.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 53,520 km
      Day Length: 15.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>28</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Antoneese</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      When Antoneese was first discovered, orbital surveys showed remains of an extinct species. Further investigation found inscriptions detailing the last days of intelligent life on the planet, which showed that they were nearing the ability to reach low orbit.

      During a commemorative event, the leader of the Antoneese told an ill timed joke, which escalated and eventually plunged their planet into a global war. The populations of Antoneese were devastated, leading to famine and a solar shield from the smoke. Most, if not all life on the planet died shortly after. The age of the texts detailing these events could not be reliably determined.

      Orbital Period: 12.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 6694 km
      Day Length: 59.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.19 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -178 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.16 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>29</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Zeal</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Zeal is a frozen terrestrial planet with a near-absent atmosphere. Scans reveal the remnants of several orbiting bodies, possibly space stations, although they appear to be made of rock. Frozen pillars of ice tether several of these bodies to the surface of the planet.

      There is little information available about Zeal. A single asari text makes brief reference to "Lavos", an alien life form that allegedly landed millenia ago and proceeded to drain the energy of every living being on the planet. Though scientifically unlikely, "Schala et Janus" is still a popular read among mythology enthusiasts.

      Orbital Period: 2.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 7708 km
      Day Length: 33.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.03 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -150 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>

    <IsColdOnly>trye</IsColdOnly>



  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>30</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Morte</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Morte is a frigid world with a thick nitrogen-argon atmosphere and several moons. The largest of these are Annah, Dak’kon, and Ignus.

      Experienced travelers more often refer to Morte as "Mortuary" due to the overlapping gravity wells between the planet and its moons. Ships trying to save fuel by flying between them are likely to find themselves dragged into orbit and ripped apart by opposing forces.

      Orbital Period: 31.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 5492 km
      Day Length: 69.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 17.11 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -134 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>31</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Shiva</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A small, unmanned flyby probe provides the only available data for this tiny planet. It is composed almost completely of ice, with a trace atmosphere of krypton.

      Planetary maps indicate mass concentrations of carbon under intense pressure at the core of the planet. Normandy's more detailed survey suggests the core may solidify into something akin to diamond. The difficulty of extracting it, however, will likely deter any mining interest in the planet.

      Orbital Period: 82.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 3198 km
      Day Length: 32.5 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.03 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -237 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>

    <IsColdOnly>true</IsColdOnly>



  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>32</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Charybdis</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Though it is one of the oldest entries in the star charts, Charybdis has not yet been fully mapped. An immensely powerful magnetic field disrupts known ship design electronics, preventing most ships from getting too close to the planet.

      Due to this magnetic field, metallic particles in the range of the magnetic field form an even distribution around the planet, which significantly diminishes the usefulness of long range visual surveys of the planet’s surface.

      In spite of these obstacles, the Salarian Special Tactics Group conducted long range surveys over a period of two decades. Results from these surveys showed unknown life forms flying around on the planet, as well as near constant lightning strikes.

      The Salarians named this species "Ceph", and while they are not yet space-faring, it is expected they will pose significant risk to galactic civilization once capable.

      Orbital Period: 94.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 4439 km
      Day Length: 46.9 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.88 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 127 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.85 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>33</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Panchaea</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Panchaea is a small planet most notable for housing Sarif Industries’ main research outpost.  Its two moons, Hengsha and Belltower, are home to the original LIMB Clinics. These bioengineering facilities pioneered the first cybernetic augmentations available on the open market. Most of their products have since been eclipsed by asari equivalents. However, Sarif is still the main producer of Neuropozyne, an immunosuppressive drug that prevents augmentation rejection.

      Sarif has been heavily criticized by the Sirta Foundation in recent years, most notably for artificially reducing the supply of Neuropozyne.

      Orbital Period: 1.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 4384 km
      Day Length: 1.4 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.2 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 675 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.44 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>34</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Gol Acheron</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Gol Acheron is a modestly-sized terrestrial planet. The native inhabitants are primitive and most live in small villages along the coast. Anthropologists describe a culture passed down from an ancient race known only as the Precursors. The settlements are guided by four sages. Most of the planet’s economy and industry is based on the collection of an energy source simply known as "eco".

      Orbital Period: 25.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 3675 km
      Day Length: 57.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.37 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 161 Celsius
      Surface gravity: 0.39 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>35</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Belias</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Belias is a blisteringly hot terrestrial planet with an iron-rich, rusty red surface. Its huge ranges of volcanoes are in a state of constant eruption and the atmosphere is choked with a thick cloud of ash.

      The Raithwall, a manned survey ship, met its end on Belias before it could finish mapping the system. The remnants of the ship have long been lost to the ever-shifting magma flow.

      Orbital Period: 3.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 6914 km
      Day Length: 33.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.48 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 497 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>36</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Dantooine</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Dantooine is a relatively unremarkable planet covered mainly in flat grasslands. The "capital" is nothing more than a scattered collection of small farms and the enclave of a reclusive monastic sect.

      Orbital Period: 239.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 78204 km
      Day Length: 10.0 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>37</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>Placeholder - some asteroids have null descriptions. Mgamerz, please fix to ensure the Bio2DA Cell is not null in the description column and ensure all asteroids have a enabled function index for opening</PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>38</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Xen</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Xen has a thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and ethane, with surface temperatures hovering well below freezing. A massive hole has been blown into the side of the planet. A data dump from online backups of planetary development mark the site as the original location of Black Mesa Research Facility. The files make reference to an emergency event called a "resonance cascade", but scientists brought in to study this event have still not worked out exactly what this means.

      Rival research facility Aperture Laboratories is on record with the simple statement "Good riddance. What a joke."

      Orbital Period: 21.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 5447 km
      Day Length: 37.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.58 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -35 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.86 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>39</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Monokuma</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Monokuma is a terrestrial world with traces of several toxic gases in the atmosphere. It is tidally locked to its star, resulting in extreme cold temperatures on the permanently dark side of the planet. The light side is covered in what appears to be large salt flats, giving it an almost reflective appearance.

      Monokuma has a noticeable rift on the dark side of its upper quadrant. While the origins of the rift are still unknown, geological studies indicate that its steep reddish cliffs likely contain large amounts of precious metal. A small mining outpost was established on the rift’s outcropping, aptly named ‘Hope’s Peak’.

      Orbital Period: 2.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 1410 km
      Day Length 2.8 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 82 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.17 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>40</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nearrum</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Nearrum is a terrestrial world with a thin atmosphere of methane and argon. Its surface is mainly composed of basaltic rock. Its most prominent feature is the Farrum Rift, a long volcanic divergence zone that stretches across half of the northern hemisphere. The cliff surfaces are covered in massive circular fissures that appear artificially created, but their size makes this unlikely.

      Orbital Period: 6.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 6779 km
      Day Length: 31.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.67 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 58 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.82 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>41</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nirn</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Nirn is an icy terrestrial planet with a thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and krypton. The planet’s mantle is hollow in most places and its surface is marred with holes large enough to see from space.

      Nirn’s underground cave systems support a surprisingly large variety of algaes and planktons, but the most notable is a small, weed-like root. This pale-green species gives off a faint glow that provides light enough for other fauna to grow. A red variety of the same root does not glow, but instead emits a faint, high-pitched chiming noise. The mechanism of the sound is still unknown, as the sample canister obtained by the original scientific exploration was noted on the manifest as ‘lost in accidental airlock cycling sequence’.

      Orbital Period: 35.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 3691 km
      Day Length: 61.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.27 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -84 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.28 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>42</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Anor Londo</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Anor Londo is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant with a sodium atmosphere and one moon, Artorias.

      A striking formation of mineral spires is visible in the upper hemisphere. These spires catch the light during their brief time on the light side of the planet, taking on the appearance of a kindled bonfire.

      Orbital Period: 85.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 34,914 km
      Day Length: 11.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>43</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>Asteroid belt description</PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>44</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Metallic Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A metal-rich asteroid. There are multiple abandoned mining ships on the surface, with one of them fractured open to the vacuum of space.

      Radius: 94 km
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>45</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>true</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>MSV Toronto</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      The Toronto is a Kowloon-class modular conveyor of human design, configured for mixed freight and passenger hauling. There is a large "No. 1" and what appears to be a maple leaf painted in blue on the side, possibly a reference to the city after which the conveyor was named. It is currently broadcasting garbled, vaguely insulting transmissions.

      Registry: Private Owner, Citadel Station
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>46</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Wander</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Wander is a mostly oceanic planet with a few long, snaky islands. The largest of these is ringed by an insurmountable mountain range. Massive stone giants dot the landscape, sixteen in all, and appear to be vaguely animal in design. Their purpose is impossible to discern. A large stone bridge and a crumbling shrine indicate that this island must have been populated at one point, but no other traces of the former inhabitants remain.

      Orbital Distance: 5.6 AU
      Orbital Period: 3.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 42,418 km
      Day Length: 9.1 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>47</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Gaul</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Gaul is a small, verdant terrestrial world covered almost completely in forests and highlands. Its thin atmosphere is mostly made up of nitrogen with traces of oxygen. The conditions are not suitable for long-term human habitation. However, ambitious explorers can manage with simple, inexpensive survival gear.

      The Alliance Defense Data Network has records of several skirmishes over the planet. The most notable, known as the Siege of Alesia, saw the native inhabitants of the planet subjugated by ExoGeni militia forces.

      Orbital Distance: 69.9 AU
      Orbital Period: 102.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 4227 km
      Day Length: 102.0 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.36 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 1176 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.38 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>48</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Installation 05</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Installation 05 is unique in that the name does not refer to the planet, but to the mechanical ring, or "halo" that encircles it. Several expeditions have attempted to discover its origins and purpose, but all except one disappeared without a trace.

      A black box recovered from pieces of the Amber’s wreckage contains a garbled, audio-only recording of Commander Keyes repeating the word "Gravemind".

      Orbital Period: 302.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 3742 km
      Day Length: 30.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.23 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 848 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.27
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>49</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>50</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Rocky Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      This large asteroid has several smaller bodies orbiting it.
      Radius: 336 km
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>51</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>52</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Orb Ibanna</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Orb Ibanna is technically a terrestrial world, however nearly all of the population lives in the mid atmosphere above the cloud layer that surrounds the planet. With cities built atop towers that rise through the heavens, Orb Ibanna is a planet for the rich and elite of the galaxy.

      A popular gambling attraction on the planet is a dangerous race track, named Abyss, that connects between towers through tubes and race tracks. Racers use carts dragged behind large turbine engines at high speeds, which provide displays of spectacular reaction time, or more commonly, explosive and guaranteed death.

      Orbital Distance: 3.7 AU
      Orbital Period: 1.02 Earth Years
      Radius: 8000 km
      Day Length: 31 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.76 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 11 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>53</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Zavalater</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      An enigmatic terrestrial planet, Zavalater has a atmosphere of nitrogen and argon. It is blisteringly cold and a faint whitish haze can be seen rippling across its blue surface.

      Three times in the last century, ships stopping to discharge at nearby planets have reported geometric patterns of lights on the dark side of Zavalater. Attempts at closer investigation could not be made, as an asteroid belt of whitish fragments surrounded the planet, and ship transponders were overridden with static laced references to ‘the Traveler’.

      Orbital Distance: 2.0 AU
      Orbital Period: 2.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 5535 km
      Day Length: 53.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.5 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 166 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>54</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Xenon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Xenon features two large mountain ranges that form a cross near the equator of the planet, creating a large X that that is visible from space. The mountain ranges are dotted with green fluorescent compounds, which allow them to be seen from space even on the dark side of the planet.

      Expeditions from various other planets often touch down on the surface, allowing galactic tourists to collect the fluorescent rocks as keepsakes.

      Orbital Period: 36.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 2236 km
      Day Length: 42.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -117 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.19 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>55</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Atoli</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Atoli is small and pastoral with a lightly oxygenated atmosphere. The surface remains largely untouched. The equator is ringed with mesas, atop which a massive and ancient wall stands. The asari call the wall Morrigu Barrow, named for the "great gate of heaven" often mentioned in their ancient legends. Along the length of the wall, unusual energy spores can be seen idly drifting through the air over the vast waterfalls that pour down from the mesas.

      Despite several attempts to send colony ships to the planet, the asari consider it a holy site and staunchly oppose any development efforts. Morrigu Barrow is nevertheless a popular destination for tourists of all kinds due to its rare beauty and unspoiled nature.

      Orbital Distance: 20.2 AU
      Orbital Period:2.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 11129 km
      Day Length: 23.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 12 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>56</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Charn</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Charn is a terrestrial planet in the throes of destruction. It orbits a red giant in the end stages of its life. The surface is cold and nearly dark. Great chasms cut through the land, their rivers long dried up. Scans show the sprawling ruins of cities built on a scale much larger than any of the galaxy’s currently known races.

      An Alliance probe passing through the system noted signs of geth activity. Ships are advised to avoid the system.

      Orbital Distance: 51.8 AU
      Orbital Period: 286.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 42,211 km
      Day Length: 12.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>

    <IsColdOnly>true</IsColdOnly>



  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>57</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>58</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Morganna</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Morganna is a massive whitish gas giant with eight moons. Originally named Epitaphs 1 through 8, the moons gained their more well-known names when quarian author Wielant circulated a poem called "Epitaph of Twilight" on the extranet. The poem, inspired by her Pilgrimage through the system, reimagined the moons as characters. Though the names were never officially changed, the poem gained widespread acclaim and most now refer to the moons as Skeith, Innis, Magus, Fidchell, Gorre, Macha, Tarvos, and Corbenik.

      Morganna’s gravitational pull has attracted Cubia, a ninth moon, into its orbit in recent years. Studies have revealed an unstable core, and Morganna’s pulsing gravitational waves will likely cause the new moon to shatter within the next decade.

      Orbital Period: 1.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 542489 km
      Day Length: 41.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 3.84 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 89 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 8.86 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>59</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Valinor</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Valinor and its moon Melkor were spared only a cursory probe on initial exploration of the system, which reported a temperate planet with a moderate supply of light minerals. Alliance colonial surveyors two years later discovered that Melkor had succumbed to orbital decay and crashed into the surface of Valinor.

      Once a promising colony planet, Valinor is now scarred by a massive blast crater. Tsunamis stirred up by violent tectonic shifts have covered most of the surface in filthy ocean, and pieces of the shattered moon have rendered the remaining landmass completely unlivable.

      Orbital Period: 0.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 2147 km
      Day Length: 59.9 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.27 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 50 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.25 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>60</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Firenze</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Firenze is a planet so small that many debate whether it should be reclassified as a moon. Its moderately high gravity, sandy surface, and tolerable extremes of temperature make it an ideal location for military training. The salarians maintain an official base of operations on the planet and on the two space stations in orbit around it.

      Despite the base’s status as an intake for rookie soldiers, rumors speculate that it may actually be a front to conceal the operations of a notoriously secretive STG cell known as the Assassins.

      Orbital Period: 7.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 22759 km
      Day Length: 13.7 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>61</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Bray</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Bray is a massive red planet with an unusually smooth surface. Sonar scans indicate the presence of a nearly hollow core. Ruined ships of failed expeditions still remain floating in low orbit, some of bearing the signs of an EMP attack, others crushed by unknown forces.

      A privately-funded scan of the planet from far above the atmosphere revealed a lattice of structures just beneath the surface, most notably a large pyramid at the center of the core. Despite several conspiracies arguing that the planet was created by a sentient ‘brain’, no other useful information has been discovered.

      Orbital Period: 20.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 74,221 km
      Day Length: 17.3 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>62</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Aen Elle</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Aen Elle is a planet steeped in legend, described in many ancient texts as a place of sublime beauty and advanced knowledge. Guided by these stories, an expedition of combined Council races was sent to track down Aen Elle’s whereabouts. The planet itself was eventually discovered in its accurate location. However, the intervening years had served to all but destroy the fabled paradise.

      Battered by a confluence with Eredin, a roving "ghost" planet, the planet is now overrun with virulent disease and grotesque creatures. Great swathes of the surface are encased in ice and the remaining atmosphere is heavy with frost. The skeletal ruins of once-graceful towers are the only remnant of its prior glory.

      Orbital Period: 37.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 10,314 km
      Day Length: 36.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.0 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -67 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>

    <IsColdOnly>true</IsColdOnly>



  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>63</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nimona</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Nimona is a mid-sized terrestrial planet. Its characteristic deep pink color come from manganese-rich soil. The atmosphere consists mostly of chlorine, often condensing into bright green clouds.

      The planet is often nicknamed "the shapeshifter" due to the ever-changing patterns of the cloud formations. Ships passing through the system will often capture images and upload them to a popular extranet gallery. The most well-known of these images shows a cloud formation that appears much like a dragon breathing fire

      Orbital Period: 90.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 3686 km
      Day Length: 48.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.2 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -202 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.22 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>64</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Virmire</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Mandalore</PlanetName2>
    <MapBaseNames>
      <MapBaseName>MapJUG</MapBaseName>
    </MapBaseNames>
    <PlanetDescription>
      %PLANETNAME% is a lush frontier world, covered in veshok forest, oceans, and rolling grasslands. Unique to the planet and its moon Concordia is beskar ore, a nearly indestructible material akin to iron.

      The warrior tradition of the Taung clans has been passed down through the ages and the unscrupulous denizens of the nearby Terminus Systems have learned to leave the planet well enough alone.

      Capital: Keldabe

      Orbital Period: 1.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 6440 km
      Day Length: 19 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.9 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 32 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.06 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>65</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Jafar</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Jafar is a large, sulfurous gas giant with dark clouds of ash circling its atmosphere. Two reddish moons sit high in its orbit. The gravitational pull exerted by Jafar and its moons is slowly pulling Sultan, a small white dwarf star, out of position. Research suggests that the star’s collapse into a black hole could happen within the next quarter-million years.

      Orbital Period: 1.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 63,169 km
      Day Length: 1.3 Earth Years
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>66</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Olkarion</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Olkarion is a terrestrial planet banded by a ring of mountains, casting the lower hemisphere into perpetual shadow. Protected from the heat of the sun, a vast forest of a tree species unique to the planet is able to flourish. The native Olkari were said to have almost magical abilities to shape the wood into various advanced forms. However, perhaps lured by these very rumors of super-technology, a turian expeditionary fleet was dispatched to the planet and the Olkari were wiped out shortly after. Unfortunately, whatever secrets they may have possessed died with them and the turians were unable to reproduce their success. The forest still stands, but is slowly dying off without the Olkari to tend it.

      Orbital Period: 1.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 7318 km
      Day Length: 28.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.6 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 32 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.4 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>67</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Charlette II</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Charlette II is a gas giant, containing trace amounts of oxygen. It appears that there used to be significantly more oxygen, indicating that may have once a cataclysmic event that removed the oxygen from the atmosphere. It has been theorized that a massive fire that engulfed the planet consumed the majority of the planet’s oxygen.

      Orbital Period: 47.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 32,191 km
      Day Length: 13.4 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>68</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Telos IV</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      The planet Telos IV was once a world of natural beauty and home to a thriving ecosystem. Decades ago, civil war between two opposing political forces lead to planetary bombardment, destroying significant parts of the ecosystem. A restoration project is underway to restore the planet to its former glory, with the planet sectioned off into chunks using Mass Effect fields.

      A space station orbits over the 45 degree northern latitude of the planet, which is used as a staging area and monitoring station for the restoration efforts. The majority of the population of Telos IV lives aboard this space station.

      Orbital Period: 6.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 4075 km
      Day Length: 24.9 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.6 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 5 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.3 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>69</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>true</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Feros</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Nirvash</PlanetName2>
    <PlanetDescription>
      %PLANETNAME% is a small, temperate planet notable for the vast reef-like growths forming the bulk of its landmass. The atmosphere is laced with trapar, a particulate matter linked to the biological activities of these growths. There are indications that %PLANETNAME% may have been mostly oceanic in the past and that the so-called "Scub Coral" is a relatively new arrival, despite covering the vast majority of the planet’s surface. The ExoGeni Corporation founded a small colony to explore this unusual phenomena.

      %PLANETNAME% has two large moons, Eureka and Sakuya.

      Colony Founded: 2178
      Population: 300
      Capital: ExoGeni Building

      Orbital Period: 3.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 8366 km
      Day Length: 30.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 5.44 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 10 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>70</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Sylux</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Sylux is a mostly barren planet that is difficult to scan or explore due to intense lightning storms covering the planet. The sole planetary output, Delano, is a popular hub for bounty hunters due to the difficulty of ship tracking.

      Orbital Period: 1.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 9547 km
      Day Length: 32.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 94.51 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 343 Celsius
      Surface Gravity 1.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>71</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ravka</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Ravka is a cold and intemperate planet that nonetheless has the ability to support life. Os Alta, the capital, is home to the bulk of the population. Known as Suli and led by the Lantsov royal family, the city is protected by an elite legion of biotically superior asari known as Grisha.For years they have held off the incursions of the Shu Han in the south and the Fjerdans in the north. The planet’s climate and remote location ensure very few external visitors, but in recent times, having a winter vacation home in Os Alta has become a status symbol among prominent asari.

      Orbital Period: 46.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 55,721 km
      Day Length: 14.6 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>

    <IsColdOnly>true</IsColdOnly>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>72</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Arche Koeln</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Arche Koeln is covered mostly by cold tundra and has no notable resources. The atmosphere is thick with metallic particles and various gases, giving the planet incredibly vibrant skies at sunrise and sunset. The remains of a Prothean temple are still relatively intact on the surface, surrounded by waterfalls and an ingenious aqueduct system. Though the temple has long been looted of anything historically significant, it is still a popular destination for photographers and anthropologists.

      Orbital Period: 9.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 7271 km
      Day Length: 13.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.91 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 7 Celsius
      Surface Gravity 3.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>73</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Briona Gwydion</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Briona Gwydion is a small, rocky terrestrial planet. A massive range of mountains bisects the equator and stretches from pole to pole. Early survey teams dubbed it Dragonbein, after the famous sun dragon from salarian mythology, due to its bony, spine-like appearance. Its official name was later changed to the Keel Mountains to honor Captain Keel of the survey ship Sheraton, which was lost shortly after transmitting the results of its initial discovery.

      Orbital Period: 112.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 66,341 km
      Day Length: 18.6 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>74</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Indieglut Lugh</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Indieglut Lugh is a pastoral planet with a dry atmosphere and nearly unspoiled surface. A network of cave rivers runs beneath the surface, home to a unique species of bioluminescent white trees that thrive in the slightly acidic water.

      The hanar established a small, experimental colony of drell on the planet a few years after the initial exodus from Rakhana. The settlement thrived until a series of earthquakes rocked the planet, collapsing many of the underground tunnels and causing uncontrollable geysers to erupt from the surface. The resultant flooding wiped out most of the settlers and doomed the rest to a slow death by Kepral’s Syndrome.

      Orbital Distance: 12.6 AU
      Orbital Period: 34.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 8864 km
      Day Length: 35.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 2.1 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 32 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>75</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Sif Berg</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      The proximity of Sif Berg’s star heats the planet to unbearable levels. Composed mostly of molten rock, the magma flow gives the surface an eerie, undulating appearance that can be seen from space with the naked eye. The rock is rich in several valuable materials, notably gold, but the challenge of extraction is a problem that has yet to be solved by any interested parties.

      Orbital Period: 0.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 7702 km
      Day Length: 67.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.18 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 523 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.3 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>76</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ran Hati</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Ran Hati is a small planet completely covered in boreal forest. Several biological expeditions have attempted to catalogue the numerous fauna that inhabit the surface, but most have ended in failure. The few that returned brought back only scant data implying the presence of monsters, but nothing viable for research. In scientific circles, Ran Hati is more commonly known as the “Forest of Pain”. Attempts to study the planet are now limited to high-atmosphere scans from an ExoGeni research ship stationed in perpetual orbit.

      Orbital Period: 9.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 3537 km
      Day Length: 64.9 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.37 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 18 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.39 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>77</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ramuh</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Ramuh is a hydrogen-helium gas giant. Charged ions in the sulfuric atmosphere have created billowing, cloudy storm fronts. Lightning can be seen flickering almost constantly across the dark side of the planet.

      The constellation Olduum, with its noticeably purple-hued stars, is visible even through the heavy cloud cover.

      Orbital Period: 113.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 52,290 km
      Day Length: 17.2 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>78</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ilos</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Valyria</PlanetName2>
    <MapBaseNames>
      <MapBaseName>MapLOS</MapBaseName>
    </MapBaseNames>
    <PlanetDescription>
      %PLANETNAME% was once a verdant world dotted with towering cities, home to a sect of Protheans known as the Freehold. However, all other history has been lost to the Doom of %PLANETNAME%. This massive eruption of volcanoes clouded the atmosphere with ash and turned the oceans to acid. The surface fractured into thousands of small, unstable islands. The cities collapsed into ruin and most of the written history of the planet was lost, along with their advances in science and technology.

      Some fragmentary records of the Doom survive in Prothean beacons, but study of the planet itself has yielded nothing of use.

      Orbital Period: 261 Earth Days
      Radius: 8607 km
      Day Length: 54.5 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 11.26 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 38 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>79</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Megin Fi</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Megin Fi is a mid-sized gas giant with a pressure-cooker atmosphere composed mostly of chlorine. Its boiling cloud cover glows an eerie green from space.

      The wreckage of the aerostat colony Mag Mell still floats above its surface. The structure’s internal mass effect generators have long since failed and the city is now inverted. The upside-down towers and the ring cloud of rubble surrounding it are a popular setting for horror stories. They are also an excellent hiding place for small ships, and smugglers often make use of the area’s sensor distortion for illicit drops.

      Orbital Period: 0.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 6172 km
      Day Length: 53.5 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 84.30 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 510 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>80</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Coite-Bodher</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Coite-Bodher is a relatively small terrestrial planet with a desolate surface and recurrent earthquakes. Historical evidence indicates that massive fallout from a battle between the turians and batarians destroyed the once-lush planet. However, the cause of the battle has been systemically purged from all accessible records and is still unknown.

      Orbital Period: 33.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 30,488 km
      Day Length: 12.2 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>81</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Newark</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Newark is a small, uninhabited planet that has warded off colonization due to its elliptical orbit of the star. Surface scans indicate a multiple small encampments that have been recently abandoned by small groups of various species that descended on the planet.

      Several crashed ships litter a canyon along the equator that was recently flooded due to the thawing of the equator’s glaciers.

      Orbital Period: 1.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 4910 km
      Day Length: 27.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.17 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 15 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.31 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>82</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Predasis</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A world that could once be described as paradise, Predasis is a world currently held by the Ruhar clan of Krogan. It is currently under siege by the Kristang Coalition of Salarians after capture of one of their diplomats, becoming involved in this escalating conflict is not advised.

      Weakly encrypted signals from the Krogan indicate there is a currently unknown species on the planet. This may be the reason for the Salarian presence in orbit.

      Orbital Period: 1.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 4,047 km
      Day Length: 26 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.05 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 27 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.83 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>83</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Decadia</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Decadia is a world devoid of intelligent life due to a nuclear war that took place 113 years ago. The last haven for the dominant species resided upon a scientific space colony that was in orbit at the time of global thermonuclear war.

      An investigation of the station revealed that the final members of the space colony population died less than two months before discovery by the Salarians.

      Orbital Period: 13.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 31,266 km
      Day Length: 21.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>84</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mobius</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A world once rich with abundant life, Mobius is now a lifeless planet. Multiple world domination attempts culminated in a display of power that resulted in the destruction of one of the planet’s moons.

      Parts of the moon fell into the planet’s orbit, and the impact destroyed the majority of the planet’s breathable atmosphere, ultimately killing off the ability to sustain life. The weapon used to destroy the planet remains abandoned in orbit, ironically named Space Colony Ark.

      Orbital Period: 6.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 9647 km
      Day Length: 44.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.22 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -108 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>85</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Wald Uberlisterin</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A small, out-of-the-way terrestrial planet, Wald Uberlisterin is nonetheless notable for a castle-like rock formation on the northern pole. This “castle” has become topic of hot contention between anthropologist and geologists, with one side stating the formation is the remnant of an unknown civilization and the other side insisting it is merely the result of tectonic activity.

      Hoshichiri Heavy Industries, owners of rights to surface mining on the planet, have elected to leave the formation untouched for now, undoubtedly hoping to extort large sums of money in exchange for maintaining its protected status.

      Orbital Period: 15.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 4645 km
      Day Length: 62.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.18 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -169 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.5 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>86</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Cuchulainn</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Cuchulainn’s atmosphere consists of massive sulphur dioxide clouds, which flood the surface with acid rain. The Garamsythe Ocean, which covers most of the planet, rises an average of five millimeters per year. A brief Alliance survey suggests that the acidity of the water may eventually break down the terrestrial surface altogether.

      The planet glows a sickly green color when viewed from space, due to traces of ionized nitrogen in the upper atmosphere.

      Orbital Period: 5 Earth Years
      Radius: 5935 km
      Day Length: 53.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.91 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 94 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.94 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>87</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Caerleon Medb</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Caerleon Medb is a small gas giant. While the planet itself contains large amounts of extractable helium-3, it is largely overlooked by mining companies in favor of its eight moons. Each moon contains vast quantities of separate materials, and the rights to mine them are continuously in contention. Sonax Industries currently holds the majority with five moons. Altai Mineral Works, notable for their success in eezo-refinery, has also established an orbital presence at Caerleon Medb.

      Orbital Period: 0.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 25,957 km
      Day Length: 18.1 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>88</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Berk</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Berk is a small, mostly barren terrestrial world. A thin band of habitable terrain stretches along the coast of its massive ocean. A large island rises from the middle of the ocean and emits a plume of smoke that is visible from space.

      The planet is incapable of supporting plant life due to the sulfuric atmosphere and weak sun. Each of the several varieties of native fauna are well-adapted, however. Possessing scales, wings, and claws, they are well-adapted to living in the rocky outcroppings near the sea.

      Orbital Period: 1.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 2843 km
      Day Length: 34.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 18 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.28 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>89</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Narshe</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Narshe is a snow-covered planet with a surface composed mostly of coal. Human mining teams stripped much of the resource away, but as time went on and eezo became more common, the planet was largely abandoned.

      Recently, however, a vein of frozen magicite was discovered beneath the surface. The unknown conglomerate with controlling shares in the Esper Mine has declined to comment on their plans for this unexpected find.

      Orbital Period: 35.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 3718 km
      Day Length: 39.5 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -96 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.39 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>90</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Midgar</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Midgar is a heavily industrialized planet. Home to a powerful energy source simply known as “mako”, the surface is covered by Shinra Company’s massive harvesting installations. The Cetra, original inhabitants of the planet, opposed the aggressive draining of the planet’s resources. They have been largely forced offworld or into hiding.

      With the dominance of eezo, however, mako has been mostly relegated to smaller applications. New research also suggests that long-term exposure may be irreversibly toxic to most species.

      Orbital Period: 123.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 7304 km
      Day Length: 57.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.42 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -118 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.99 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>91</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Natina</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Natina is a barren, volcanic terrestrial world with an atmosphere choked in soot. The planet’s incredibly strong gravity and atmospheric pressure causes the magma eruptions to condense and harden almost immediately. The resulting surface is deep black and ash-laden winds have scoured it to almost uniformly reflective sheen.

      This unique display, along with the frequent volcanic eruptions, makes Natina a popular destination for artists of all kinds. The planet has been affectionately dubbed ‘Yellow’ by many photography fans, alluding to the distinctive cover of the famous Galactic Geographic holozine.

      Orbital Period: 0.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 6865 km
      Day Length: 56.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 5.73 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 37 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 2.78 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>92</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Spira</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Spira is an oceanic world and the bulk of its landmass consists of islands. The remains of seaports along several of the coastlines seem to suggest the planet was inhabited at one time. Sub-surface scanning indicates the presence of several underwater structures.

      Massive tidal waves make any surface landing attempts extremely difficult. A high plateau, dubbed Zanarkand after the first ship to successfully touch down on the planet, offers the only relatively safe staging area for exploration.

      Orbital Period: 2.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 7074 km
      Day Length: 47.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.33 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 35 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>93</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Cleyra</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Cleyra is a large gas giant. Winds generated by the planet’s rapid rotation whip the particulate-choked atmosphere into a perpetual sandstorm. Completely obscured to most sensors, a tight-beam scan of the surface was nonetheless able to detect a crystalline structure near the core.

      Observation ships stationed in high orbit have recorded fragments of chant-like audio emanating from Cleyra’s surface. Linguists studying the recordings were unable to match the sounds to any currently known language.

      Orbital Period: 5.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 3718 km
      Day Length: 1.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.06 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -124 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>94</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Efrafa</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Efrafa is a high-gravity terrestrial planet. Its rolling fields are criss-crossed by large tunnels and trenches. The origin of these warrens is unknown, but they provide a convenient home for several small elcor communities. These are collectively governed by a council of elcor elders known as the Owsla.

      A raiding attack led by a vorcha mercenary known as Woundwort nearly succeeded in wiping out the colony. However, the elcor retreated into the warrens and collapsed the tunnels behind them, burying the vorcha in the rubble. The elcor ballad “Dhinsaa Erazi Ershan”, or “The Heroism of Hazel” honors the leader of the Owsla, whose actions were instrumental in saving the colony.

      Orbital Period: 115.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 4911 km
      Day Length: 30.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.13 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 12 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 10.28 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>95</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>96</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>97</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Zonama Sekot</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      WARNING: Level 1 Toxic Hazard

      A tropical hothouse of a planet, Zonama Sekot is a lush paradise. The myths of the long extinct Ferroans, preserved only in rudimentary holo-form, state that Zonama is possessed of basic sentience, the spirit of which is called Sekot. Several star charts recovered from ruins indicate the planet may have moved through several different solar systems in its lifetime. The surface does bear massive scorch marks near the equator, giving some credence to the idea of a planet capable of space travel, but no current research can suggest how this feat might be accomplished.

      Surface travel is discouraged due to a virulent strain of spore-borne bacteria in the air.

      Orbital Period: 1.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 5693 km
      Day Length: 20.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.16 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 25 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.9G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>98</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Isabela</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Isabela is a large planet tidally locked to a small dwarf star. As a result, temperatures are frigid and much of surface lies in perpetual dark. Massive oceans composed of liquified methane cover more than 90 percent of the planet’s mass.

      Isabela is a haunt for pirates. Its extreme conditions and ever-shifting surface make it easy to lose any pursuers. Many of the planet’s more frequent visitors have modified their spacecraft for oceanic landings, and the methane seas provide a cheap source of energy for those equipped to harvest it.

      Orbital Period: 21.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 9749 km
      Day Length: 45.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.4 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -171 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.5 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>99</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nibel</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Nibel is a small planet mostly covered in withered forest. Survey scans from low atmosphere detected a transmission from an unknown location. When decoded and viewed, the rudimentary images seem to depict a cataclysmic explosion of light. Satellite imaging of the surface reveals a ring-like pattern of destruction. Current scientific theories posit that gravitational pulses from Sein, the system’s star, may have triggered a violent release of stored energy in the planet’s core.

      The planet’s three moons - Ginso, Gumon, and Horu - are similarly barren, though the source of their destruction is not clearly observed.

      Orbital Distance: 11.3 AU
      Orbital Period: 69.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 1183 km
      Day Length: 30.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 22.4 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -130 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.6 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>100</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Themyscira</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Themyscira is a temperate world. Its surface is dotted with large islands. Considered a backwater by most, the planet is a haven for a small colony of raloi. This splinter tribe of warriors, known as the Bana-Mighdall, withdrew to Themyscira in order to preserve their culture away from the influence of the Citadel races. They eschew most modern technology and their society is heavily rooted in polytheistic principles. Though many have become hunters and craftsmen, the majority of the Bana-Mighdall still retain their warrior traditions of old.

      Orbital Period: 111.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 40,394 km
      Day Length: 19.1 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>101</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>102</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Metallic Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A metal-rich asteroid.
      Radius: 91 km
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>103</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Prometheus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A spiked ball floating in space, Prometheus is a world covered in grandiose towers that make reaching the surface a one way trip for any flying aircraft. As the only catalogued planet with this type of geography, it has proven difficult for science teams to determine the origin of what could have caused such a uniform distribution of mass.

      Acidic rain pummels the surface for half of Prometheus’ solar year, wearing away towers over time. New towers appear to crop up every few hundred years without any obvious signs of tectonic activity beneath the surface of the planet.

      The orbit of the planet around the star is an odd elliptical path, leading some to question if something knocked Prometheus out of a circular orbit.

      Orbital Period: 1.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 6,210 km
      Day Length: 32.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.21 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 22 Celsius
      Surface Gravity 1.3 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>104</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Echo II</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A simple planet with a crust mostly made of obsidian, Echo II is a lifeless planet with an almost glass like surface. Near the north pole are the remains of what appear to be a long range monitoring station, built by an unknown species. This base is the only indication that life ever existed on Echo II.

      An investigation into the purpose of the monitoring station yielded few meaningful results; the only salvageable piece of information from the dated technology shows that the station was monitoring a planet in the system that appears to no longer exist.

      Orbital Period: 0.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 6894 km
      Day Length: 58.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.40 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 520 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.3 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>105</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mononoke</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Traces of sodium in the atmosphere give Mononoke its overall dark grey color, but it is otherwise a typical hydrogen-helium gas giant. An abundance of water vapor in the upper atmosphere account for its white clouds.

      A long-range probe recorded footage of a brief phenomena in which the surface of the planet appeared to be covered in long, trailing spores.

      Orbital Period: 57.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 59,729 km
      Day Length: 14.0 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>106</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nullam</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      One of the larger mysteries in the galaxy, Nullam is an uninhabited planet that has been largely unexplored by the spacefaring species of the Milky Way. The surface appears to be mostly made of lava in the southern hemisphere, with a breathable atmosphere in the northern hemisphere that could sustain life, if one was foolish enough to attempt to land.

      Intense, physics defying gravity waves appear to emanating from Nullam, causing certain locations on the planet to have a gravitational shearing effect. When these mysterious gravity waves collide, anything with significant mass at the point of collision are torn apart in multiple directions.

      Orbital Period: 141.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 22,479 km
      Day Length: 10.9 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>107</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Valum</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Distant Valum has seen only a cursory examination by an unmanned probe, with a more in-depth survey scheduled for 2190. It has a trace atmosphere of nitrogen and argon. The initial scan shows a few uninhabited structures in formation similar to common manufacturing assembly yards. With the planet long gone cold, the facilities have degraded into a frozen ghost town.

      Unusual fake gravity waves have been detected beneath the surface of the facility, leading to a hypothesis that this facility was producing gravity altering devices before it was unsafely shut down. The generated waves are able to be detected from tens of millions of kilometers away, leading to the conclusion that the produced devices were weapons grade, or meant to move planet sized objects.

      Orbital Period: 275.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 7623 km
      Day Length: 47.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.04 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -176 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.9 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>108</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription></PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>109</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Vetus Domum</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Vetus Domum is a supposed former home planet of an unknown ancient alien species. The surface is a smooth, curvy landscape covered in ash from at least tens of thousands of years ago. Strong planetary winds carry this ash, whittling down any structures that stand out on the surface.

      Unmanned probes to the surface have shown there to be remains of buildings under the ash that are safe from the harsh wind. No remains of bodies have been detected, indicating the inhabitants may have abandoned the planet before a catastrophic event that made living on the surface uninhabitable. The probes have detected a repeating radio signal emanating from beneath the surface, repeating the word “Prometheus”.

      Orbital Period: 2.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 5729 km
      Day Length: 50.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.8 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -40 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.87 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>110</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Niihama</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Niihama is a heavily industrialized world run entirely by corporations. Genex Chemical, a bioengineering firm, has faced several large-scale uprisings in recent years. With automation rapidly reducing the need for cheap labor, most of the planet’s workforce is unemployed and unable to leave the planet. An extremist faction known as Individual Eleven has claimed responsibility for at least three of the outbreaks.

      Sector 9, a combined-race special ops task force, is working with the planet’s corporate leaders to resolve the situation.

      TRAVEL WARNING: Due to violent social unrest and acts of terrorism, all incoming and outgoing traffic to Niihama is restricted.

      Orbital Period: 1.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 1528 km
      Day Length: 1.0 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 55 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>111</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Valholl</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Valholl is an icy planet perhaps most notable for its status as a sacred burial ground. At the height of their uplifting, krogan warriors who fell in honorable battle were retrieved from the battlefields. Their bodies were prepared and transported to the frozen surface of Valholl to be interred. The genophage has all but wiped out the ancient traditions of feasting and celebrating the lives of the fallen, and the planet is seldom visited. Only the crooked shafts of ceremonial spears plunged into the ground mark the passage of thousands.

      Orbital Period: 18.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 11190 km
      Day Length: 47.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.20 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -136 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>112</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Zeromus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Zeromus is a large hydrogen-helium gas giant. Its massive gravity well has attracted hundreds of moons and asteroids into its orbit. Most are ripped apart by the forces and become part of an ever-growing ring system. Indigo vapor trails make a faint haze in the atmosphere as the planet’s solid copper core slowly collapses under the pressure.

      The planet is commonly called "the Condemner", and not even pirates venture too close. Even out of the gravity well’s range, the sheer amount of space debris can obliterate all but the most strongly-shielded ships.

      Orbital Period: 39.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 72,492 km
      Day Length: 17.7 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>113</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Caelondia</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Caelondia is a fractured collection of land masses held together by the gravitational force of its planetary core. The remains of a surface installation can be seen on the largest of the pieces. Known as the Bastion, the facility was created by the Mancers as a weapon to destroy their sworn enemies, the Ura. Attempts to use the weapon resulted in a catastrophic backfire that blew the planet apart. This event later became known as the Calamity.

      Though the planet itself is uninhabitable, a small number of Ura and Mancers survived the Calamity. Relegated to small outposts on Zia and Zulf, the system’s two moons, these rival factions engage in a never-ending series of skirmishes with each other.

      Orbital Period: 73.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 4926 km
      Day Length: 23.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -193 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>114</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>115</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Cluster</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A collection of small siliceous asteroids, loosely bound together by gravity.
      Radius: 12 km
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>116</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>117</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Therum</PlanetName>
    <PlanetName2>Therum</PlanetName2>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Therum is a distant but rich industrial world claimed by the human Systems Alliance. Its plentiful heavy metals have fueled the recent manufacturing boom on Earth. Core samples rich with the fossils of simple silicon-based organisms indicate Therum was more habitable in the past than it is at present. Perhaps this explains the many Prothean ruins dotting the surface, most of which have been looted by mining corporations.

      Colony Founded: 2167
      Population: 34,000
      Capital: Nova Yekaterinburg

      Orbital Period: 6.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 6724 km
      Day Length: 28.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.68 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 59 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.12 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>118</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Cloudbank</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Cloudbank is a small world almost completely covered by mechanical terraforming. Records salvaged from Goldwalk, the capital city, indicate that this vast disruption of the landscape is due to a rogue robotic force. This force, called the Process, was an ever-evolving system once utilized by the municipal administrators to change the landscape and environment of the city. The architects, in their zeal for ever more perfected technology, lost control when the Process began to develop outside its original limitations and it swiftly consumed the planet.

      Alliance probes of the system show a higher than normal concentration of geth signals. Whether they are somehow tied to the planet’s fate or merely curious bystanders has yet to be determined.

      Orbital Period: 0.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 4238 km
      Day Length: 57.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.27 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 551 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.63 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>119</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Oculon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Oculon is a terrestrial world with a nitrogen-methane atmosphere containing trace amounts of hydrocarbons. Its frigid surface is mainly composed of water ice and hydrocarbon slush.

      Several space stations of salarian design orbit the planet, but closer inspection shows significant damage to several of them. They appear to have been long since abandoned, the cause of the damage unknown.

      Orbital Period: 33.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 4572 km
      Day Length: 45.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.40 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -71 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.4 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>120</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Vermillion</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Vermillion is a terrestrial world, with several regions that could be considered parts of a paradise planet. Parts of the planet are uninhabitable due to lack of an ozone layer protecting them from the system’s star, however the areas that are covered are common vacation destinations for a variety of species.

      Space travel onto the planet is limited to its capital spaceport, Phenac City, in an effort to improve the planet’s appeal as a relaxation destination. Transport to various parts of the planet is done by more rudimentary means, such as by cruise ships.

      Orbital Period: 5.3  Earth Years
      Radius: 6077 km
      Day Length: 21 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.1 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 27 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>121</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Medoh</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A small oxygen-nitrogen gas giant, Medoh has become has been developed as a full-featured testing ground for aerodynamic non-space-faring vehicle design. Constant winds that swirl due to the high rotation rate of the planet provide excellent conditions for testing unpredictable wind patterns on habitable planets. Due to the relatively small size of the planet, combined with the high rate of rotation, it is expected to lose most of its atmosphere within the next 10,000 years.

      The single moon of Medoh, Revali, is uncharted except for a single tower that marks an otherwise unremarkable surface.

      Orbital Period: 470.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 1,350 km
      Day Length: 2.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>122</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>123</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Distress signal</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A distress call is coming from this asteroid, however nothing adorns the surface except for a single large tunnel entrance. The distress call signal is weak and appears to be coming from the asteroid’s interior, repeating a message about ‘Giant alien spiders’.

      This is almost certainly a trap. Risking the Normandy to save these unknown victims from ‘Giant alien spiders’ is certainly not worth the risk.

      Radius: 127 km
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>124</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>125</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Carbonaceous Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A dark, carbon-rich asteroid.
      Radius: 83 km
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>126</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Liara's Dig Site</PlanetName>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>127</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Vah Rudania</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Vah Rudania is a hot, barren terrestrial world. Chiseled into the surface are maze-like patterns, with scans indicating a subterranean tunnel system that can be entered from specific points in the maze. The surface is dotted with these labyrinths, though no surface dwelling life appears to be able to survive the intense heat to make use of it.

      The single moon of Vah Rudania, Daruk, has several large craters on it. The few colonial areas on the moon have a planetary defense system to defend against incoming meteors.

      Radius: 5171 km
      Day Length: 60.5 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.84 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 180 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.87
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>128</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ruta</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Ruta is a water planet, with a very cold terrestrial atmosphere. Volcanic activity under the planetary ocean and water currents keep the majority of the surface from freezing. A haven for marine life, Ruta has many unexplored secrets in it’s depths.

      A colonized moon of Ruta, Mipha, is considered one of the leading pioneers in medical science. The moon’s capital research facility, named Mipha’s Grace, contributed significantly to the development of Medi-Gel, in partnership with the Sirta Foundation.

      Orbital Period: 0.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 10,480 km
      Day Length: 56.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.96 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -60 Celsius
      Surface gravity: 0.98 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>129</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Orokin</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Orokin is a relatively small terrestrial planet. Its inhabitants, ruled by an elite few, became obsessed with researching and exploiting an unknown resource known as the Void. An experiment gone wrong resulted in a generation of Orokin gifted with unnatural and often fatal powers. The research of an Archimedian geneticist was able to devise a method of transferring these Orokin into new bodies, or frames. Records after this point become few and far between due to a massive uprising simply known as The Old War.

      Modern scientists are still uncertain about the exact identity of the Void, but many have pointed out its apparent resemblance to modern biotics. Historians also make note of the Sentient, a race of synthetic beings created by the Orokin and who existed centuries prior to the quarians’ creation of the geth.

      Orbital Period: 0.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 38,482 km
      Day Length: 16.2 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>130</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Vigrid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Vigrid is an errant

      Orbital Period: 1.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 4327 km
      Day Length: 63.9 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.52 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -136 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.46 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>131</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Antirumgon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Antirumgon is a small rock and ice planet, with a trace atmosphere of methane and ethane. The frozen surface is mainly composed of carbon with deposits of calcium.
      Antirumgon has been used as a crude anchorage for Terminus pirates for many years. The shells of temporary dwellings blasted by Alliance frigate patrols dot the surface. But always, the pirates return to ground their ships' drive charges, chip out some water ice, and trade slaves and stories.

      The deeper layers of Antirumgon's interior are semi-liquid slush, due to the presence of methanol. It is thought that bacterium in the deep core create this natural anti-freeze. Some species of Terminus pirate drill through the ice crust to recover this natural alcohol.

      Orbital Period: 4.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 9508 km
      Day Length: 32.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -178 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.90
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>132</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Antibaar</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Antibaar is a cold terrestrial world with an atmosphere of methane and argon.  Its frozen surface is mainly composed of iron with deposits of magnesium. The world has been noted as a possible target for long-term terraforming; if the atmosphere could be increased to the thickness of Earth's, the global average temperature would rise by 10 degree Celcius.

      Antibaar's combination of low temperatures, high speed surface winds, and low visibility make it dangerous to explore on foot.

      Orbital Period: 3.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 6501 km
      Day Length: 54.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.79 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -34 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>133</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Patamalrus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Patamalrus' atmosphere is very similar to Venus in terms of pressure and temperature. Unlike Venus, however, Patamalrus' atmosphere has a significant quantity of oxygen, both free and bound in sulpher dioxides. The surface is largely composed of magnesia with deposits of carbon. It is possible, if unlikely, that simple life may be developing on Patamalrus.

      Computer modeling suggests that the powerful solar winds from the Tereshkova stars will blow off Patamalrus' atmosphere in a few million years, lowering the temperature on the surface to the -70s.

      Orbital Period: 15.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 5831 km
      Day Length: 47.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 90.47 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 451 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.78 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>134</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Hunsalra</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Hunsalra is a small hydrogen-helium gas giant. It has unusually large amounts of nitrogen in the upper atmosphere, which glow purple when ionized by the solar wind. Hunsalra’s convenience as a place to dump drive charge has left its orbit littered with debris "dumped overboard" by visting crews.

      Orbital Period: 46.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 11,496 km
      Day Length: 18.6 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>135</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Thegeuse</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Thegeuse is a terrestrial world with an atmosphere of chlorine and krypton. The surface is mainly composed of silicates with deposits of carbon. Thegeuse has a low mass for its size, and is tidally locked to the star Tereshkova-A. The temperature difference between the sunward "hot pole" and the dark side "cold pole" creates constant gale-force winds across the terminator.

      Orbital Period: 25.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 5130 km
      Day Length: 5.2 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.49 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -141 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.47 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>136</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Solmarlon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Solmarlon is one of Tereshkova's two outer worlds. Significantly removed from the rest of the system, and with unstable elliptical orbits, it is thought they may have formed within 3 AU of the binary stars, and were hurled outward due to the instability of such an orbit.

      Solmarlon is a hydrogen-helium gas giant with significant quantities of sodium in the upper atmosphere, giving it a distinct grey color.

      Orbital Period: 399.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 69,862 km
      Day Length: 14.4 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>137</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mawinor</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Mawinor is the second of Tereshkova's outer worlds. It is essentially a rock of unremarkable ores with some deposits of water ice, but no minerals of value. The frozen surface is composed of silica.

      Like the gas giant Solmarlon, it is thought that Mawinor formed too close to the Tereshkova stars and was thrown outwards by gravitational effects. Computer models suggest it will be ejected from the system in a few hundred thousand years.

      Orbital Period: 662.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 1170 km
      Day Length: 61.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -228 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.08 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>138</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>139</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Carbonaceous Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A dark asteroid of mixed carbonaceous materials.
      Radius: 42 km
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>140</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Solcrum</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      WARNING: Level 1 Heat Hazard

      Solcrum is the largest moon of the gas giant Notanban. It has a trace atmosphere of krypton and xenon. The crust is composed of various metals with deposits of sodium. As with every body in the solar system, the surface is scorching hot and thoroughly irradiated by the blue giant Grissom. Surface excursions without proper protective gear are certain to prove fatal.

      On approach to Notanban, Normandy's passive sensor array intercepted a fragmentary coded transmission from the surface of Solcrum. Attempts to decrypt the message were fruitless; it does not appear to be in any software coding language used by the Citadel races.

      Orbital Distance: 10,367,883 km (from Notanban)
      Orbital Period: 0.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 4534 km
      Day Length: 0.6 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 351 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>141</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Benda</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Benda has a dense atmosphere of sulphur dioxide and chlorine. Though technically classified as a "terrestrial" world, but the surface of the planet has never cooled enough for a crust to form. It is a global sea of molten rock. Like Zaherux, its atmosphere is being blasted away by the solar wind. Once its thick atmosphere is gone, Benda’s surface will be a "mere" 400 degree C.

      Orbital Period: 812.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 6788 km
      Day Length: 41.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 26.35 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 3151 Celsius
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>142</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Zaherux</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Zaherux's nitrogen-argon atmosphere is being blasted away by the solar wind of the blue giant Grissom. Its surface consists of "seas" of loose silica dust, some kilometers deep, which periodically swirl into global sandstorms.

      Many unmanned probes to Zaherux have been lost over the years. Though investigation has attributed all to mechanical failure or computational error, a popular extranet meme insists the entire planet is composed of dormant nanotechnology, created millennia ago by a race even more advanced than the Protheans.

      According to the story, Zaherux's silica dust is actually "disassembler" robots which periodically awaken to defend themselves. Though discounted by every reputable scientist, this theory has been popularized by a series of sensationalistic texts by asari author Delsae Orthysa.

      Orbital Period: 266.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 6729 km
      Day Length: 51.5 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.32 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 959 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.61 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>143</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Notanban</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Notanban is a hydrogen-helium gas giant with traces of ammonia. Molecular nitrogen is present in the highest levels of the atmosphere, giving the planet its odd violet tint.

      The upper levels of Notanban's atmosphere are inhabited by "shoals" of tiny ammonia-based lifeforms, no larger or more complex than the plankton of Earth's oceans. Held aloft by air pressure and wind, these bioluminescent creatures constantly flee from the approach of the terminator. Should they be exposed to the light and heat of Grissom, they die.

      Orbital Period: 990.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 73,314 km
      Day Length: 16.9 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>144</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>145</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Rocky Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      An asteroid composed of mixed metals and silicates.
      Radius: 54 km
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>146</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>147</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Maji</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Maji orbits the Vamshi binary giant stars. Vamshi-A is a blue star of spectral class A4III which burns at half again the temperature of Sol. Vamshi-B is an aging red giant of class M5III, over 220 times the size of Sol.

      Maji has a thin atmosphere of methane and carbon monoxide. The difference in temperature between the hemisphere facing the suns and that facing deep space causes constant wind, stirring the silica and sodium dust of the surface.

      Unsavory characters from the Terminus Systems occasionally use Maji for forms of cruel sport, dumping slaves, hostages, quarreling shipmates, or even (when bored) vicious animals on the surface. One must kill the other before they will be rescued from the lethal radiation of the giant stars.

      Orbital Period: 5.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 5727 km
      Day Length: 55.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.42 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -121 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.85 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>148</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Almos</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Almos is a hydrogen-helium gas giant with traces of sodium darkening its atmosphere.

      Orbital Period: 46.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 60,948 km
      Day Length: 67.1 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>149</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pregel</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Pregel is an enormous terrestrial world with an atmosphere of chlorine and ethane. Its surface is mainly composed of sulphur with deposits of aluminum. No landing has ever been attempted.

      Orbital Period: 17.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 10,510 km
      Day Length: 49.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.0 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -131 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>150</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Casbin</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Casbin is a classic "pre-garden" terrestrial world, with conditions similar to those on Earth millions of years ago. Its hot, humid atmosphere is mainly composed of nitrogen and carbon dioxide. An increasing amount of the surface is covered by simple lichen and algae. Should no unexpected calamity occur, these tiny plants will change the atmosphere to an Earth-like nitrogen-oxygen mix over the next few millennia.

      Due to its potential for future habitability and sapient life, Casbin has been designated a Sanctuary World by the Citadel Council. Landing is prohibited by law, and any disturbance of the fragile young ecosystem will result in harsh fines and imprisonment.

      At present, the planet is passing through the debris trail of a long-period comet.

      Orbital Period: 1.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 7819 km
      Day Length: 44.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.1 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 99 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>151</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pomal</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Pomal is an enormous terrestrial planet, with a very dense atmosphere of carbon dioxide and sodium. The surface is scorching hot, and mainly composed of sodium oxides and deposits of nickel. There is evidence that Pomal was once covered with broad, shallow seas. Should a probe ever be sent to the surface, a check for ancient fossil life might prove valuable.

      Orbital Period: 0.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 9616 km
      Day Length: 47.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 31.59 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 492 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>152</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Matar</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Matar is terrestrial planet with a thick atmosphere composed of nitrogen and krypton. Its frigid surface is mainly composed of sodium oxide with deposits of copper. Because of noxious surface gases, explorers are warned to use extreme caution.

      Matar lacks a magnetic field. This makes it useless for discharging FTL drive cores in orbit. The energetic particles of solar wind from Hong strike the upper atmosphere directly, ionizing the krypton. This gives the planet its distinctive "minty" green-white hue.

      Orbital Period: 29.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 4599 km
      Day Length: 54.5 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 3.72 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -64 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.57 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>153</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Theshaca</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Theshaca is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant. In the past, it was often used as a drive discharge point for pirates raiding human settlements from the Terminus Systems. In 2178 the Alliance set up a network of covert sensing devices on Thesaca's moons. Recordings of pirate FTL exit vectors over the course of six months led the Alliance Navy to eight major pirate anchorages. Since the "Theshaca Raids," no ships from the Terminus have been reported in the Hong system.

      Orbital Period: 84.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 65,976 km
      Day Length: 14.0 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>154</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Cayde-6</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Cayde-6 is a tiny dwarf planet with a trace atmosphere. The surface is mainly composed of water ice trapped beneath a skin of weak ammonia ice. Bioluminescent plankton beneath the surface spread a faint bluish glow through the frozen layers.

      Orbital Period: 238.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 1402 km
      Day Length: 30.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.04 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -211 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>

    <IsColdOnly>true</IsColdOnly>



  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>155</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nodacrux</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Nodacrux is a verdant world, with abundant water, temperate climate, a thick nitrogen-oxygen atmosphere, and a rich ecosystem. It would seem to be perfect for life. The relatively high percentage of oxygen makes humans feel energized and alive, though it has also allowed insect analogues to grow to frightful sizes.

      Unfortunately, Nodacrux is a case of "almost, not quite." Thunderstorms are as common as on Earth, but in Nodacrux’s thicker, oxygen-rich atmosphere, they are deafening and spark constant wildfires. More damning, however, are the large and ubiquitous tufts of pollen that float on the high-pressure air. In humans and other oxygen-breathing species, they cause severe or lethal allergic reactions.

      Orbital Period: 3.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 5988 km
      Day Length: 22.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 2.63 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 23 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.9 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>156</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Clomarthu</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Clomarthu has a reducing atmosphere of methane and nitrogen. The surface is hot, and mainly composed of sodium with deposits of uranium. In terms of size and orbit, Clomarthu is a virtual twin of Earth, but utterly lacks life.

      Orbital Period: 1 Earth Year
      Radius: 6028 km
      Day Length: 18.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.9 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 95 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.9 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>157</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Alko</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      The geological properties of Alko have been scanned from orbit, but little else is known about it. A fairly typical mix outer system terrestrial of rock and ice, Alko has a trace atmosphere of krypton and xenon. Its crust is composed of silicates and water ice with deposits of aluminum. Unregistered starship traffic has been recorded in the vicinity of this planet. Travel is not advised.

      Orbital Period: 28.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 4949 km
      Day Length: 45.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -167 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.5 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>158</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pataiton</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A rather small hydrogen-helium gas giant, Pataiton’s atmosphere contains large quantities of chlorine.

      Orbital Period: 110.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 16,622 km
      Day Length: 18.6 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>159</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A dark asteroid of mixed carbonaceous materials.
      Radius: 42 km
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>160</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Metallic Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A metal-rich asteroid.
      Radius: 139 km
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>161</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>true</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>MSV Khenarthi</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      The Khenarthi is a modular conveyor of unknown design, and looks much like a tent drifting through space. The surface is covered with large, crudely-drawn advertising billboards. Attempting to ping the ship resulted in a return transmission showing an image of a feline biped, who ‘has wares if you have coin’. A secondary transmission, poorly encrypted, makes reference to an illicit substance known only as ‘moon sugar’.

      Registry: Rawl'kha Shipping, Elsweyr
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>162</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Clotanca</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Clotanca is a large but low-density terrestrial world with an atmosphere of nitrogen and carbon monoxide. Its crust is composed of sulphur and unremarkable silicates. Occasional deposits of heavy metals, usually the result of meteor strikes, dot the surface.

      High-speed winds, powered by the hot blue star Caspian, present a constant hazard. Atmospheric entry is hazardous, and EVAs are discouraged.

      Orbital Period: 124.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 7810 km
      Day Length: 19.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.73 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 92 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.78 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>163</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Almarcrux</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Almarcrux has an atmosphere of methane and ethane. Despite its great distance from Caspian, the energetic young star heats the surface almost temperate levels. Thick ground fogs are common at the terminator, where water ice frozen during the long dark side night meets the warm air masses from the day side. The crust is mainly composed of copper with deposits of sodium.

      Almarcrux's abundant water and relatively mild temperature and gravity have placed it on the short list of terraforming candidate worlds. However, there is significant opposition from eco-ethics groups, who assert that Almarcrux's primitive methanotrophic bacteria may be a precursor to a full-fledged native ecology.

      Orbital Period: 584.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 4715 km
      Day Length: 64.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.76 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 31 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.78 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>164</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Farnuri</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Farnuri has a trace atmosphere of carbon dioxide and helium. The surface is mainly composed of silica laced with iron oxides, indicating the world had an oxygenated atmosphere at some time in the past. Given the relative youth of the blue star Caspian and the significant gravity well of Farnuri, this must have occurred with astonishing swiftness, perhaps a result of some cataclysmic event. Further research is required.

      Orbital Period: 352.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 8968 km
      Day Length: 67.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -98 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>165</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Antida</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Antida is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant. Its atmosphere is darkened by traces of sodium. It is one of relatively few planets known with an orbital period of more than a millennium.

      Orbital Period: 1296.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 29,657 km
      Day Length: 12.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>166</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>167</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Chasca</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Chasca is a large but low-density world, fundamentally similar to its inner neighbor Inti. Like Inti, Chasca is tidally-locked to Matano. The same side always faces the sun, resulting in a scorching day side and a frozen night side. In the temperate areas around the terminator, temperatures average around 30 Celcius. Combined with a nitrogen-oxygen atmosphere, this slender band of habitable terrain allows limited colonization by humans.

      Chasca's ring is unique. It appears to be, for lack of a better term, a massive piece of alien "installation art." The rings are made of small pieces of synthetic material, and are almost invisible from space. From the ground, they catch and scatter the light of Matano in picturesque ways. It is not known who created the ring, or when.

      Chasca is very early development, with little more than a few pioneer teams scattered across the surface. Information is being collated about native hazards and ecology, while a massive colonist recruiting drive is gearing up back on Earth.

      Colony Founded: 2183
      Population: 150

      Orbital Period: 1.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 8059 km
      Day Length: 1.3 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.86 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 67 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>168</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Inti</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Inti is a terrestrial planet with an atmosphere composed of ammonia and helium. Its surface is mainly composed of sodium oxide with deposits of magnesium. Its density is rather low, leaving the planet tide-locked to Matano.

      Inti is an unremarkable world, drawing little more than a cursory scan for surface pirate anchorages when Alliance patrols enter the system.

      Orbital Period: 0.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 9032 km
      Day Length: 0.6 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.56 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 157 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.99 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>169</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Hashmal</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A craggy world of basaltic mountains, Hashmal is wracked by constant geologic activity. Tectonic plates are constantly piling up new mountains or collapsing old ones. The planet’s surface is covered in massive rifts.

      Orbital scans show what appears to be a tower standing on one of the tallest peaks, dubbed the "Pharos of Ridorana" for its luminous surface. Much like the lighthouses of ancient Earth, the foot is littered with the remains of expeditionary ships that ventured too near and crashed against the rocks. The tower itself, however, remains untouched by the chaos.

      Orbital Period: 29.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 6843 km
      Day Length: 56.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.2 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -116 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>170</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Illapa</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Illapa is a hydrogen-helium gas giant with an unusual ruby color caused by contaminants in the atmosphere. The world has over 120 moons, one of the highest totals of all known systems.

      Once full development of Chasca colony begins, a helium-3 refining infrastructure will be developed in the Illapa system, concentrated on the large ice moon of Coniraya.

      Orbital Period: 74.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 72,820 km
      Day Length: 15.7 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>171</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Supay</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Supay has the composition of an ice dwarf planet, but is unusually large for such a body. It has a trace atmosphere of krypton and xenon. The frozen surface is dotted with deposits composed of potassium and light metals, brought to the surface by cryovolcanic processes.

      Supay's icy surface was often used as a source of potable water by passing merchant vessels. Since the Alliance claimed the inner system world of Chasca, satellites placed in orbit automatically bill any vessel landing on the world for the mass of water removed from the surface.

      ExoGeni has had a difficult time keeping these satellites operational; they often meet with "accidents" caused by impact with jettisoned ship debris.

      Orbital Period: 275.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 4317 km
      Day Length: 63.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -216 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.25 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>172</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>173</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Metallic Asteroid </PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A metal-rich asteroid.
      Radius: 47 km
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>174</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>175</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Rocky Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      This asteroid has an unusually sculpted and artistic appearance, with many long, sweeping curves.
      Radius: 34 km
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>176</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Tuntau</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Tuntau is an enormous, low-density terrestrial planet, with a thick atmosphere of methane and helium. Despite being nearly 20 AU from Phoenix, the star’s great heat and the insulating thickness of the atmosphere make the surface surprisingly temperate.

      The crust is mainly composed of sodium and silicon dioxide with deposits of various light metals. While Tuntau is not habitable, the relative pleasantness of the surface conditions make it a popular location for small ships traveling through the Argos Rho cluster to land for drive discharge.

      Orbital Period: 63.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 11,867 km
      Day Length: 69.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 3.12 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 21 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>177</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Patashi</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Patashi is a sun-blasted terrestrial world whose atmosphere was blasted away millennia ago by the star Phoenix. The surface is scorching hot, and mainly composed of iron with deposits of tin.

      Due to its relatively low density, Patashi is tidally locked to Phoenix. Seas of molten light metals cover much of the sunward side.

      Orbital Period: 0.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 7082 km
      Day Length: 0.3 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 546 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.75 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>178</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Sylsalto</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Sylsalto is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant. It has no remarkable features.

      Orbital Period: 36.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 56,621 km
      Day Length: 13.6 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>179</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Vebinok</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Vebinok is a small terrestrial world with a thin atmosphere of krypton and xenon. Its frozen surface is mainly composed of carbonaceous material, water ice, and low-density silicates. Rare but concentrated lodes of light metals have been deposited by asteroid impacts.

      One hemisphere of Vebinok is covered by surface deposits of oxidized copper. Approximately 270 years ago a turian bulk gas transport was attacked by pirates in the Phoenix system. Damaged, it made a rough landing on Vebinok. The heat of the landing melted significant quantities of surface ice, and ruptured shipping containers spilled LOX across the surface. Before this evaporated and escaped Vebinok’s weak gravity, it reacted to cause the widespread rust.

      Orbital Period: 94.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 3379 km
      Day Length: 68.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.27 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -154 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.28 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>180</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>181</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Fragmented Asteroid </PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      This asteroid appears to be a piece of a larger planet that was blasted away by firepower of unimaginable magnitude. Debris litters the area around it. Ships with high-grade sensor packages can pick up a weak, intermittent transmission that one ship log described as ‘millions of voices crying out in terror.’
      Radius: 71 km
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>182</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>183</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Metgos</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      WARNING: Level 2 Heat Hazard

      Metgos is a large terrestrial planet with an atmosphere of carbon dioxide and nitrogen. Its hot surface is mainly composed of nickel with deposits of potassium and heavy metals. It is a mineralogical treasure trove, with concentrated heavy elements constantly being brought to the surface by volcanic activity.

      Metgos is inhospitable and dangerous, and expeditions must be well-prepared to survive any length of time. With its high mass, heat-trapping clouds and constant volcanic venting, Metgos seems well on its way to becoming a Venusian "pressure cooker" world.

      Orbital Period: 2.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 7301 km
      Day Length: 47.2 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 169 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>184</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Varmalus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Varmalus has a thick atmosphere of nitrogen and helium. Its surface is scorching hot, and mainly composed of alumina with deposits of borax. The planet has an extensive network of subterranean caves, formed over the millennia by volcanic processes. In these relatively cool areas, some primitive life has developed.

      Orbital Period: 0.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 9593 km
      Day Length: 19.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.3 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 503 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>185</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Theyar</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Theyar is a large gas giant with traces of chlorine and sodium in its atmosphere. It also has a significant amount of water vapor in the clouds of its upper atmosphere.

      Theyar was struck by an asteroid at least 12 kilometers in diameter within the last hundred years. The superheating caused by the impactor’s atmospheric passage created a large bank of vicious storms along the equatorial band.

      Orbital Period: 12.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 60,774 km
      Day Length: 11.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>186</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Canrum</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Canrum is a small, rocky world with a trace atmosphere of methane and krypton. Its surface is mainly composed of magnesium and silicates with deposits of carbon.

      Canrum was the site of the warlord Shiagur's defeat by turian peacekeeping forces during the Krogan Rebellions. While this band was not especially powerful, Shiagur was a female warlord – and one of the few remaining fertile females, at that. She had, through viciousness and cunning, parlayed her unique value into a position of power. Krogan males competed for the right to join her band and lie with her.

      When Shiagur's death was announced, vengeful male krogan admirers near and far swore blood oaths against the participating turian crews. In the end, several thousand of the turian participants were killed in open combat or through assassination. To this day, many krogan proudly proclaim that they have the "blood of Shiagur."

      Orbital Period: 67.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 5,220 km
      Day Length: 32.5 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.07 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -132 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.55 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>187</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Syba</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Syba is a standard Neptune-type gas giant, the upper cloud decks of its hydrogen-helium atmosphere tinted a dramatic blue by traces of methane.

      Orbital Period: 162.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 45,145 km
      Day Length: 12.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>188</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Unidentified Space Facility</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>This space station appears to have been assembled from used "off the shelf" civilian ship modules of diverse origins. There are no obvious hull markings, and it is not broadcasting any ID signal.</PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>189</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Vectra</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Vectra is a typical hydrogen-helium gas giant with traces of methane and sodium in its atmosphere. The heat of the star Gorgon is slowly blasting away the gas giant's massive atmosphere, which is visible as a long, dim tail that trails behind the planet.

      Orbital Period: 234.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 69,833 km
      Day Length: 234.7 Earth Years
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>190</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Camaron</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Camaron is a terrestrial world with a thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and argon. The surface is scorching hot, and mainly composed of iron with deposits of nickel. Like Wuo, Camaron is tide-locked to the blue giant, forever "looking into the face of the Gorgon."

      Orbital Period: 664.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 5198 km
      Day Length: 664.8 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.23 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 747 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.55 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>191</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Sharblu</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A standard hydrogen-helium gas giant, the methane in Sharblu's atmosphere gives it an azure hue.

      The asari crew who initially surveyed the system (during Earth's 17th century) named Sharblu after a then-popular soprano. The singer was renowned for her unusual skin tone, which was quite similar to that of the planet.

      Orbital Period: 1711.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 43,342 km
      Day Length: 1711.0 Earth Years
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>192</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Slekon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Orbiting at an unbelievable distance of 710 AU (over 66 billion kilometers) from Gorgon, Slekon is a huge gas giant, with an atmosphere tainted by methane and chlorine.

      Orbital Period: 4483.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 77,115 km
      Day Length: 4483.1 Earth Years
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>193</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Wuo</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Wuo is a terrestrial planet only known from scan data picked up by unmanned probes. Though over 76 AU from the blue giant Gorgon, temperatures in Wuo's orbit are still dangerously high. Only ships with very powerful heat radiating systems can venture that deep into the system.

      Fortunately, Wuo is not a terribly interesting world. It has a thin atmosphere of nitrogen and methane, and the scorching surface is mainly composed of alumina with deposits of platinum. The world is tidally locked to Wuo, leaving the sunward side scorched and irradiated wasteland, and the dark side a frigid and ice-crusted.

      Orbital Period: 158.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 6959 km
      Day Length: 158.0 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.44 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 1157 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.66 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>194</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Presrop</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Presrop is the moon of Klendagon. It is a frigid, barren world, with an extremely thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and ethane. The crust contains plentiful deposits of heavy metals. The Alliance has opened bidding for the moon's mineral rights, but exploitation will be complicated by the system's proximity to the "Five Kiloparsec Ring" around the galactic core. The Ring is an area of intense star formation, and too dangerous to safely travel.

      Presrop's landscape is a nightmare of jagged, overlapping ridges and geological shock zones created by some ancient disaster. This has not deterred a generation of illegal "wildcat miners" from attempting to exploit the moon's mineral riches. Unfortunately, many have lost their lives.

      Orbital Distance: 168,500 km (from Klendagon)
      Orbital Period: 10.8 Earth Days
      Radius: 4113 km
      Day Length: 10.8 Earth Days
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.1 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -73 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>195</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Tamahera</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Tamahera has a thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and xenon. The surface is icy, and composed of sodium oxide with deposits of calcium. It contains a few unremarkable metals, but mainly consists of rock. The presence of canyons and flood plains indicates that liquid water once existed, suggesting Tamahera had a thicker insulating atmosphere in the past.

      Orbital Period: 1.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 6302 km
      Day Length: 40.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.34 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -30 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.66
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>196</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Canctra</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A terrestrial world of average size, Canctra's atmosphere is composed of nitrogen and argon. Its frozen surface is mainly composed of tin with deposits of calcium. Aside from some spectacular formations of water-ice at the poles, the planet has little to recommend it.

      Orbital Distance: 14.3 AU
      Orbital Period: 60.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 5471 km
      Day Length: 66.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.83 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -175 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.7 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>197</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Altea</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Altea is a large, terrestrial world and was the seat of King Alfor at the height of his power. A peaceful and learned people, the Alteans had keen interest in science, diplomacy, and technological advancement. Unfortunately, a large-scale scientific experiment in collaboration with the Galra caused unimaginable destruction and their alliance was broken. Zarkon, now styling himself Emperor, betrayed King Alfor and turned his fleets on Altea. The combined firepower of his capital ships devastated the planet.

      Once verdant and thriving, Altea is now devoid of life. Magma storms erupt continuously from the shattered core. The planet is surrounded by a ring system of its own rubble as it slowly breaks into pieces in the aftermath of the destruction. The Alteans and Galra themselves have long since gone extinct.

      Orbital Period: 128.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 68,714 km
      Day Length: 17.5 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>198</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>199</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Damaged Asteroids</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Asteroids in the vicinity bear marks of high heat weaponry impacts. There are clear points on this asteroid that indicate the temperature was high enough to melt sections of the rock, as they are stream away from the center like ribbons before they froze again.

      Radius: 83 km
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>200</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Klendagon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Klendagon is an arid terrestrial, slightly larger than Earth, but with a lower density that reflects its relative lack of heavier elements. The crust is composed of tin and aluminum, with wide deserts of dust-fine sand that are easily stirred by the wind.

      Klendagon's most striking feature is, of course, the Great Rift valley that stretches across the southern hemisphere. What is most fascinating about the Rift is that it does not appear to be natural. The geological record suggests it is the result of a "glancing blow" by a mass accelerator round of unimaginable destructive power. This occurred some thirty-seven million years ago.

      Orbital Period: 2.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 7377 km
      Day Length: 53.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.64 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -53 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>201</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Ontarom</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Though Ontarom's surface is uncomfortably hot, its nitrogen-oxygen atmosphere and abundant, shallow seas make it an ideal candidate for habitation by most known species.

      Unfortunately, the orbit of the moon of Thonal has been slowly decaying since the system coalesced. Its proximity is beginning to have tidal effects, and its dynamo-like revolution through Ontarom's magnetic field is generating increasing powerful electrical storms.

      While some have suggested emplacement of mass effect drives in an attempt to lighten the moon and correct its orbit, the scale of such a project - tens of thousands of drives, costing enough to bankrupt the governments of all the Citadel races - make it a pipe dream. A multi-racial effort is underway to catalogue and preserve the unique genetic diversity of Ontarom's vibrant young biosphere. ExoGeni Corp. and Heyuan Genomics represent the Alliance's share of the effort.

      Orbital Period: 1.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 6443 km
      Day Length: 39.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.79 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 58 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.82 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>202</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Klencory</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Klencory is a rock and ice planet with an atmosphere composed of chlorine and argon. The frozen surface is mainly composed of potassium with deposits of Iron.

      Klencory is famously claimed by the eccentric volus billionaire Kumun Shol. He claims that a vision of a higher being told him to seek on Klencory the "lost crypts of beings of light". These entities were supposedly created at the dawn of time to protect organic life from synthetic "machine devils."

      Shol has been excavating on Klencory's toxic surface for two decades, at great expense. No government has valued the world enough to evict his small army of mercenaries.

      Orbital Period: 20.6 Earth Years
      Radius: 7677 km
      Day Length: 18.3 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.01 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -109 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.82 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>203</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Famfrit</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Famfrit is an ice dwarf world, its surface composed almost entirely of frozen water. Solar winds stir the dark cloud cover into a roiling mass. An unusually large and beautiful ring of ice crystals orbits the planet, the result of an asteroid impact that shattered the surface and threw a great deal of melted water into the atmosphere. The rings will completely decay in a few thousand years. Nevertheless, they remain a popular subject in the art forms of several species.

      Orbital Period: 272.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 3111 km
      Day Length: 23.9 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.00 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -188 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.09 G
    </PlanetDescription>

    <IsColdOnly>true</IsColdOnly>



  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>

  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>204</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Juncro</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Juncro is a hydrogen-helium gas giant with traces of chlorine and sodium in its upper atmosphere. Like Uranus is the Sol system, it is "tipped on its side," its north pole facing the star Newton.

      Orbital Period: 60.0 Earth Years
      Radius: 66,642 km
      Day Length: 16.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>205</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>MSV Fedele</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      The Fedele is a Kowloon class modular conveyor of human design. In addition to the standard cargo bay, the hull has several biological research modules attached.

      Registry: Private Owner, Dr. R. Heart
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>206</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Matol</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Several attempts to chart Matol have been made, but none have been successful. By normal standards a small rock planet, Matol has a dense atmosphere composed of carbon dioxide and argon, with a surprising amount of water vapor. Fogs and rain are common on the barren, lifeless surface.

      Matol is pleasant enough to be considered a terraforming prospect, though its low mass and the high radiation of the energetic blue star Herschel place it fairly far down on the list.
      Orbital Period: 207.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 4077 km
      Day Length: 34.6 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.49 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 33 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.5 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>207</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Clugon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Clugon's hydrogen-helium atmosphere is given a fairly dramatic emerald tint by chlorine and ionized gases. It has nearly 100 moons.

      Orbital Period: 1013.7.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 17,988 km
      Day Length: 19.2 Earth Hour
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>208</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Clobaka</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Clobaka is a moderately sized terrestrial world with a hazy hydrocarbon atmosphere. Its surface is mainly composed of chlorides with deposits of solid and liquid-form hydrocarbons.

      Orbital Period: 2052.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 8198 km
      Day Length: 59.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.81 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 7 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.88 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>209</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>210</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Tungel</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Tungel is a massive terrestrial world, nearly twice the size of Earth, with a dense atmosphere of nitrogen and ethane. Its scorching hot surface is mainly composed of iron, with extensive deposits of heavy metals and radioactives. It is a mineralogical treasure trove, and many corporations are lobbying for mining rights.

      Orbital Period: 85.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 11,539 km
      Day Length: 42.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 2.0 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 242 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.9 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>211</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Rocky Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A metal-rich asteroid.
      Radius: 118 km
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>212</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Altahe</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Altahe is an exceptional form of planet called a Roche World. Put simply, it is one half of a pair of small and unusually dense terrestrial worlds (Altahe and Ontahe) that orbit each other so closely, they effectively share a single atmosphere. This is does not mean that one could fly from one to the other, but both have identical atmospheres, and dust from one often can be found on the other.

      Both worlds share an atmosphere of nitrogen and ethane.  The surface is warm, and mainly composed of silica dust and dark basaltic rocks, with extensive deposits of heavy metals and radioactives. Tidal effects from Ontahe create constant heavy wind.

      Orbital Distance: 0.8 AU
      Orbital Period: 0.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 4404 km
      Day Length: 53.8 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.98 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 36 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.1G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>213</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Farthorl</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A modest terrestrial planet, Farthorl has a thin atmosphere composed of carbon dioxide and chlorine. The crust is mainly composed of sulfur with deposits of nickel. The terrain is extremely rough - a patchwork of craggy, overlapping craters dating back to the formation of the solar system. Farthorl is tidally locked to the star Acheron. The day side has never been fully mapped.

      Orbital Period: 0.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 6506 km
      Day Length: 0.2 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.69 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 239 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>214</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Grosalgen</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      An enigmatic rock and ice planet, Grosalgen has a thin atmosphere of carbon dioxide and ethane. The surface is composed of frozen water and chlorine.

      Orbital Period: 41.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 5198 km
      Day Length: 28.9 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.53 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -175 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.6 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>215</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Imaneya</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Though exceptionally large for a terrestrial world, Imaneya is composed of water ice and with a core of various carbonaceous compounds. It has a density only half that of Earth, and an atmosphere of nitrogen and carbon monoxide. The surface is composed of surprisingly pure water ice, with a high albedo.

      Orbital Distance: 22.2 AU
      Orbital Period: 117.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 11,621 km
      Day Length: 56.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.88 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -185 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.9 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>216</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>217</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Carbonaceous Asteroid</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A dark asteroid of mixed carbonaceous materials. This asteroid shows sign of impacts by weapons fire.
      Radius: 63 km
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>218</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Nepmos</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Nepmos is a resource-rich terrestrial world somewhat larger than Earth, with a dense atmosphere of sulphur dioxide and argon. Nepmos' crust is very thin and unstable, not more than 8 kilometers deep in any location. Subsurface magma flows are a hazard to ground travel, and earthquakes are frequent. While heavy metals and radioactives are plentiful, this geological instability has deterred investment by mining concerns.

      An additional complication is that the Styx Cluster lies uncomfortably close to the "Five Kiloparsec Ring" around the galactic core. The Ring contains a great deal of molecular hydrogen, fueling the majority of the galaxy's star formation. This area is too dangerous to safely travel.

      Orbital Period: 0.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 7593 km
      Day Length: 68.1 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.12 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 68 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 1.2 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>219</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Quaji</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Quaji is a terrestrial planet with an atmosphere of methane and ethane. The surface is composed of silica with deposits of uranium and heavy metals. Clouds of small water ice crystals are common. Quaji's skies are full of fine silica dust. From the surface, the sky has a pronounced salmon hue.

      The cursory initial scans from the Alliance surveyor ship Ibn Battuta showed geometric patterns in the northern hemisphere deserts, visible only in the ultraviolet band. Normandy's sensors see nothing of the kind.

      Orbital Period: 2.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 5160 km
      Day Length: 38.7 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.83 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -7 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>220</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Wermani</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Wermani has only been visited by a single unmanned probe. It is a standard hydrogen-helium gas giant with large formations of water vapor clouds in the upper atmosphere.

      Orbital Period: 9.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 71541 km
      Day Length: 9.2 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>221</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Chofen</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Chofen is an unusually small hydrogen-helium gas giant, with traces of sulphur and hydrocarbons in the atmosphere. The Alliance surveyor ship Ibn Battuta reported inconclusive evidence of hydrocarbon life in the deeper layers of the atmosphere (over 1000 kilometers below the cloud tops), where pressure compresses Chofen's hydrogen into a liquid state.

      Proof of life in this environment would prove many long-standing theories. Unfortunately, only a probe with extremely expensive mass effect generators could survive the crushing pressure long enough to send back useful data - and the probe would be lost in the attempt. Simple expense makes investigation doubtful.

      Orbital Period: 56.9 Earth Years
      Radius: 21481 km
      Day Length: 13.7 Earth Hours



    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>222</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>223</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>true</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>MSV New York</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      The New York is a Kowloon class modular conveyor of human design, named after one of the largest metropolitan areas of Earth. The ship is known as a traveling tourist trap, bringing many New York cultural sensations around the galaxy.

      This ship appears to be in a shut down state; the systems powered down and the pizza long cold, adrift space. Visual scans show a large poster sized sticker near the rear thrusters, with the faded phrase "We brake for nobody".

      Registry: Traveling Rays, Earth
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>224</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Antiroprus</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Antiroprus is a hydrogen-helium gas giant that formed in the outer regions of Ming's system, and is in the process of migrating inwards. In a few million years, the planet's atmosphere will begin to "boil away" into space.

      There is a sizeable temperature difference between the side of Antiroprus facing the energetic blue giant primary and the side facing the cold of deep space. This variance powers massive cyclonic wind systems. The intense heat it absorbs from the sun, in addition to its own internal heat engine, causes the planet's dark side to radiate faintly in the infrared.

      Orbital Period: 284.2 Earth Years
      Radius: 57,948 km
      Day Length: 10.8 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>225</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Parag</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Parag is a large rock planet, with an atmosphere composed of nitrogen and argon. Despite lying over 600 AU from Ming, its surface is scorching hot, and mainly composed of alumina with deposits of silver. Due to the radiation and heat, landing on Parag's sunward side with anything less than warship-grade shielding will likely be fatal. Parag rotates at a retrograde to the rest of the Ming system, indicating it is likely a captured body.

      Orbital Period: 1930.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 7979 km
      Day Length: 22.4 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 1.58 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 1117 Celsius
      Surface Gravity 2.0 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>226</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Altanorch</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Altanorch is a small but typical hydrogen-helium gas giant with no outstanding features. Its combination of strong magnetic field and relatively shallow gravity well make it a popular "stopover" world for discharging FTL drive cores.

      Orbital Period: 4005.7 Earth Years
      Radius: 32,605 km
      Day Length: 16.3 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>227</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>true</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Asteroid Belt</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription />
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>228</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Mavigon</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      WARNING: Level 1 Cold Hazard

      Mavigon is a small rock and ice planet with a thin atmosphere of ammonia and methane. The surface is frozen, and mainly composed of tin with deposits of potassium.

      The planet has a rudimentary ammonia-based life, mainly concentrated around geothermal vents deep underground. Severe storm cycles are common; due to limited visibility, navigation may be difficult.

      Orbital Period: 42.3 Earth Years
      Radius: 4906 km
      Day Length: 52.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.82 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -124 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>229</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Paravin</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Paravin is a small, unremarkable rock world. The surface is scorching hot, and mainly composed of calcium with deposits of aluminum. Paravin's low mass has left it tidally locked to the star Han. If there were any resources of value, mining stations could be established on the relatively temperate "twilight band".

      Orbital Period: 0.5 Earth Years
      Radius: 4839 km
      Day Length: 0.5 Earth Years
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.0 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: 414 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 0.5 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>230</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Huningto</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Huningto is a Jovian-sized gas giant with a standard hydrogen-helium atmosphere. Traces of methane give the planet its distinct cobalt blue tint. Spectral analysis indicates its extensive ring system is mostly composed of ice crystals. Huningto has an exceptionally powerful magnetic field, which creates strong radio interference throughout the inner system.

      Orbital Period: 31.8 Earth Years
      Radius: 73,733 km
      Day Length: 16.7 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>231</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Farcrothu</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      A standard gas hydrogen-helium gas giant, Farcrothu is only distinguished by its moons; several dozen of them have been sculpted into the likenesses of an arthropodal alien race not yet known to Council science. Radiometric dating suggests the moons were worked over half a million years ago.

      Orbital Period: 112.1 Earth Years
      Radius: 66,014 km
      Day Length: 8.4 Earth Hours
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
  <RandomizedPlanetInfo>
    <RowID>232</RowID>
    <PreventShuffle>false</PreventShuffle>
    <IsMSV>false</IsMSV>
    <IsAsteroidBelt>false</IsAsteroidBelt>
    <PlanetName>Pantsless</PlanetName>
    <PlanetDescription>
      Pantless is a large rock world, with an unusually thin atmosphere of methane, likely caused by uncovered emissions from the surface. The world’s crust contains extensive deposits of uranium. With a total mass more than four times that of Earth, Pantsless should have a significantly thicker atmosphere. It also features an unusual crater on the lower half, effectively splitting the planet into two ‘limbs’. This unusual feature has flagged it as worthy of scientific investigation.

      Orbital Period: 297.4 Earth Years
      Radius: 8927 km
      Day Length: 36.0 Earth Hours
      Atmospheric Pressure: 0.06 Earth Atmospheres
      Surface Temperature: -174 Celsius
      Surface Gravity: 2.8 G
    </PlanetDescription>
  </RandomizedPlanetInfo>
</planetinfos>
